SPEAKER_00: We're back for day three and today we're shipping our company. And so if this is the first time you're tuning in, we are building a company in 72 hours at the Grokbot Galaxy event in San Francisco. Just a quick round of intros if this is the first time you're joining us. I'm Matt. I work in developer experience at SpaceX AI.
SPEAKER_01: Hello, I'm Potato, also known as Lauren. And I work on Grokbot at SpaceX AI.
SPEAKER_02: I'm Roshan. I work on product at SpaceX AI on Grokbot, some other stuff too. So
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. And so if you're joining us from yesterday, we've done actually quite a bit overnight because Lauren set up a bit of a software factory. But before we jump into that software factory, I think we have an announcement for y'all. And that is if you sign up, if you're new users, you haven't used Grokbot before, you don't have an account, you sign up in the next 10 minutes, you can get a month for free. So new users get one month free of Grokbot and that kind of starts right now. So you'll see a clock below. So go online, registered and then you also have to create what is the we have to create a bot?
SPEAKER_02: You have to download Grokbot, you have to create an account, and you have to set up a recurring task. And Potato is going to tweet about some examples for how you could do this, like searching through your emails, any other routines that we love, keeping an eye on GitHub issues.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, like looking at Slack, you know, things that things that take a lot of take up a lot of your time are great to automate and you can just tell your Grokbot to like, hey, check my emails every day and I'll set it up for you. So very very easy.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, we have a QR code here if you want to get my screen up on the stream that we're showing. It's one free month of Grokbot, valid for new accounts only. So if you've been watching these past two days, but for some reason haven't signed up on your own, eight minutes and 20 seconds left from that timer down there for you to claim a free month of Grokbot. I think it includes a lot of credits too, right? It's like a pretty good free month.
SPEAKER_00: Like you get 200 bucks like of usage in the first month. So
SPEAKER_02: Awesome. Okay. $200 in value, free month of our highest tier.
SPEAKER_01: It's a lot of usage.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, we'll have to see how much usage we we used over the last few days.
SPEAKER_00: Awesome. So yeah, you got 9 minutes to take care of it. And I I feel like we can maybe spend actually 7 minutes. Time goes by pretty quickly. I feel like we can maybe spend some of that time talking through what we built last night and where things are at.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Roshan, do you want to maybe show off some of the I think we we made a lot of changes for our game. But maybe to start like maybe we should talk about like what our game is for people who are just tuning in.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, let's start by Yeah, I think that's a great idea. So for those who are just tuning in, we are building a game studio and launching our first game today imminently in the next few hours. I think we have a little bit of Paula if we want to get in before we get it all out out there to the world. But we are building a game and we have a team of really an army of Grokbots that we've been using to build this game with. Towards the tail end of the afternoon yesterday, we put together a team of bots that are basically helping create a software factory here. And so you're looking at my copy of this factory that was inspired by some of the bot templates that Lauren shared with me. And I don't know, Lauren, do you want to maybe talk through some of the the ways the factory works? I can show some show some of this while you're doing that.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, so so for for a start like I think the factory is pretty interesting where what Roshan and I did was basically we we did a lot of brainstorming last night about like game mechanics and just thinking through polish and how we want the game to actually be fun. So we initially started with a game that kind of felt like one v one rock paper scissor game with like Elo and and you know like a scoring system and a leaderboard. And then when we played it, we found that it was not really that fun. So we got inspired by some of the other games that we enjoy. And we kind of, you know, got inspired by some of those mechanics and we and we we crafted some plans together with Grokbot and Cloud Agents. And then we used P Stack, which is my personal set of of skills. It's a cursor plugin and a Grokbot plugin. And in that plugin, there is a skill called Potato Mode. And Potato Mode is a skill that essentially teaches your bots to be much more rigorous and much more you know basically much better at orchestrating other bots and agents. And yeah, that that's it right there on the screen. And one of the cool things about P Stack is if you type slash Potato Mode and you say full autopilot this plan, it will actually go off and break down that plan into lots of different small phases. And then basically set up a mini factory where you know the the you have like agents that implement the PR, the small PRs. You have agents that go off and verify, they'll run your application, they'll fuzz it where you know they just actually click around and test it, you know, find bugs and basically give you a ton of trust so you can actually just merge the the PRs will just auto merge themselves in full autopilot mode because of that rigorous verification and and checks being done. So overnight, I think we landed like more than 100 PRs so far.
SPEAKER_02: I think we're at 150 now. 145 is a
SPEAKER_00: You should look at what's closed. We're over where they at like 170.
SPEAKER_02: Really? Okay.
SPEAKER_00: 160, 170, something like that.
SPEAKER_01: Let's see. Let's see. Yeah, 160
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah. So we did we did all all sorts of like like you know revamping the UI, upgrading our backend and making sure it was like you know good security and it can handle the load, I hope.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, fingers crossed.
SPEAKER_00: Well, we'll find out hopefully. I wanted to show kind of a little bit of that in action. So this is my I just merged 124, which was a UI rewrite that we were working on and rebasing a few times over the last few hours. And you can kind of see how the bots communicate with each other in action. You have sort of I have a bot here whose name is Play, whose job is to basically be a play tester. As you can imagine, any good game needs a QA team. Well, we don't have a QA team. We had an intern yesterday, but that intern is not with us today. And so we have a we have a QA bot whose job it is to basically look at each PR. And this is using one of those subscriptions we talked about where you can create a recurring task or respond to an event. And looks at each PR. And anytime it sees a PR that looks like it is green on our CI suite, we'll just jump in and play test it and go through the UI, drive the entire game end to end, knows how the game engine works and will provide any feedback on what might need to be changed before we you know merge that PR. And you can see have all of our bots coordinating here to get all that work done. It's pretty cool.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I really love routines in Grokbot because you you like again like going back to this factory concept. Well, first of all, I actually don't really even like the term factory, but I guess it's like the closest you know analogy of something that's very automated. And I think a lot of us, even if you don't do engineering work, there's so many tasks that we do that are so repetitive. Like I, for example, am very bad at checking my emails. I just get so lazy at at doing that. It's you know I I it's almost like I'm consciously avoiding it because I I'm I'm dreading how much time and effort it takes to like go through and like, oh, this one's spam, you know, like, oh, I have to reply to this one and like I I don't even know what I I need to reply. So Grokbot can kind of you can teach it how to like go through your inbox, it can go through Slack, it can go through GitHub PRs. Basically anything you can imagine, you can automate with Grokbot. So definitely check out you know the check out Grokbot and ask your bot to to help you out with those.
SPEAKER_00: So we we got by the way 2 minutes and 20 seconds on the promo here. So if you're a new user, you sign up for Grokbot and then you know you perform you you set up a recurring task. So create an account, set up a recurring task, you get a month free of Grokbot. And if I was just, you know if I was just to summarize maybe what I'm hearing is that it sounds like essentially what we're trying to do with this like software factory concept, which might be kind of ambiguous, is like a set up really good feedback loops for agents to be able to do work themselves. And that means removing the manual steps that we would normally have to do, clicking through UIs, validating that things work, looking at logs. If you pass all the right information, the right context to an agent, you might be able to automate those things. And the same way we can do that for software development, we can do that for things like email or other you know business operations functions. And that's kind of what it means, right, to build a company with AI. It's like break down all these human workflows, isolate them, and then figure out how you can have an agent that does all this stuff that an agent should do, right? Maybe an agent shouldn't be sending emails for you, but it can get rid of all the spam, it can unsubscribe you from lists, and then it can send you an email that you need to look at, help you come up with a draft and make that process a bit more smooth. Right?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, you paired perfectly.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, cool. It's cuz when I hear factory, I'm like, I don't know
SPEAKER_01: I know. I don't like that term either, but I think it yeah, it's a it's a term that I think like a lot of people use. Um we have like about a minute left for the one month free. So definitely download it.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, and while you while you guys are talking, I'm firing off a few bots to do some uh some additional UI polish on what we've built. Um
SPEAKER_01: Should we should we show show off the UI for a little bit?
SPEAKER_00: Are we ready? There's there's still some scrolling issues.
SPEAKER_01: I feel like if we're not embarrassed by it, if like then we you know we've launched to to may want to hide the the bar to put it in full screen.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, there's definitely some Yeah, there's some work that we've done to Yeah, let me do that now. Um Okay, let let's take a look.
SPEAKER_01: Can we see Roshan's screen?
SPEAKER_00: Let's take a look. Um we have a we have a sponsorship form on the main page that I think we'll need to we'll need to move out or refactor. But
SPEAKER_01: I can find so many as well.
SPEAKER_00: Yes, there we go. Um so yeah, zooming in a little bit. Here's our game. We have a we're a code name calling it Cupcake, a real name drop coming soon. So if you want to if you want to see what it's called when we launch this, stay tuned. Um we've have signing with Twitter support working, which is really cool. We have a global leaderboard. So right now it's just Potato and I who've been play testing the game, but hopefully you all will be able to jump in soon. We actually added a guest mode last night, which lets us uh lets anyone kind of jump in and try the game before signing in. So we're going to see if we can get that live and hopefully our database can handle the load. And let's see here. Uh yeah, so we have basically like a card based little battler game that we ended up with with little cute art styles that are inspired by our bots. Actually the PR that we was just kicking off while we were talking is to to adjust some of the art styles here. So this looks a little bit more like a card with the art filling up more of the page. But you can see these bots have sort of stats that they get they get assigned. And so we have a pool of these bots. And the concept of the game is basically that you choose your lineup and then over the course of a couple of rounds are pitted head to head against another player all sort of you know with with a matchmaking system and all that as well. And so you're catching me mid game here. Clearly some polish stuff here that our our factory is cranking on. But I think this is pretty fun. I think there's some really cool strategy elements to it where you're sort of like trying to make a a lineup that you think is going to win. It looks like I
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah, I won that round.
SPEAKER_01: at the start of every round as well, you get like some gold. I think we we we might want to rename that to like a token or something.
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah, we should do that. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: But the idea is like you have this shop where you can buy bots, you can buy power ups for your lineup. You you only have 10 gold to start. But you know you can add a new bot, you can sell bots that you don't want. They each have a different ability and skill that does something different. And then that's how you kind of play the game and put some strategy in it and and go on until you win all three rounds. And actually fun fact is that all of the bots here are real bots from the bot marketplace, the Grokbot marketplace. So we got I think there's like at least 70 of them that we found.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And we generated avatars for all of them, unique ones. And so it's kind of small right now, but well you have a lot of UI polish to do as you can see.
SPEAKER_00: I think our bots will be able to take care of it though. I think I think we know exactly what we need to change. Some CSS issues here, some clipping issues. Um but hey, I just won that one. So thanks for the thanks for the Elo bump. Yeah, there we go. Number one on the leaderboard, first time. I've been in second place in the leaderboard the entire day. We've been testing this all day.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Exactly. Oh no, damn it. You're climbing climbing the leaderboard. I got to I got to catch up.
SPEAKER_00: Um yeah, we have some tears here too. So yeah, hopefully we'll give you a chance to compete to to make it to the platinum tier, which would be really fun.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. And if you're just joining us, you you might have missed the first 10 minutes where we gave away free Grokbot Ultra. But I think I'm going to try to convince uh the team that maybe you know when we launch the game, if you know for the we have a leaderboard, it'd be really cool if we gave away more Ultra plans for like people on the top of the leaderboard. So let let me see what I can do. I'll try to convince Yeah, I I I'll I'll try to convince our team whether we can do that.
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah. Oh okay. See what we can do.
SPEAKER_01: Um but yeah, very excited to get that done.
SPEAKER_00: Amazing. Yeah, I guess maybe before so we're we're going to just to give you guys a bit of a of what's going to happen in the next few minutes here. So at 9:00 a.m. Pacific in about 6 minutes here, we're going to cut over to the main stage. So for those of you who have not been following along for the three days, we're doing a bunch of stuff. It's all happening live in person. We are here in San Francisco just like a half block away from all of the Dreamforce festivities. And so we have a streaming studio upstairs in this space where we've been building and and cranking away. We also have a main stage downstairs where we've been doing talks about how you can use Grokbot for like every part of your business. Uh and so we've been cutting out to those streams and actually bringing that content into building our own business. Uh so we're going to cut over to one of those talks in just a few minutes uh and get give you all a chance to hear about how you can use Grokbot for marketing and marketing operations. And then we'll bring marketing operations up here to chat with chat with our colleague to to go into how we do that for our for our launch. So hopefully we can kind of tie and gain gain some of that knowledge. Well, what are we going to do off camera? So I think we should maybe give the viewers a bit of a plan for what we'll do in the next hour or so before we're back on stream. Um I know I want to take care of some UI polish. I feel like that's going to be my focus.
SPEAKER_01: Well, for my factory spent I guess my team of bots spent a lot of time last night working on the backend and and making sure we are secure and hopefully performant enough to handle a lot of players at the same time. So I think I will do some more testing of that. Make sure we can actually you know launch.
SPEAKER_00: Load tests. Hopefully lots and lots of load tests.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I might help all of the UI polish too cuz actually I'm a very like I I do a lot of like client and UI work. So I'm always get like nerd sniped by UI things cuz I think yeah, like the feel of the game is like so important, right, to to make it fun. So I want to definitely do that.
SPEAKER_00: Sweet. And then I have some user feedback loops. So ideally we'll have a way for you guys to submit feature requests, submit what you like, what you don't like. And then we'll show how we can collect that information, store it safely, surface it to the team, and then implement kind of what we think is important, which I think is you know collecting user feedback and understanding what people are saying is is essential to product development. So Well, one thing that I think we want to do over the course of the day is actually continue to update the app. And so we're not going to just launch this and walk away. We're going to I think we have a really long roadmap already. Last night actually before we cut out, we spent some time doing audio design. And we have a bot had a bot whose job it was to help us with audio engineering. And so we can revisit that bot. We haven't had a chance to prioritize music yet, but I think we can end up with some really cool tracks that we generated with Suno. And so maybe we work some of that in, maybe a stretch goal for our launch. But hopefully afterwards we can add some music. We promise we won't make it annoying. Be nice nice great music. He has a ton of stuff there. We had a bot who is off doing some 3D prototyping for how we might make the whole animation system more 3D and make our characters more 3D. And so I think it'd be great to revisit that idea if we can. So yeah, a bunch of ideas that we can kind of cook with over the course of the day. And I think we'll have a lot to do. So
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I'd love to see you know ideas in the chat as well like if you I guess caught caught a glimpse of our game and you have suggestions on UI polish or you know questions about mechanics or I don't know, any any any cool suggestions would be would be fun to to to read. And then also I think I want to actually shout out production team because today we have a very special I guess live stream because we have the like a live agenda and our bots up on the screen, which is super cool. So Steve right there. Oh you just missed it. Steve is my chief of staff bot who is running the show. Uh who is who's cup who's bot is Cupcake Ange?
SPEAKER_00: That's my bot.
SPEAKER_01: Oh that's your bot.
SPEAKER_00: And I also renamed my chief of staff bot to Steve because I was giving Matt Herman Slack yesterday for having his name chief of staff. And then my bot was named chief of staff. And I was like too much too many chief of staff.
SPEAKER_01: Oh no, well we can't have the same name though. You need something else.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, I can change my What's a good What's a good name for a chief of staff bot if not Steve?
SPEAKER_01: I don't know.
SPEAKER_00: What about Steve N?
SPEAKER_01: What about Yeah, I don't know.
SPEAKER_00: It's too late. It's Steven now.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I don't know. And Bake I guess is Roshan.
SPEAKER_00: And now look, we have notes from production coming through on the screen.
SPEAKER_01: Love that. Yeah, it's like every day we're we're building a business, our production team's building a production company. There's just a lot of like cool building and evolution happening here.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Um amazing. Amazing. Well, I think we're 3 minutes away from our first talk of the day. Uh that's going to be Grokbot for marketing operations. If you're just joining us, this is day three uh launch day of building a business in 3 days. We're building a gaming studio and launching our first game really really soon. Uh and we'll have a little more to share on that very very quickly here. We're excited to open this up and give everyone a chance to start playing and helping us improve it so we can feed put your feedback into our automated feature factory that we've built. So really excited to get into that. Uh yeah, I think we have some plans for the next few hours.
SPEAKER_01: Oh no, is that an error we need to fix?
SPEAKER_00: This is an error on my side that we need to fix. So it looks like I don't know if it it works for your account. I'm down on logging with X. So we got some work to do in the next hour here and we're going to get on it.
SPEAKER_02: Pieces are there. I I feel good. I feel good. The pieces are there.
SPEAKER_00: Awesome.
SPEAKER_01: Cool.
SPEAKER_00: We uh we're I guess we're going down down downstairs. Maybe we got we got a minute. So I'm going to basically what I'm doing is when I see an error like this, I'm sure Lauren has a way of that automated this already. I'm kind of like looking to see what's going on on the server side and then maybe passing that off to Grokbot um and letting it know that
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I mean you can even um tell Grokbot to open that and it's
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: it's for you. Um and so there's really no limitation to the work that you can hand off to it and I think this will only become more true over time as the models improve. And so um as I mentioned, uh there's really that ease of use that you get with GrokBot. Um you have these always on agents where you no longer have to worry for any of you uh who are out there who are maybe doing work at an inconvenient time but you can't close your laptop because if you do then the agent is going to stop working. You don't have that concern here. And really when you combine all these primitives together, you get to a place where in this really natural way you talk to your bots, you know the access that they have. Um they're really intelligent. They can keep working around the clock and produce um some really high value outputs for you. So I'm really excited particularly for this audience um to share a few use cases that I have personally that the RevOps and MarOps team internally at SpaceX AI has for using GrokBot to do our work more effectively. So first a quick show of hands for people here in person. How many of you are on your RevOps or MarOps team at your company? Anyone working on GTM engineering, GTM systems? Okay. Workflows, processes, automations. I'm sort of speaking the same language as all you. Seeing some nods in the audience. Well what's really exciting about GrokBot for RevOps and MarOps is um I can sort of go through all of these. Some of these I'm going to demo in just a second. But if I had to call out just one to really highlight about how a tool like GrokBot changes the nature of our work is we can finally build tools and not just rules. So often times when you're in these roles that are inherently about cross-functional collaboration and aligning stakeholders, uh so much of the job is just like communicating communicating information out, hoping that people follow guidelines for like the right way to set up a campaign, the right way to get something tracked. But finally with a tool like GrokBot we can all think of ourselves as much more technical to the point where we're not just setting out the guidelines for hey if someone at the company wants to get XYZ campaign done, they have to follow this checklist and instead we can set up the infrastructure, the like internal apps where those teams can do the work. And the apps are just set up to respect those rules in the first place. And so you can sort of think of the marketing and sales teams as playing a game that you are designing as that sort of back office ops team. But really across all of these use cases that we're highlighting here um there are there's really so much to do uh that that really fundamentally changes the nature of the work. And so uh I want to walk all of you through a demo of some specific ways that I use GrokBot um to highlight a couple of those use cases from the prior slide. And before we do that I just want to introduce you to my team of bots. So there are some obscure references here with uh the names of my bots. Uh I don't know if by any chance there are any Radiohead fans out there in the audience. Amazing. So maybe you would understand the reference to uh owned over there. It's a beloved instrument. Uh but all of these are sort of references to music devices. Uh in another life I might have pursued that passion a bit more but now I can um use do that with my bots. Uh and so we've got OP1 my sort of synthesizer chief of staff um who drives a lot of my work. We've got Fisher which is sort of the like receiver of all the information from across my inboxes, email, calendar, text messages, Slack. Juno is my product manager bot um that sort of helps me think through corner cases, product requirements when I'm going out and thinking of tools that I want to build for our marketing and sales teams. It helps me really think through all the implications and build the right thing in the first place. And then owned is my engineer bot. Um so it has a really clear sense of our systems, how they interact with each other, things like the CRM and our data warehouse and our existing codebase and how we build internal tools at SpaceX AI. Um and so uh what you'll see in a second here in our demo is first I want to show you um what I call the self-completing task list. Uh so this to me I'm sort of a productivity nerd um for over half a decade I've been building my own internal systems for getting work done more efficiently because especially in a role like RevOps or MarOps, as I said earlier so much of it is just stakeholder management. You are getting so many messages from so many different places, trying to make sense of it, trying to understand what is truly high priority. Um and finally with a tool like GrokBot what you can do is you can set up these bots to monitor all your inboxes and help you distil okay of all these messages you've received, things that showed up on your calendar, which of these are actual tasks versus which of these are just FYIs or things that we can safely ignore. Um and so what we'll do here is we can see my bots have already been active in the background. So Fisher, the sort of executive assistant or receiver agent that's tapped in to all my inboxes. Um we can see today at 9:04 a.m. um it completed this ongoing routine that it has. You can see um over here. It has this regular routine that it runs on a schedule where it checks all my inboxes and picks out whatever is new. And then it proactively um actually like while I was giving this talk messaged OP1. Again that's my chief of staff agent. And it gave it the rundown of across email, calendar, work chat, all the information that came my way. And so this alone is such an unlock in terms of knowing like I can even if I wanted to I could turn notifications off on Slack, on email. And I would just know that in the background my bots are monitoring those channels for me and surfacing to me the things that are most important that should really take away my attention. Um and that alone um really cuts down on the context switching for me and really helps me get into much more of a focus mode in my work and just be a lot happier um in my work. So really really cool, right? That alone changes the game and then what you see here is Fisher is receiving this information. It's proactively telling my chief of staff hey here's what's new. And then my chief of staff is distilling that down into um the actual tasks and subtasks that I was able to identify from that input. So right sometimes you get messages and you don't actually have to act on them. Sometimes you get messages and you have to act on them but you can't really tell just by reading the message alone like what's really going on here. And so with bot what you can do is it reads the message, it reads the entire Slack exchange and it sort of distils for you like hey I think here's what that person is asking for. Um and so it just makes your life so much easier. Now here's the really cool thing is this is where we get to the self-completing part of the of the self-completing task list is um my two bots Fisher and OP1 are working together to identify tasks. And then OP1 identifies one of those tasks, looks like there's a territory dispute. A couple AEs have some disagreements about who should work a given account. And what OP1 can do is relay that task to another bot that I have which is a territory planning bot. It can give it context on what's going on. And then that territory planner bot who has full information on our rules of engagement, um how we set out different territories, all the context from our CRM. That bot is able to complete a pretty good first draft of of that task of what um deliverable is needed to complete that task. And so uh I didn't even have to think about you know what what we should do about this territory dispute. Of course I can always come in and validate the work and make sure that it actually makes sense. Um but it's really amazing to think that like I I have a team. I truly have a team. A team that is monitoring my inboxes, distilling the tasks, relaying those tasks to the right other teammates who can get them done for me. And then I just come in and sort of oversee the whole process um and and finalize things. So that's demo one. Demo two is really how I was able to build um what to put it in a pithy way is a dating app for leads that we use internally at SpaceX AI where you know often uh for those of you in the audience who know what I'm talking about, marketing and sales handoff is like such a classic issue in companies where marketing is producing all these leads, sales people are like I don't really love these leads, I don't want to have to work them. So they're just sitting there, getting stale. You don't really have a feedback loop where marketing can refine their targeting to give sales more of the kind of leads that they want. And the whole process is just broken. And so uh I sort of identified a better way to handle the marketing sales handoff which is what if every AE could log into an app and they would just see the leads that they own. They can swipe left to end those leads. When they end those leads they have to give a specific ended reason. When they hit submit it actually writes back to the CRM in all the correct ways. When they swipe right they can add that uh prospect. They can add that lead directly into a follow-up sequence. And so this is what I mean when earlier on I said this really transforms what we can do as someone on RevOps or MarOps where all of a sudden we're not um just talking about SLAs and making sure that the sales teams abide by the SLAs and hey why aren't you working these leads and okay let me relay that anecdotal information about these leads back to the marketing team. Instead we just set up the game for the teams to play. They play that game and we get a lot of really valuable information on okay why are these leads being ended? How can we sort of programmatically feed that back into the marketing teams to improve the targeting and give sales more of the leads they like? How can we make it as easy as possible for sales people so that this is something fun that they want to get to inbox zero with their leads every day. So the way that we did this was um I basically told my product manager bot I want to build an internal app for sales reps to review their leads. Um I gave it a rough idea of the mechanics for the app, some extra things that I want. And most importantly from the start we really want to get this off flow with our CRM right um because that's sort of the most critical thing. We want people sales people to be able to log in and see the leads they own and make sure that we're writing uh information back into the CRM properly. So what happens when I send this message is Juno is a really good thought partner for me. Um so I have this rough idea for an app. And with prior AI tools what might have happened is the AI really wants to please me. It really wants to do a good job. And so right away it jumps into okay I'm starting the coding process. Here it is. And maybe it doesn't look like what you envisioned. Maybe it doesn't work like what you envisioned. Maybe it anchored too much on what you had in that first prompt. And so in a way you're sort of scared to use the AI and overthinking like did I get that prompt right? Did I need to give it more detail in the first place? Oh no now it's running away and building the wrong thing. What GrokBot does is it takes a second, it asks you follow-up questions. Really good follow-up questions. Things that I didn't necessarily think about when I first had the idea for this app. And so we can answer these questions. We'll see it. It'll ask a few more. We can go through this process. Let's see. I want to show people only their new leads, no additional filters. We want to make sure okay so this is a really good question. When a lead when a lead is accepted, what should change in the CRM? Now what I want to tell bot is actually we shouldn't change any fields in the CRM when a lead is accepted because the real moment that the lead status changes is when the rep reaches out. We already have an automation for tracking that activity and updating the lead status. So we're really getting in the weeds here and AI is the the AI the GrokBot is really prompting me to think more deeply about my idea and to say hey you know what that's a good point. I'm not just answering questions mindlessly but I'm really thinking through some of the implications here. Let's do reason and optional notes. And there will probably be just one or two more questions that it'll ask. Let's see. Offline actions. Great question. Let's queue and confirm before done. So then we'll see that this product manager bot will come up with a spec for our product. And not only that but let's do let's do local only here. Not only will it come up with the spec but what we'll see in just a second is well I won't spoil anything. So we can see it's drafting the product spec. And actually it's sort of giving it away. So what Juno is going to do for me is it's going to write this spec and then proactively hand it off to owned our engineering bot to actually get the build started. And again I think the really magical thing here is I didn't have to prompt Juno to do that. Um often when you're using AI tools, if you even get to this point of thought partnership and producing really good quality outputs um you have to take those outputs and like send them into the right new system. Um if you even have a consistent bot that you go to that just does your engineering work. And here you can again really think of it as a team that's working on your behalf to get things done end to end. So it messaged, owned, it has this product spec ready for the engineering to begin. And now we can see that our engineer is off to work. And now sort of cooking demo style I'll show you uh what the finished product looks like um since I won't bore you with all the details of owned doing the build. But what we've got here this is all fake data so no worries here. Um this is just a mockup of the real interface that I was able to build with GrokBot and that many of our reps now use on a daily basis to get their reviewed leads down to zero. And so we've got uh all this information available at a glance about the lead. Um we can simply put the card to the left to end that lead. We can uh swipe to the right and we can put that lead in a sequence. We can see more information about how the lead came in in the first place. And it just works. Already since introducing this new app to our sales reps which by the way went from idea to implementation in just two weeks. The live build time was really 10 hours and then a lot of the other time was spent just introducing people to this tool, um getting them familiar with it, gathering more feedback and and feature requests. Um in the two weeks since we've adopted this on the team, we've seen our leads reviewed rate shoot up. Um the AEs love it. Marketing teams love it because they're finally getting high quality feedback from sellers on how they can improve targeting. Um and we can see how working with GrokBot really elevates what we can do. Like you know show of hands out there in the audience. How many of you feel like without AI you would be able to build a product like this? Amazing. Okay. Right? We got we got one hand. Now I would say with AI and especially after seeing this demo, how many of you feel like you could pretty confidently go into a chat with AI and build this or any other internal tool that your team needs? Amazing. Amazing. I'm seeing a lot of hands now. Um and that was exactly me. I I really joined this team with a lot of ideas for how we could improve processes, with a lot of specialized knowledge around specific tools where I just knew the menus and buttons to use. But I'm at a point now where what I'm using more than anything is just my brain to really think critically about what do we need as a team um and how we can be more efficient. So um now I really want to distil what we learned from that demo. And uh really some of the big lessons are if you were able to hire a full team, if someone came to you and said you have had count to hire a full team of people reporting to you, who would be on it? Really what GrokBot does is it democratizes in a way that CEO life. Anyone can hire an unlimited set of specialists with the right context and access. I think this is really powerful for our day-to-day in terms of just dreaming bigger about what we can each do for the teams that we're on. The next lesson is really to trust your bots, give them agency, and at the same time give them guardrails. So there's something really powerful about knowing really confidently all the access that your bots have, all the things that they can do for you um because that helps you entrust them with bigger and bigger tasks. But at the same time knowing that things aren't going to go too far off the rails because they'll always come back to you before they ship anything. Messages, writing back to the CRM, pushing PRs. And I think GrokBot really helps you achieve that balance between pushing AI tools to the limit and then running into issues or feeling like I don't really know what access it has. I don't know how helpful it can really be. So I haven't really started using it yet. The final thing and this is really I think more of a call to action than anything for those of you out in the audience whose role is similar to mine is think of yourselves not as just the people setting rules, processes but really you are a product manager and your product is revenue growth. I am extremely excited about where the RevOps, MarOps, GTM engineering, GTM systems, whatever you want to call it, where this profession is headed. And I think that's particularly relevant with Dreamforce going on this week is all of us are thinking about the systems that our GTM efforts are built on. And I think in this new world where all of us have access to tools like GrokBot, it means we can think of ourselves as identifying any bottlenecks to growth and getting rid of them. That's our job day in and day out. It's just talking to teams, doing the human thing, forming relationships, building trust, distilling what needs to be built to help the teams grow more effectively, operate more effectively, and then going and building those things. So that's it for the main presentation. Um we're going to have some time for questions next. Um thank you so much for joining. All right. So we have some people with microphones.
SPEAKER_01: My check, my check, my check, my check.
SPEAKER_02: So WhatsApp is a nice tool for marketing, right? WhatsApp.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: And I'm able to get WhatsApp working on GrokBot by connecting with my own personal one. Is there a connector that makes it easier to do in some way? What's what's your suggestion for me working with WhatsApp with GrokBot?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Um I'm not sure if uh we have a connector on the way that's native to WhatsApp. Um there are other tools I use. Uh this is not to particularly promote one over others but sort of speaking personally uh there's a tool called Beeper that I'm not sure if you're familiar with but it's basically like a mega chat app that you can log into all your separate messaging apps. Um and you can actually install that on your bot's computer. So again this is a really magical thing about GrokBot is you don't need to have native connections to anything. Um you can just go into GrokBot's computer, install whatever app you want um and then it can use those apps just like you would. And I presume the same might be true for the WhatsApp app. Ah okay. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Seems to be these kind of like middleware connectors to like Meta or something. Like you know we spend a lot on Meta and Google but having those just natively like you know easy authenticate connect I think is like a massive unlock because it keeps just logging out, right? Uh but do you have an idea on like the kind of roadmap for when those will come online or yeah?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. So there are certain things that I'm not able to go into uh just in terms of what's on the way but one thing that we did announce just yesterday is a one password integration. Um so you're able to share your password vault with your bot. Um and what you could do if you're really open to it is you could set up a routine for a given bot to um like sort of track whether the token is still active, whether the login is still active on a tool. And if you need to re-auth um then you can have it re-auth for you using what's in the one password vault.
SPEAKER_01: Okay because I think like yeah the key insight at least for like us too is like we want like let's say Meta or it's search ads, uh we want it to monitor how the ad's doing, increase decrease spend and then potentially create a new ad you know because it can. Like it's actually like I have it building ads that I have to manually post but then if it could start running in that circle that's like our our dream state.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah and I think it's really about breaking down into you know the the other really um appealing thing to me about this particular perch in looking at all these developments in AI is like fundamentally what our role is about is understanding systems and processes and workflows to begin with. Um I think that's true even before the world of AI is we're sort of always bringing that systems approach to how does this get done and how can it get done even better. And I think by leaning into that tendency that we already have um we can help the AI tools codify those those processes into these like actual automations that are running on our behalf. And so when I think about automating complex jobs end to end, I spent a lot of time thinking about like okay what are the fundamental like blocks
SPEAKER_00: like blocks of doing this task. Um so maybe the first chunk is like being able to log into that platforms and look at the analytics. And then the second chunk is and download a report. And then the second chunk is okay now look at that data in the context of all the other data we have and so on and so forth. So I think the better that you are even in a non-AI world at breaking things down and like writing detailed instructions for how to do things um the better off you'll be building bots around them because like you can give it clarity. You can sort of have separate specialized bots for each portion of the job and then have them all work in tandem like you saw before.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I have a question. So if the bot just keep evolving, what do you think would be the market stack that's going to disappear first? And how do you think about like the relationship between bots and human?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. I think of it I really think of it a lot as a mirror. Um often times when I'm talking to bots especially in one of those um thought partnership sessions like you saw with the Q&A um I think of the bot as of course in some ways it's influencing how I think about what I'm trying to do. Um so like it might bring up certain aspects of the build for that app that I didn't think of myself. But ultimately it's then prompting me to do that thinking and I'm like huh okay yeah good point. And and now I'm thinking about it. Now I'm really engaged with it. And now my engagement with that thought breeds more thoughts and more ideas and then I just share that with the bot and then it has more context to work off of. And so you can think of it as like if nothing else you're sort of like thinking out loud with these bots um and they're giving you they're you know in some ways we prompt AI. In some ways AI is prompting us to think more deeply about what we're trying to accomplish with it. Um so that's what I think about like the relationship um between me and the bot or any one who uses Grokbot. Um in terms of the stack that I think will go away I it's sort of hard to say. I think um there will probably still be many instances of like it's really good to just understand the right buttons to click and menus to navigate to use certain complex tools. Um but I think something that's sort of happened especially with coding is like the barrier to entry is so much lower. Um I think the engineering profession had this sort of reckoning over the past few years that more and more professions are going to start to have with the introductions of these kind of tools around like okay what do I do if my role is no longer just being the gatekeeper of this like really complicated looking code that no one else understands? Like now all of a sudden anyone can produce that code. And so what's the value add of an engineer? There is a value add. There definitely is. But that value add is more about that higher level thinking, that intuitive feel for the systems. And so I think it's helpful to really get to know the tools deeply because of similar to before like what it prompts you to think about. Like no one really wants to be a master at navigating menus. But there's something about that tedious work that really makes you slow down and think about what you're trying to do in those complex tools just like AI also prompts you to slow down and think. So I think that is what's going to remain. I think using complex tools to the extent that it gives you deep familiarity with your profession and expertise and taste, I think that will persist. But I also think that in many ways there'll be a lot less button clicking and like wiring things up properly and setting up the integrations. Um so a little bit vague but hopefully you sort of understand philosophically what I mean.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, thank you.
SPEAKER_02: Um I'll throw one from an enterprise solution large organization type um idea but I've got my Grokbot. He's got his. We're both working on a a similar project whatever it might be. Um how best should we approach or think about having the agents work in harmony so we don't have to do as much? And then on top of that um the I'm I'm using Grok myself and it's it's learning how I think and how I'm doing things and how I'm approaching things at a brilliant level. It's fantastic. But it's individual to me. So how I approach a project may be very different how he approaches it. So how should we think about synergies between the two?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. On this front there's something that I can't quite get ahead of anything at the company and announce but um I think we'll have something really exciting to address this uh pretty shortly.
SPEAKER_03: It's all good. I'll say it. We're just waiting for multiplayer. We want COD, you know.
SPEAKER_00: The the team is working hard to uh build a lot more cool stuff.
SPEAKER_03: You probably also can answer as well where are you going to get Grokbot on Tesla?
SPEAKER_00: Oh on Tesla? I can't answer that unfortunately. But I appreciate the excitement.
SPEAKER_03: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_00: My my parents have Teslas so believe me they're asking me that question too. Yeah. Any other questions?
SPEAKER_04: One question from X. How can we get the Juno template?
SPEAKER_00: The Juno template um I can definitely provide any of these bots that you saw here today as templates afterwards. We can figure out the logistics and get that to the right people after the stream.
SPEAKER_04: Um one last question. What has been the feedback from the sales team on the lead dating app that you created?
SPEAKER_00: So they love it. Um they really do. Um everyone was like this is crazy. Um just the idea of you know being on the subway on the way to work and I'm swiping left and right and some of looking over my shoulder and like has no clue what I'm using but I'm I'm working through my leads. I'm I'm building pipeline. Come on guys. Uh so people really love the concept. I think it's reflected in the numbers. Um we like I mentioned earlier uh within a couple weeks of introducing this hit record highs in terms of lead review rates. Um so I think that sort of shows it all. Um sales reps are working through their backlogs, getting to inbox zero. Uh and the tool really helps them do it way way better than clicking through five different menus, opening up five tabs to look into this lead and what ad do they even see when they became a lead and all these different things only to like then have to click through three more menus and end the lead properly. Um clearly that was not something they were a fan of. Um so they really love it. One really funny thing that I heard from a rep was like yeah I I'm I am pretty sure I don't need another dating app in my life. And my reaction was like well at least this is a dating app where like if you get the date it could actually earn you money, right? You don't have to spend money on this date. Um so they really love it and uh I can see many ways that it could expand and really be like one command center um from Signal to SQO. Um so this is really just the beginning and it's really exciting to have that ability to like keep building more and more and more um thanks to a tool like Grokbot. Awesome. Well I think that is our time. Um now one last Oh one more question.
SPEAKER_05: Yeah, last last question. Thank you for the presentation. What tasks should remain human owned will be even with capable uh bots?
SPEAKER_00: One what tasks should remain human owned is the question. Yeah. You know more and more over time it becomes clear how much relationships matter. I mean we've always known this as human beings. We are social creatures. We want to form relationships. I think you know how many of you in the room like knew what RevOps or MarOps was when you were four years old? Okay, no hands. How many of you would you say you like a thousand percent today a thousand percent know what RevOps and MarOps is? No hands. Okay. These are concepts that we created as human beings to solve certain problems. Um and those concepts that we created were around being really specialized in certain tools or processes. I think what it always comes back to is forming relationships, building trust, and solving problems no matter what it takes. whether that's having a certain title, using certain tools, or whether that's just like figuring it out on the fly. I think those things will always remain our job. Um so we should just keep doing that thing, leaning into our instincts. I think there will always be plenty of human work to do in that vein. So you're all seeing this on the screen. Um I'm really excited to announce to all of you we just launched this challenge. It's live on X. And the way this challenge works is you can share a Grokbot that you simply cannot live without. And then you and a guest could be headed to Starbase in Texas for the rare chance to watch a Starship launch in person. Um this is really exciting. When we came up with this challenge internally we were all like can we enter also? Like oh my god how does this work? Um and so all you have to do to enter is um just go on X, follow at Grok and at bot. And then quote our challenge post. Um I think that's what you'll reach if you scan that QR code. Um so quote the post, give a description of your Grokbot and a link to your shared bot template. Um and uh and basically good luck and and see what happens and hope to see you all at uh at many more events like this in the future. Uh it's been really fun talking to you all today. Thanks.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, we're back. Welcome back everyone. Hope you've enjoyed the morning so far. We are cranking away at deploying our game. And so for those who are just joining us uh we've got a team of SpaceX AI folks here. We are on day three of our three-day uh mission to launch a game studio and our very first game. Uh the idea here is that we we're using Grokbot to power uh and build a game from or build a business from scratch. Uh and kind of going through the last few days of ideation have settled on a game studio and a game. So we're pretty excited for those of you who have deployed production apps at web apps into production with a tight timeline. You might understand some of the things that we're working through right now. So Lauren and Matt are cranking away at all kinds of stuff. I figured we'd hop back on and kind of tell you a little bit about where we are in the process and kind of just walk you through what's going on so you get a feel for what's happening behind the scenes. Um we are currently uh managing a bunch of uh client secrets and web secrets and so we probably won't show our screens a little for at least a little bit, you know, just uh we're not we're not going to deploy live production secrets on stream. Uh so sorry for anyone who was hoping to to get that out of us but basically what we've built is a uh sort of card battler style game. Uh we showed this a little bit earlier as a preview. Uh we're actually doing a really great UI polish pass that we're really excited about. So hopefully um we're going to give everything a fresh coat of paint, make our cards look super slick. Um uh lower lower your expectations.
SPEAKER_06: Okay okay okay. I mean it looks a little bit better but uh I mean still a lot of improvement.
SPEAKER_00: Still a lot of improvement and so maybe that brings me to the the plan for the day which is um you know we're here in San Francisco live at Grokbot Galaxy. We're in this beautiful space. Bunch of stuff happening in person. We have a bunch of talks happening downstairs. We have our little studio space set up upstairs in this space. And uh we're going to be cutting back and forth to a bunch of content throughout the day. We might have some guests on today. For those of you who've been tuned in for the three days you know we've been kind of mixing it up as we go, bringing in some experts in the industry and how to build a business, bringing in some folks around uh you know from from SpaceX AI who are experts in working with Grokbot and kind of showing you some of their presentations as well. And so we'll we'll keep cutting over to stuff as we go. Uh and you know what we really want to do is get this app live and get all of your feedback. So uh Matt earlier this morning was working on some feedback channels. We're going to make you know make a way so we can get your feedback that you're experiencing while you're playing playing the game and using the product into the app. I'm going to talk a little bit more about monetization this afternoon and bring in um some SpaceX AI folks who can help us with the marketing plan and a revenue plan. So I'm pretty excited about that if we get the chance. Uh but then really just want to get get the app live and be able to iterate based on your feedback. And so we're hoping we'll do is ship a little bit of a play test in the next little while. Uh get the play test live and then once we have that live go and um really just ship and iterate. So you know I think there's the classic startup line where if you're not embarrassed by it it's not ready for prime time. So definitely some stuff we're embarrassed by I think but that's a good thing. We're going to turn that into a good thing, get it live and um be able to just iterate throughout the day. So lots of opportunities to add polish, lots of opportunities to add new features. Um really just want to make sure we can make something really fun that folks are excited to play with uh and building something that people want. That's where we are right now. Um just to give you a sense of what's happening in the actual deployment process. So we're using a bunch of different tools to make this come to life. So we've been using Grokbot obviously is our core driver for the business. We have a team of Grokbots doing everything from managing our software factory where we have automatic bug fixes, automatic play tests, automatic reviews. And we have um let's maybe not show screens if that's okay while we're working. Uh thank you. Thank you. Uh automatic bug fixes, automatic PR reviews happening. We have uh you know like any good game we need some play testing. And so we have play testing happening. And we have bots that are kind of doing all these various things kind of put together in a little bit of an engine. So anytime we catch a bug in production a bot can notice that uh and can go ahead and prompt a cloud agent to go and fix it and make a make a PR for it. And we have a play tester bot who'll pick up that change, run it through the game engine, make sure that everything is working well. And then kind of you know approve the PR uh in addition to the other approval steps in our continuous integration suite. So all that is powered by a combination of Grokbots and GitHub working together. Um but we're obviously gluing together a bunch of other stuff to make this work too. So what Matt's working on right now is getting authentication working with Clerk. And so we had a Clerk developer account that we set up in order to get uh log in with X to work. So we're going to support log in with X on the product where folks can log in and participate in the leaderboard. So hopefully you guys get a chance to sign in. You'll be able to you know play the game. Uh each player will get an Elo score. So depending on how it goes over time you'll hopefully be able to you know increase your rank in the game. We're pretty excited about that. Uh and so we'll be able to you know make that leaderboard available to folks who sign in with Twitter. Uh but we also have a practice mode in the app. And so what Matt's working on right now is getting our Clerk configuration cleaned up, making sure that we have all the domains pointing in all the right ways, all the DNS records set up in all the right ways. Um we were joking off camera. It's always DNS. And so we were just debugging a DNS issue right before this. Um and it's it's sometimes always cores. And so we're we're also debugging a cross-origin issue as well. And so again for those of you who have deployed apps into prod uh managed large web apps I think you can probably commiserate with some of these some of these issues. Um so yeah we have Clerk that's helping handle our authentication. Uh we're using Vercel as our hosting provider here. And so that's been really great. We have a bunch of Vercel settings that obviously when you flip from development to production mode um we've been kind of testing each PR. That's how our play tester bot uh handles testing is by kind of accessing those Vercel preview links. But going to production obviously involves hardening the app a little bit, making sure we have great database control, great ingress control, egress control, um security ratcheted down the way we need. And then obviously auth working with Clerk, DNS set up, and all that good stuff. And so all those things are in progress. Um we do have a domain name which we're pretty excited about but we're going to hold off on sharing that for now until we get the product live. And so coming soon we'll we'll reveal the name. Um and yeah other than that we have uh you know kind of like all the infra getting ready to go. So we've also been running a bunch of load tests against our database. We're using PlanetScale as the database provider here. Uh we have a you know series of databases we've set up to handle the core games the core game store. And uh you know we're basically uh like I think last night actually ran a bunch of load tests against the database. Uh we're doing some production hardening this morning to make sure things are in a good spot there as well. Trying to think of what else we have in our stack. Um for those who weren't around yesterday we've also have an entire operations stack around the business. So we have a Slack channel or a Slack team where we have a bug reports channel. Um I'm actually seeing some bug reports filter in right now which is pretty great. What's really nice about these systems when you get bots talking to your other tools is that they can use those tools just like humans would um but they're often a lot faster at using them than humans are. And so one common workflow that we use a ton internally at SpaceX AI is we have feedback channels and issues channels for our products. Anytime someone posts an issue we have triage bots whose job it is to go in, take a look at the issue, see if it's reproducible, look at some logs in our internal logging systems, kind of come back with well is this something that needs a fix? Uh do I need to tag the right person who make who might be able to help advise on this? Uh and those are really cool systems because it can really sort of it can sort of shorten the time period between something being reported and then you know getting to a fix. And very often saves a lot of engineering work where someone has to go and manually look through a bunch of logs. So we're trying to replicate some of those behaviors for this app basically creating a Slack space, making it so that anytime we see an issue or anytime one of you reports an issue we can just automatically fire a bot to take a look at that, see if it's a real issue, reproducible, look at logs and then kind of come back with a PR uh versus just coming back with an investigation or a dashboard that someone else has to go and write some code for. So that you know earlier today you heard us talking about the software factory. Uh and I think that's really what that is in practice. It's sort of this automated software development loop. Um you know and really for for production apps apps that are out in the field uh this is so important right because you know no app no software is perfect. Um you know we we don't we don't intentionally put bugs in software but bugs exist. And so a large part of the work of an engineering team is kind of looking at issues that exist, uh kind of making sure that we're seeing those issues come in, being able to triage them, fix them, and then continue to do that while evolving the product. And so you'll see another set of issue well hopefully not too many but we're going to we're trying to we're going to but we are also doing a UI rewrite. So I don't know. We we rewrote the UI. We just uh revamped uh our our authentication stuff. So
SPEAKER_00: when you flip from a development to production kind of authentication, there's a bunch of OAuth and callback stuff you have to reconfigure and uh I don't know. It's a interesting lesson because you know a big part of not just building a business but building like software is connecting things together and figuring out like production environments and like what production is, how that's different from a development environment. Um and yeah it's not always like fun and just like making stuff happen. Sometimes it's like literally figuring out the glue. But agents are are quite good for that because you know previously you would have had to diagnose these issues manually, which if anybody's tried to do this before it takes a lot of time. And so having an agent understanding you know I think a a larger point is is all of the same skills that apply in like software engineering or running a business still apply. So if you think about like what it means to be able to debug something like previously that was like okay I'm going to understand all of the steps in a process and then I'm going to go by go through those manually one by one until I kind of identify an error point. Now we can we can lean on agents to help us do that but all the principles are kind of still the same which is like between point A and point B there are x number of things that can go wrong. And how do I think about where we are, where we're going, and then where all of those sort of points are, right? And I I often describe this like you know fixing like a lamp. Maybe if a lamp is not working, the first question you should ask is is it is the light bulb working or is the bulb burnt out and is it plugged in? And if you can diagnose those two issues and they're they're both working, then the issue is somewhere in between those two, right? And then your job as an engineer or someone trying to fix this lamp, someone who's trying to do it themselves is to figure out what point in that chain can go wrong. And this is exactly the same with software. So you know we have a lot of like API keys and things floating around which is why we're we're kind of talking through this. But these are good good lessons and it's the same thing in business, right? So
SPEAKER_02: Uh Yeah yeah yeah.RB UmRBRB yeahRB soRBRB wellRB nowRB I'mRB inRB thirdRB place.RBRB UhRBRB I'veRB fallenRB downRBRB in in theRB rankings cuz I've been umRB slacking off. And we have Ben J Bush in second place. Roshan still holding strong on first place.
SPEAKER_01: While you were talking, I know you've been working on getting the clerk app working in production. I just signed in and I'm looking at the clerk dashboard. Let's not show this on screen, please. We're looking looking at the clerk dashboard and I see one active user. So we have our first production active.
SPEAKER_00: Yep. That is that is me. I'm the I'm the active user in production.
SPEAKER_02: I I'm playing a game right now, too.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, cool.
SPEAKER_01: Okay, maybe clerk's dashboard is lagging behind.
SPEAKER_02: I just lost then.
SPEAKER_00: So you know essentially what we did was flip from dev to prod. And now you know our our prod instance has active users and and we're starting to get things working. So
SPEAKER_01: I see I see three active users. Okay okay. So we have we have user authentication. We have a game engine. I think that's working.
SPEAKER_02: Okay. Mhm. I think that works. Yeah. Right now I think I think it just it just started working.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. What else is on our launch checklist? So we were talking a little bit off stream about all the things we need to do to feel good to get this launch out to the world. And so what are the things that are on our launch checklist? And maybe what I can do is why don't I just like make a Notion doc and we can just you know put together this checklist right now. I'm going to bug you guys a little bit. I know your head's down but let me see what I can do. I'm going to pull up my screen and so now like let's go ahead and cut to my screen if we can. Actually give me one second. Let me just close some tabs. There we go. There we go. We're good. We're good. We're good. Okay. And so for those who are not familiar, we have a Notion doc that we have been working on. And yep got it got it got it. And we basically yesterday just to catch you guys up on how we we thought about managing the context for the company is that we we ended up creating well it looks like we have our our agents have really gone
SPEAKER_02: Is that me? I think I think that needs to be cleaned up. It's kind of
SPEAKER_01: Our agents have gone hard in here. We also have a here we go. So yeah we we did create a sort of task board that we've been using with our agents. They've been logging data into a Notion database. This is a little messy it looks like. Where's my checklist that I'm looking for? Okay we'll see if I can find it. We have a working to do list here. We have a bunch of other company contacts that we've been putting in. Things like our canonical database schema, things like the source of truth for our game mechanics. And these are just really helpful ways for bots to be able to interact with other bots and to be able to interact with company contacts. I think Lauren had a really great point on Tuesday when we kicked off which is like you know very often for coding agents the codebase is the best source of context and memory. And so that's obviously a huge part of the actual software engineering loop. But for many of the operational things it helps to be able to write docs. And so we have a bunch of these docs that we've created. What I want to do though now is make a launch checklist. So let's just work through this live. I think we need a few things. We have to get authentication working.
SPEAKER_02: I think that works now. You can check that.
SPEAKER_01: Authentication is working.
SPEAKER_02: I just wanted to put something on the list.
SPEAKER_01: You can check that. You can check that. Cool cool cool. Do we want to land the UI rewrite before we
SPEAKER_02: I don't think we need to.
SPEAKER_01: You think we should just
SPEAKER_02: I'd I'd be curious I mean I think I feel like should we should we launch it right now?
SPEAKER_01: You're saying the checklist is that's it? There's nothing else?
SPEAKER_02: I mean I think we could maybe set expectations. This is like a first play test. Uh the UI is not very polished. And we're not sure if things will break.
SPEAKER_01: I'm pretty actually pretty sure things will break.
SPEAKER_02: Things are going to break. Yeah but I feel like we could probably I don't know what do you think? Should we should we polish it more? What what does chat think if you want to play it right now?
SPEAKER_01: Mhm.
SPEAKER_02: Just as long as you understand that it's pretty it's not very polished at the moment.
SPEAKER_01: I don't know. I haven't clicked through it in a while. So if you guys think it's ready then
SPEAKER_02: How how about this? Why don't you go to our go to your browser,
SPEAKER_01: Okay.
SPEAKER_02: hide the URL,
SPEAKER_02: maybe do maybe hide the URL maybe turn off the screen for a second.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah let me turn off my screen share for a second.
SPEAKER_02: Then you go to our app, our game, hide the URL,
SPEAKER_01: Yep.
SPEAKER_02: and then see if you can play it.
SPEAKER_01: Let me try
SPEAKER_02: And then we can show off we can show off playing it. And if we feel good about it, let's just share the URL with everyone in the chat and do our first play test.
SPEAKER_01: Cool. We haven't renamed it yet. We got to finish the rename. So
SPEAKER_02: We'll do it live.
SPEAKER_01: Okay. Okay so if we want to go back to my screen, moment of truth, let's see let's see if things work. Uh we can put my screen back up.
SPEAKER_02: Can you zoom in?
SPEAKER_01: Uh I think if I zoom in it's going to cause some formatting issues. So let's try running it with default views right now. These are the kinds of things that I think we need to clean up. Um so if I hit practice uh we added a practice mode.
SPEAKER_02: Oh okay. Maybe explain the game cuz I feel like we made so many changes it's not clear.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Well we need to add a tutorial. I think that would be really cool.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um yeah. So essentially what we've built here is sort of an auto battler style game where we have um the set a set of preloaded cards. Uh these cards are all generated from Grokbot templates. And so we seeded a set of cards or a deck of cards with um you know uh abilities from the Grokbot marketplace. And this is really fun where we have our office ops desk, our writing bot, or a dial bot. Um each of these cards have stats. They have two key stats. They have an attack stat and a health stat, like an HP stat. And they all have an ability. And so each card has a separate ability that's been minted for that card. And um what's really cool about these is that these abilities really modify the gameplay. The way the game works is it takes place over three rounds. Uh in each round you set your lineup of bots. And so you kind of align your bots up. And you're matched against another person who's also set a lineup of bots. Uh and what the way it works is you basically spend you have a a pool of gold that you use that you're sort of spending over the course of the round. So why don't I just show you show you the first round. Um I'm going to just go ahead and buy three bots. Um so I'll buy my office ops desk.
SPEAKER_02: The text is pretty small by the way. So you might want to just read out stuff.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Well why don't I pinch and zoom? That might be easier.
SPEAKER_02: Oh yeah perfect.
SPEAKER_01: So we have our office ops desk card. You can see that attack there. You can see the health there. And you can see up here that it's in the first spot in our lineup. It has this ability called hold the line. It's pretty cool. So anytime it gets hurt from the front of the line it'll restore one HP. So just basically be a little damage tank for us.
SPEAKER_02: What is that Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And I don't know if I love these uh help texts but we can always That's what a card looks like. We actually have a cool uh way we're going to modify that. And so basically what I do here is I set my lineup. So I got the office ops desk. Uh earlier if you saw these the base cards cost three gold. And so I start with 10 gold. And I'm down to seven now. Um and so oh you found a bug. Okay.
SPEAKER_02: That's important. Uh but yeah I did a lot of uh you know like things like fixing our migrations. I had I had a bug. Um oh one thing that for the techy people in in who are in in our chat so one thing I I was thinking about as we're building this was like type safety. And it's like a very you know when when you start building a real game you start thinking about um like how to actually maintain. And uh again entirely honest like when we first started building this it was very very scrappy, very loose. Didn't look at the code at all. So um I didn't even know what we were going to expect.
SPEAKER_01: Wow we have almost 500 users.
SPEAKER_02: Oh the that the name suddenly changed to unknown bot. I don't know what happened there.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah good point. Okay that's a good catch. That might be one we should fix.
SPEAKER_02: We should probably fix that but you can you can still show the card.
SPEAKER_01: Oh 100% So here's an unknown bot that previously had a name, definitely has a cute image. Um this bot is a 33 uh and is unknown and apparently had an ability before. Let me see if I buy
SPEAKER_02: Can you refresh and see it?
SPEAKER_01: Okay well when I buy the bot we get an error.
SPEAKER_02: Oh okay. Yeah that's a bug. I'll I'll I'll fix that.
SPEAKER_01: There's dial bot. Dial bot is a 33 bot that has poke. So anytime the game starts this bot deals one damage to the enemy in the front lines. And so what's cool about this game is that basically you're setting a lineup. And then the cards uh the bots all have abilities that uh you know make it so that you can uh basically modify the behavior of other bots in the other team's lineup. And so the idea here is that it's sort of lineup versus lineup with a bunch of cool abilities. So this is our second bot dial bot. And then we're going to buy our third bot here, writing bot that spends almost all my gold. You'll see I'm down to one. And you'll see that we have our writing bot here whose ability is to give the frontmost friend to attack. So what ends up being really fun about this is that because of the way these cards all have different things they can do and because they all modify the lineup you can kind of compose this together. So for example I know that my strongest attack bot here is this office ops desk. And actually it's pretty able to withstand a lot of damage, too. So what I can do is drag my writing bot to the second slot. And what the sec what the writing bot does is give the frontmost friend two attack. It also has a ton of defensive of its own. I think what this will do is set me up for a really strong start in spot one and then be able to have two sort of characters who can tank a little bit of damage from you which I think will be great. And then you'll see this guy yeah gets to heal two attack. I think I like this setup. Yeah and then we'll get dial bot at the very beginning of the match. We'll just deal one damage to the enemy front. So I really like this combo cuz I think this will give me you know a four attack to start um against a potentially weaker opponent which I think is going to be really really cool. So I like this lineup. And then the way the game works is if I had a little more money I could buy these upgrades. And so every round between rounds and again it's the best of three rounds um you basically go in and can get you know an upgrade. Uh in this case I already had to get a plus one plus one. I don't have three gold. Let's just go ahead and fight round one. So you're seeing here I'm getting paired against uh another team of bots. And it looks like my strategy worked out pretty well. Let's see there we go. That worked. And so what you're seeing happening over the course of the game is that um the bots are duking it out. Those abilities fire. It's a bit of an event stream here. You know one idea I'm thinking is I wonder if we should show the event stream.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah we probably should show like like the the stream cuz yeah I was just as you were playing I was just noticing that it happened so fast that I didn't actually know what's going on.
SPEAKER_01: Yep.
SPEAKER_02: So it'd be cool if yeah you could maybe even step through the thing even if you wanted to play or just let it auto play.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah quick quick quick. Actually you know what for an MVP why don't we just make it click through? It feels like it could be kind of an auto play button.
SPEAKER_02: Sure. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Um okay cool. So we're going to continue. So now that's round one. Uh and then of course you can continue through two more rounds. But what's really cool now is we have a few new bots that have entered the fray. And so
SPEAKER_02: Oh you got a uncommon card if you can see the green bar.
SPEAKER_01: I got an uncommon Yeah so I got an uncommon card which is super strong. Looks like uh this card gets stronger when the card in front of it faints. And so this might be a really cool one to pair with one of my other bots. But now I have some choices to make, right? So I have I know that what I'm fighting against so I can see my my opponent's lineup um at least from what I saw last time. I have 10 gold. And these bots are pretty expensive but but I have some some room to work with. So I think what I could do here is sell one of these cards.
SPEAKER_02: Do you want to pinch the zoom so we can see some of the text as well?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah I think
SPEAKER_02: Like what what uh what what bots do you have in your shop now?
SPEAKER_01: So I have the SEO and AEO. Deal one damage to the enemy in the same seat.
SPEAKER_02: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: I feel like we should definitely buy the nightly audit engineer since it's uncommon. And maybe sell the dial bot. I don't think that's that's it.
SPEAKER_02: 100% yeah. I think we should sell the dial bot. Yeah. So that gave me a gold. We should probably say how much they sell for on here.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah you get one gold for selling them.
SPEAKER_02: So you know how much money we're making. Um but I'm going to buy my nightly audit engineer. And this gives plus two attack when the friend ahead faints. And I actually really like this combo. So what what this is going to do is my office ops desk is going to get this hype benefit which will give it plus two attack. So it'll be a 55. And then when it faints this will turn into a 56.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Mhm that's a pretty that's a pretty good combo.
SPEAKER_02: That's a pretty You have enough gold to buy the power up to the apple.
SPEAKER_01: Oh right okay. Where do you think we should put that?
SPEAKER_02: Uh what does that do? Can you zoom in? Can you see the text?
SPEAKER_01: I'll put it in it. Yeah the apple is uh just gives us plus one plus one to any bot.
SPEAKER_02: Oh.
SPEAKER_01: Just stack the front line.
SPEAKER_02: Sure. It looks like our main damage dealer.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah let's try it. Okay so this is now a four four six. It's pretty beefy.
SPEAKER_02: Yep.
SPEAKER_01: Um and then we have four gold left. I guess we could swap another bot. We could sell and buy but I kind of like this lineup.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah I think this lineup is really good. Let's let's go with that.
SPEAKER_01: Okay let's go with that. So here we go. We're going to fight round two.
SPEAKER_02: This is where maybe the the sound effects and the music you had could be be kind of Yeah look we
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. But this was an awesome We had two bots two bots We did so well here. And again this is just practice. So this is just fighting our AI um which is not very smart. But you know as we start Yeah yeah but when we start actually releasing it we'll have
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. It still feels good to win.
SPEAKER_01: uh players will be able to you know compete with each other and we'll uh we'll start tracking scores and the leaderboard will start getting active. So
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: um And we'll keep iterating on it, too. So a lot of polished things that we're seeing. So one of the things that we do internally is we have this tradition where anytime we're going to launch a product we fuzz it or we kind of walk through literally step by step of the entire experience. We can literally just do this. We all get into a room together, sit in our laptops, and test the feature. Uh obviously this
SPEAKER_02: Mhm. Yeah yeah. Should we should we share this with the chat now?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah well do you think we're ready?
SPEAKER_02: Only one way to find out.
SPEAKER_01: Okay okay okay. Well here's the homepage. Um there's a bot menu. See all the bots
SPEAKER_02: Oh yeah this this is actually a bug. We don't need to show this. I don't know why the my bot edited this.
SPEAKER_01: Oh we have some private cards in here.
SPEAKER_02: But um actually I guess you this could be cool to show. Um so like we were saying earlier we looked at the X AI uh if you go to X AI X.ai/bot/marketplace, you'll see all of the bot templates that we have that are featured. And basically what we did is we turned all of these into bots in our game. And we also generated a custom uh profile picture for them, like a a cute little avatar. Uh we're still we we're going to make this UI look a lot nicer but yeah there's a lot of cards to choose from and they have different rarity as well. So like there's the common cards, you have uncommon cards, rare cards.
SPEAKER_01: These are really good.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah so these ones are like better stats or more interesting abilities. And then we have
SPEAKER_01: Link's engineer bot.
SPEAKER_02: epic epic cards.
SPEAKER_01: I agree Link's she's epic.
SPEAKER_02: Uh and oh yes Dr. Egg bot. We have Dr. Egg bot right there.
SPEAKER_01: I feel like Lauren might have might have I might have cheated a little bit and and favored my own bot.
SPEAKER_00: bot favored bot as an epic bot.
SPEAKER_02: Well I didn't I didn't make Dr. Egg bot legendary.
SPEAKER_01: I feel like as game creators we should each get one legendary bot of our own.
SPEAKER_02: Maybe maybe. Yeah or maybe we can feature somebody's bot, right? Someone in the chat spot as a legendary bot. That could be cool actually.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah yeah that's fair. Yeah I think it that's fair. If you create a bot template and we like it we'll add it there.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah yeah yeah. Um you can do that just from Grokbot. Create a bot in Grokbot, hit the share button, you can export it as a template. Share your bot templates with us. And the we'll maybe we'll pick a few of our favorites and bring them into the chat. I like that. Or bring them into the
SPEAKER_01: All right so
SPEAKER_02: game. I think it's really important for our game studio that we actually get real feedback.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: So let's do a really quick five second huddle.
SPEAKER_01: Cool.
SPEAKER_02: Should we launch it right now?
SPEAKER_01: You have the Twitter account, we're the X account ready, right?
SPEAKER_00: I have the X account yeah. I mean the X account is not there's no details on it but we have the URL. The URL's good. Uh all is good.
SPEAKER_02: So the URL you have the URL. We could do a play test. We need to say this is a play test. Right we'll just set expectations. You know it's going to probably go we'll have bugs and errors but hopefully you'll get to play it with us and give us feedback.
SPEAKER_01: Let's ship it.
SPEAKER_02: Let's ship it?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: I'm down. All right.
SPEAKER_01: Okay I feel like Matt should do the honors and and make our first X post.
SPEAKER_00: Our first X post.
SPEAKER_01: I didn't I didn't say I was logged into the X account. So the X account I created everyone did.
SPEAKER_02: That's great. Matt's going to get the post up. And then once that's up we'll put it on your screen maybe.
SPEAKER_01: Sounds good. Yeah I can pull it up.
SPEAKER_02: And then we'll show URL and then we'll just start watching our uh our logs I guess make sure everything's working.
SPEAKER_01: And we'll show the URL. I think I'm logged in on my phone. Yeah and one thing we'll uh so a couple of things for folks who are just catching up, just tuning in while Matt gets us set up, we are you are watching us joining us mid launch. We are launching our game studio that we've been working on for the last day and changed. We're in the we're on day three of our 72 hour live stream to build a product, build a company entirely with Grokbot. Uh we you know spent some time early on ideating. We settled on an idea early elect late day one, early day two that we've been running with. And we're building a game studio and we're launching our first game. And um well we we know it has a lot of polish that it needs but we're really excited to get it out there and get it into people's hands. Uh so we're imminently here going to uh reveal our our domain and reveal our X account. Um and what's one thing I'll call out is like you know the those will be the only real accounts and domains associated with this. And so I want to make sure that you know you're you're coming to the source. Uh and that any any other associations you see here are not going to be by us. So we'll we'll reveal the two official sources of truth for this app uh and and be able to share those out.
SPEAKER_02: Yes. Yes. Did you get the post up?
SPEAKER_01: We are posting now. Yeah. I'm I'm literally updating the I like the X account is default and blank.
SPEAKER_02: Very exciting. Yeah this is like and and I I guess if you if you've ever worked at a startup or built a startup if you're on or are thinking about one you know this is what this is what it's like. It's super scrappy. Things don't work but there's a real I think it's really fun when you know you have you're you're working with a team of founders. You have there's a lot of energy. I see Roshan in your screen. Oh no uh that's your screen.
SPEAKER_00: That's my screen.
SPEAKER_01: We're just watching we're just watching.
SPEAKER_02: We're watching half the live.
SPEAKER_01: Okay so we go to the I'm logged into my account but on my phone
SPEAKER_02: I have it up I have it up on you already. As soon as you tweet we can cut to my screen if you're ready.
SPEAKER_01: All right okay.
SPEAKER_00: We're live.
SPEAKER_02: Thursday Arena is live.
SPEAKER_01: With our default default profile picture cuz I literally didn't have a
SPEAKER_00: 100 100 I love it.
SPEAKER_02: And yeah uh remind to everyone that Thursday Arena this is the only official X account for our game studio. And thursdayarena.com is our only official game.
SPEAKER_01: Game. So if you're seeing anything related to this project that is not coming from the @ThursdayArena X account or is not being shown to you on thursdayarena.com it is not us.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Uh this these these are two spots, the source of truth.
SPEAKER_02: And yeah let me actually just retweet the uh your post and follow.
SPEAKER_01: All right. Yeah side there's a side quest of our game which is how many followers can can we get on this Twitter account this X account?
SPEAKER_00: So one thing one little tool that I built like I like emojis. Uh so I have this what I have my own uh site emoji.maphalmer.io that actually allows you to download any apple emoji um as a PNG. Little tool that I have for myself so I can get a little a little cupcake emoji here. Maybe that's our maybe that's our first um X uh X profile image. Um but yeah we're
SPEAKER_02: Haha. Matt emoji so cute. Cute name.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah we're working on some uh in the background I'm working on some of the like uh favicon and like styling things as well as OG images. A little quick tip for you. Anytime you make a website, anytime you have a business you probably want it to show up nice. Like if I went to Thursday Arena and like search for it on Google or something, right? Um meta information are the thing are the things you see here. So like clearly we're not doing our SEO or AEO yet. We're going to work on that. But you want the information shown to be um like number one you want it to to use best practices in search engine optimization and also to look nice for users.
SPEAKER_02: Sorry to interrupt you but look at our leaderboard. We have we have 96 people on the leaderboard. I don't even know if we have pagination. Do you want to bring up the leaderboard? Uh you may have to sign in.
SPEAKER_00: So we got our uh our
SPEAKER_02: Sign sign in works. Yes.
SPEAKER_00: Sign in works. So that's good to hear.
SPEAKER_02: Very nice that it works. I'm very impressed.
SPEAKER_01: We probably should pick some of these logos. While they're doing that I also have a bot that's working on building us some dashboards. Uh and so we want to be able to track how the launch is going.
SPEAKER_02: Yo Roshan you're number one right now. Okay okay let's that let's do pagination.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah we need to work on this. I don't like this. I don't like this.
SPEAKER_02: Uh this is kind of
SPEAKER_01: I was in second place all of the last 24 hours. So let me let me enjoy my number one spot for
SPEAKER_00: I need to Oh my gosh I only have
SPEAKER_02: Uh uh you're losing Matt. I'm going to go to silver.
SPEAKER_00: I'm going down on uh on the leaderboard here.
SPEAKER_02: You need to think about your strategy.
SPEAKER_01: Take that bot. And so one of the things I'm doing while Matt's playing here is I love bots for routines for product launches. I do this all the time. So anytime we launch something internally in SpaceX AI I put together I I ask a bot to say you know you're my data scientist bot. You have all the contacts and how all of our data science works and all the all the stuff in our dashboards. Generate me a launch pulse. And so that's what I'm doing on my screen right now where I just asked my bot to you know put This is a lot more fun than dashboards. I know I know. Uh but put together a 15 minute pulse. So every 15 minutes I'm going to get I'm going to get thrown some dashboards to see how the launch is going. Can track some new sign ups, track the number of practice rounds we've had, get a sense of if we maybe have a conversion funnel here where we want to convert people from practice accounts to real accounts. All the cool sort of product metrics that you might love for any new app but we're live. It's exciting.
SPEAKER_02: So uh shall we call people who are trying to climb the leaderboard?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah maybe we'll hit over to
SPEAKER_02: So now we have second place Ben J bot.
SPEAKER_01: Wait first let's head over to uh Lauren's screen real quick. And she's going to shout some folks out.
SPEAKER_01: Thank you thank you.
SPEAKER_02: I might actually have we might consider have uh making this leaderboard update every minute or something. Uh but I can just refresh.
SPEAKER_01: Okay cool. What does it do now?
SPEAKER_02: It doesn't it doesn't auto update.
SPEAKER_01: Okay so refresh yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Uh Ben J Bush getting very close to beating you Roshan. He's at 1046 points and you're at 1047. So
SPEAKER_01: Oh so we're we're up to 225 followers on X.
SPEAKER_00: Wow I love that.
SPEAKER_02: Very nice. And um Are you working on the I think it'd be really cool to show like how many users we have live. I know you can bring that up.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah I'm working at my my bot is is
SPEAKER_02: Oh okay okay so don't share Roshan's screen yet but I think it'd be really cool to see how many people we have like concurrently.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: And I'm I'm To be honest I am very impressed that this the app hasn't crashed yet because oh Ben J Bush is now in first place. Congratulations. Um uh we did mention that maybe we'll have we have some prizes for people on the leaderboard. We'll we'll talk about that very soon. Uh but yeah as I'll as I'll saying you know like the factory was really spinning up last night. Uh we were merging PRs automatically. To be entirely honest I didn't look at the code at all. I just used potato mode and P-stack. And um you know told my bot to like make this really performant and make sure we can handle a giant you know a giant swarm of people on X playing our game. And so far so good. It's it's still you know I'm dropping down the ranks now. I'm I'm only at 11th place. I got to start playing some games.
SPEAKER_02: Um but uh while Roshan's still working on the uh the dashboard I can actually show you some of the commits I guess the um to be honest I I I I this is the first time I'm looking at some of them but a lot of this was like um I didn't really I didn't I didn't tell my bots to put in a lot of effort in the commit titles. You can see actually Roshan was landing a lot of commits in the last hour. Um let me just filter
SPEAKER_01: Sorry I know I also be working on dashboards but I'm also trying to get my rating back up. So I'm also just doing
SPEAKER_02: Oh wow that's huge. Um and um yeah so so our backend is built with Go. And it's actually a serverless backend built with Vercel functions. Um so I think that's uh maybe part of the reason Oh we also use PlanetScale for our database. So that's probably why it's so it it's actually working pretty well right now thanks to the we're standing on the shoulders of great of great uh engineers. Um and um so one thing I was trying to think about last night was how do I make sure that the backend and the front end the client like stay in sync. So you know when your backend talks to your front end uh it would be talking over some protocol. Uh so for us we we we we just use a REST protocol. Uh but um so one thing I was trying to think about was type safety. So type safety is this idea of you know on the back end like let's say you have a a bot type, right? And the bot has certain fields like you know it has a display, a display name, it has a avatar, it has some stats associated with it. And let's say you know as Matt, Roshan, and myself are contributing to the code base um how do we ensure that if I make a backend change and Roshan makes a front end change that we don't conflict? You know like maybe Roshan does redesigns the card and uh I I removed a field, right? And now the field that the UI is reading from is no longer able to get that data. So uh one of the things that I started to look at was like how do we ensure that type safety over over the the network. And I honestly didn't really have a if I had to spend more time I I might have designed this differently but for now it's kind of a basic approach where we parse the uh the responses we get from the backend through Zod. Zod's just really great uh library, a JavaScript library. Um and uh it essentially lets you parse the response and handle them and make sure that it's all validated and correct. Uh can someone also create a QR code to our ThursdayArena .com? Oh it's up there.
SPEAKER_01: You got it. Awesome awesome.
SPEAKER_02: Oh it's up there.
SPEAKER_01: Um all right then follow. Uh I have some dashboards. Should we take a look at that?
SPEAKER_02: Oh cool. Yeah yeah. Let's switch to Roshan's screen.
SPEAKER_01: Um yeah let's switch to my screen please. What's a what's a business without a dashboard, you know? It's I you know I'm a product person. I I need metrics. I I'm blind without them. Uh let me zoom in a little bit here. So um yeah this is Grokbot. Um you can kind of see some of the bots that we have set up. It looks like my founding engineer here is just still listening to all the PRs that are coming in. So we're working away. Um what I love to do is as I was saying a second ago is for new launches put use Grokbot to drive my metrics and reporting. Um I find that this is actually uh a really powerful way to just get quick on demand data versus having to go to a dashboard website, log in, kind of navigate through a bunch of clicks. And honestly what's even better about this is I can just get my live cuts of data that I need like now. So I don't have to go and like recreate a dashboard.
SPEAKER_02: I just wanted to interrupt you to say I love hockey stick charts. Like that the one I'm squinting in the middle.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yes. Oh yes. Let's take a look take a look at the charts. So we already have over 600 practice sessions. This is like as of I don't know two minutes ago. Um I love funnel metrics. So it looks like 38 of our users or 38 practice sessions converted to sign in with X. 400 people signed in with X. I know that number's already higher than it is just based on what we saw. Um we have wow a hockey stick chart. This is traffic spike. Um
SPEAKER_02: Okay. Amazing. It's time to it's time to get funding guys.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah yeah. Up into the right um cool little funnel snapshot here. Uh these are really great. We can kind of see where in the funnel we're losing people. Obviously like for for for games and SaaS products we care a lot about retention, recurring visits. And then obviously if you want to monetize this this will be you know metrics that our our monetization partners will care a lot about. Some cool signed in matches by phase. I don't know why it's calling this SaaS matches but that's okay. Um shop result in battles so we can kind of see when people are signing in. We have a sign in with X button throughout the product so we can kind of see when we're capturing the sign in event which is really cool.
SPEAKER_02: Mhm. Um actually something I'm curious about uh I've always wanted to know is like you know as a as a product manager when you're thinking about how to grow the product and act on user feedback and you know prioritize what's most important uh what what do you look at? Like cuz I guess for me you know like I want to see the obviously I want to see the user numbers go up and engagement but
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: do you have any like go to things that you see to like you know like where do where are people falling off in the product like or in the game?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah I think it actually really depends on what type of product you're building. And so for where we are we're a zero to one company. We just launched this. We're like hopefully going to get a few hundred, maybe a few thousand users today if you guys keep signing up. Um and for a zero to one product we we don't have monetization in the app right now. So really I think what we care about is just the classic sort of Bay Area growth machine, right? Is like we really want to get as many people into the product really liking what we've built as possible. And so the things I care about most are are people playing, are they having a good time? Can we
SPEAKER_00: like what we've built. And so some of that will be through feedback, some of that will be through the funnel. So for example, um being able to see if people are making it all the way to a game, all the way to the end of a game, playing another game, or are they kind of starting off and then just falling off immediately and kind of not coming back. So funnel metrics are really great for that, particularly for zero to one products where you want to get a sense of how things are going. And then obviously, you know, for a scaled revenue product, which hopefully we can get to as well, um revenue is a big is a big metric. Uh we talked with um some guests on Monday that help build small businesses and help empower small businesses to really grow. And you know, kind of heard over and over again that revenue is the main thing that businesses care about. And you know, we're we're no different, right? Any good company needs to make money, needs to make money to keep the product growing and to keep the product, you know, continuing to evolve and fund all the engineers and help us buy coffee and and all those good things. And so um revenue ultimately at the end of the day becomes becomes a huge driver. But we're pre-revenue. We're pre-revenue. So while we're pre-revenue, um I like to focus more on product metrics. I like to focus on engagement, um retention, some of those classic metrics, but obviously tuned to tuned to our product here. So um you know, maybe we're happy with a bunch of people just practicing and not signing up for X. But you know, maybe for the people who sign in, we could give them even, you know, better experiences. We could uh you know, really make the leaderboard more competitive or add more features for signed in users. Uh you know, maybe we we give them, you know, all kinds of perks, um things like this. And so um yeah, I think that's kind of how I think about it. The other thing that I also really like to to think about because we're building a game, the game mechanics are really important here. And so you know, we mentioned earlier, we love playing games. We haven't built a ton of games ourselves. And so we've learned a lot throughout this process. But one of the things we can do with these metrics is we can also just get a sense of how the game is operating. And um one of the things that I know is really important from game design is making sure that we don't sort of fall over on the mechanics, meaning is there enough variety? Is there enough replayability? Is the game balanced in a good way where it feels like you're not losing every time or you're not winning every time? Is there a truly competitive dynamic? And so while I was talking a minute ago, I just asked my bot here to pull some examples of, you know, win losses and how games are going. It looks like we have uh yeah, a little loss heavy right now. We're at a 41.8% loss ratio. And it looks like we have um yeah, you know, I wonder if our AI matchmaking is working okay because when I was playing most of my games, it seemed like they were playing against AI. So maybe we should try and
SPEAKER_01: Uh I think that was because we didn't So the way it works is like you you get matched with another player's snapshot.
SPEAKER_00: Right. Right.
SPEAKER_01: And I think at the time we were play testing it, there was nobody else.
SPEAKER_00: Right.
SPEAKER_01: So once you play once you played my snapshot, for example, it's gone from the pool.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And so then you just match with the AI player. But now we have players who are actually getting ranked. If you If you look at the leaderboard,
SPEAKER_00: So here we go snapshot. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: the the scores are are continually updating.
SPEAKER_00: Cool.
SPEAKER_01: Now Nicholas Check is in first place. Congratulations at 1084. I'm very curious who is going to be the first player to break out of gold if you open the leaderboard and and zoom in a little bit.
SPEAKER_00: Awesome. I have it. I have it.
SPEAKER_01: Um I actually forgot what the next tier is. I think it's diamond after this.
SPEAKER_00: I think so. We might need to add more tiers. We'll see. Elo should be back. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, we'll see. We'll see. Um so um the way Elo works as a rough example is like it gets harder to get points as you ascend the ladder. Um and um if you're Yeah, and it also there's also some like math behind you know, if you get matched up with a much higher rated player and you beat them, then you gain you gain more points.
SPEAKER_00: A little bit. Yeah. I what I'm wondering is we might have a
SPEAKER_01: Can you zoom in?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, I will zoom out because it's hard to pick cards.
SPEAKER_01: Did you Did you Did you match uh or you can just pinch?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Did you match against a real person?
SPEAKER_00: I think I'm AI.
SPEAKER_01: Um
SPEAKER_00: That might be a good bug for us to look into.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, but then I guess I mean other people I see other people's scores changing. So they have to be matching with players.
SPEAKER_00: Maybe our Elo is updating for AI.
SPEAKER_01: Let Let me try and play a game as well and see.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Okay. So while Lauren's looking at that, I'll bring us back to Grokbot. Um and we were talking a little bit about game mechanics. So this can be really helpful too. It looks like we can see some really quick charts on our win loss. Um and then also just like opponent difficulty. So we have ghost players, AI players, and unknown. We should probably come up with some some better naming for those. So these charts are a little bit slow.
SPEAKER_01: But so if if we look at the win loss, there are more losses than wins, which means that AI is just beating people.
SPEAKER_00: Yes, that's exactly what that means. So this is actually interesting from my game studio perspective because uh I actually I mean I don't know. I've never really built a competitive game before, but I think I believe the idea is to try to strive for more or less like a 50%
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, cuz you need to feel like you can win, but also not feel like you can't win.
SPEAKER_00: ratio. Right, right. Otherwise like right now it might feel like it's too unbalanced where you just you just keep losing and it's not that fun.
SPEAKER_02: Right. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: I think I feel like it'd be a good This is something we need to iterate on is like how do we actually get it more up to 50%? Maybe we we can kick off a bot here and there that kind of analyze the data.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: And this I think is also another example of how Grokbot is powerful when you hook up all of those things. So Roshan's Grokbot is connected to like Vercel, to PlanetScale, to GitHub, to our all the the metrics here. Um and so it can pull all of this information together and start thinking, you know, like send it to your game designer bot and say you know, help us look at this data and understand
SPEAKER_02: Exactly. Could be that right now.
SPEAKER_00: Uh yeah, help us look at this data and understand uh you know, where you know, maybe the game is not as fun because people are like losing more than they are winning. Um you know, and it doesn't feel like you have a good chance of winning. Um and it can it can get you so many good insights just because of the fact that it has all this context pulled across all of your different sources. So I often tell people like the most important thing about Grokbot actually is not even setting up your bots. It's actually connecting all of the your different tools and plugins. You know, you can actually get very far even with just one bot if you don't want to set up a team.
SPEAKER_02: Here's Yeah, here's what I have right now. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Um Yeah. P Stack of course, Slack, Vercel, X, PlanetScale, Notion, um Clerk, Excalidraw. We were doing some whiteboarding earlier. But yeah, really anything you need. Um we did some sound design. So my bots were creating their own skills, which is really cool. So they can do that. Yeah, anything you need if you want Doctor Eggbot, you have some featured bots here, but also um a bunch of um yeah, a bunch of apps. And what's cool about this too since we're on the same team, I can see oh Matt sold remotion. So maybe I could also get remotion. Um but yeah, anything you need um a plugin exists for it or you can just also point your agent at the um like point Grokbot at an MCP URL. It'll install it for you itself. We uh we added one password yesterday, which is really cool too. So um a lot more of these coming online every single day. Um like agent mail for email, Canva for design, Clay for go to market, which you heard about earlier today. Lots of cool stuff here. Um cool. Well, I have Crit who's my game design bot. I asked my data bot to kind of share the live launch with Crit. Uh Crit's been helping us on game design, kind of walking through the mechanics that we might want to build. Are they good? Are they bad?
SPEAKER_02: Oh I I think production has an update for us actually. We have some cappuccinos coming in on set. Uh we're doing live delivery. Thank you production.
SPEAKER_01: Thank you so much.
SPEAKER_00: Need fuel for the launch. But yeah, Roshan, I think you're right. I I seem to be getting only AI matches for some reason. Maybe I I don't know if it's just us, but other other players are getting Have you gotten like a real player match?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. No, I haven't. We need to work it's on us.
SPEAKER_00: So I don't know what happened to our We we definitely have bugs. But I see people climbing the leaderboard. So I assume
SPEAKER_02: I think we're just letting you get Elo if you even if you play AI.
SPEAKER_00: No, no, no. I don't think so. My Elo doesn't didn't change after I won or lost my games.
SPEAKER_02: Uh interesting.
SPEAKER_00: So maybe we're stuck in some kind of
SPEAKER_02: Dang, how did I get to 27th place?
SPEAKER_00: Uh or maybe we're just stuck in some weird
SPEAKER_02: Well, I'm going to ask I'm going to ask my bot. What's going on?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, maybe maybe you can show us like how you would do a bug fix.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. So in this case, this is a bug I noticed, right? If it was a bug that was reported through some system where we'd find it ourselves, I would probably like ask the the engine to take care of it. But in this case, I'm just going to go to my founding engineer bot and say like, hey, I think our Elo our match making I'm just going to narrate for a second. Hey, so I think our Elo and our our matchmaking are messed up. What is happening right now is every time I play a game on thursdayarena.com, I uh get paired with an AI player instead of another another player's uh set or lineup. Um but for some reason on the leaderboard, the Elo scores are changing a bunch. And so not quite sure are some people getting paired and just like the matchmaking is off. Can you dig into that to figure out what's going on? Um use potato mode and um use a cursor cloud agent for the investigation. Um don't open a PR yet. Just come back to me with what you think is going on and then we can try and apply a fix.
SPEAKER_01: Can I share that?
SPEAKER_02: Um wait, let me I want to see more uh
SPEAKER_01: You can just mention like that you don't have to open it on you don't have to open Slack.
SPEAKER_02: Oh yeah, sure, sure.
SPEAKER_01: Oh we can at least say like that button now works.
SPEAKER_02: Okay. So we can cut over to my screen which I can show you what I've been cooking on uh for a little bit. So one thing um that I'm big on and you know, Lauren talked about these like feedback loops. Uh and we're working on basically getting feedback from users and then integrating that into the project. So now you can send feedback. And so if I say hey, what's up um and send that, we're going to be able to have that user feedback flow through into our Slack channel and I can see that I am getting feedback. Now uh obviously because we're submitting user generated content, there's a lot of moderation that's going on behind the scenes, rate limiting, um profanity, all of the things that you need to be very careful of, sanitization if you're logging something to a database. Um all the things you need to be careful of if you're accepting user input. And then also this is behind an authenticated route, right? So you have to authenticate with X. We know that we're not just accepting uh you know, submissions from anybody. Um but this is the first step right to being able to then take that feedback and action upon it. So maybe we could have Grokbot summarize the feedback that we're getting, um categorize that into features to then improve our application. Um and then we as a product team could decide, oh hey, this is actually really good feedback. We need to incorporate it. It's also a way you know, Lauren talked a lot about fuzzing or like testing our own application to start doing that at scale where we could have people reporting bugs. Um and then we could start running like automated bug reports on some of these submitted feedback. So this is one step. I'm also working on some other more creative ways and fun ways for you all to engage with the product um which should be coming soon. And then we're also kind of working on some like ads, sponsorship stuff. But I think we're desperately in need of a redesign as well. This UI is like making me cringe.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, there's a lot of good feedback coming in on the X post.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. So if you if you cut over to my screen real quick,
SPEAKER_02: So I'll go to Lauren's screen.
SPEAKER_01: Um so what I would love to do, I'm not going to show the feedback live of course as Matt said. But I do want to talk about like you know, as an engineer, how do you actually make use of feedback? Why is it so
SPEAKER_02: We can get over to uh to Lauren's screen so she can show off some of the feedback flows, please.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yes. I'll show you how I use Grokbot to set up like uh a factory. Um but yeah, while while we we get my screen on the on the screen uh on the top of
SPEAKER_02: There we go. There we go. Thanks.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, so what I what I usually do so again like if you're if you're looking at my Grokbot for the first time, Steve is my chief bot. And I talk to Steve and he delegates all my other bots. Um and uh the point I wanted to make here is that so I copied the link to our Slack channel. And I'm going to tell it something like like I'm going to uh use dictation. All right, Steve. Um the link above is a is our Slack channel that is receiving user feedback that uh players of our game are leaving for us. Um so I want to set up a factory workflow where we you know, look at the feedback, we triage it, we try to reproduce the issue, and then file a ticket uh in our Notion database. Um and that's this is going to be our first step for now. I'll eventually want to hook it up to you know, bots that can automatically fix those issues and open PRs. Um but we'll save that step for later. And then another thing that's really important about uh receiving user feedback uh you know, user generated content is that we want to filter for anything that isn't about the game or you know, it contains profanity or you know, link like weird links uh you know, and on and very importantly if we're doing using AI to review feedback, you want to tell your AI to um what do you call it? Uh watch out for prompt injections as well. So yeah, that's that's what I wanted to show. Um and then I'll I as as as always, I will just say rest this in your own words. Um and then I'll click like that.
SPEAKER_02: Cool.
SPEAKER_01: Uh is there anything else interesting we want to show?
SPEAKER_02: I might have something in shortly, not yet, but shortly.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I think we're I can talk about
SPEAKER_02: Okay, let's see what see I can talk about
SPEAKER_00: Can we look at the leaderboard? I I just looked at it recently. We can cut to my screen for a second if you'd like. Um
SPEAKER_01: So yeah, for sure.
SPEAKER_00: We have our first platinums.
SPEAKER_01: Oh dang, wow.
SPEAKER_00: We have our first platinum players.
SPEAKER_02: Grinding. This is crazy.
SPEAKER_01: Dang.
SPEAKER_00: To be fair, it's only Elo 1100. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Platinum's a great achievement. Congratulations to the six players, five players who have fought through our UI bugs to ascend the platinum ranks.
SPEAKER_01: I'm so impressed.
SPEAKER_00: We will we will make this better, but this is awesome. Um
SPEAKER_01: We we have we have to get these players some some prizes.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah, yeah. We'll Hey, the day is the day is young. It's only 10:43 Pacific. And I feel like there could be a lot of leaderboard shakeups happening really soon. I feel like I am commentating an eSports game. You know, it's like everyone
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, I want to say like maybe maybe we maybe we can figure out uh like uh like a set of prizes. Like maybe we can give out some Grokbot Ultra plans for people on the leaderboard.
SPEAKER_02: Ooh, okay.
SPEAKER_01: Uh we'll need to talk through the details, but maybe we can do something like the top 10 players, maybe. Uh we'll obviously need to get approval for that, but um
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: we'll we'll give our best shot and really appreciate everyone on the chat playing our game. Uh you can start sending feedback to us on Slack, on us not on Slack. I mean through the in-game feedback. And we'll start looking at them and start fixing them. Um we know that there are a lot of bugs and a lot of things to polish. So we really appreciate that, you know, the the time you're taking to to play our game and play test it.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. You know, one mechanics thing I'm thinking is every round you always get after the first round, you reset to the same goal. And so what you do mechanically is you always sell one bot, you buy a new bot, and you apply an upgrade. And I wonder if we should try to rethink that mechanic a bit because it sound I think right now what happens is you kind of do the same actions. There's still a bit of strategy for how you move the cards around, but you kind of do the same actions. Um you know, uh and so it feels like a little bit repetitive in terms of the the shop mechanic. That might be a thing for us to think about is like how we Excuse me, how we improve the shop mechanic.
SPEAKER_01: I also going to while while you do that, I'm going to tell the bot that I just made to um look at the feedback that we've gotten on Slack.
SPEAKER_00: Cool.
SPEAKER_01: And then categorize them and maybe make some charts uh you know, so that we can actually start seeing like maybe we have you know, a a majority of issues that are gameplay related or actual bugs. So
SPEAKER_00: Oh nice. So actually if you
SPEAKER_01: I'll try to get that out soon.
SPEAKER_00: I was going to say if you can cut over to uh my screen, Matt's screen real quick, we can show some of the feedback that's coming in. It's actually pretty great. Um
SPEAKER_01: Very very brave.
SPEAKER_00: I mean I I've audited the feedback. And we are we are moderating it. Oh my goodness, this is wild.
SPEAKER_01: Almost that.
SPEAKER_00: So this was me doing a play test that we hadn't tried before. I actually tried to spend all my gold and then realized if you do that, you end up stuck because you cannot buy new bots. Um yeah, we should Actually, I'm going to report that as an issue too. Um sorry, but we can go Can we go to Matt's screen and pull up the uh feedback channels that we're seeing come in?
SPEAKER_02: Oh yeah, that's that's only about
SPEAKER_00: Pending.
SPEAKER_02: Pending, pending.
SPEAKER_01: In the meantime, I'm just enjoying my cappuccino.
SPEAKER_00: I'm I'm just stuck. I need to log out. There is no log out.
SPEAKER_01: Is the sign out button not working? Classic.
SPEAKER_00: Okay. Classic. Okay, cool. We got a lot of bug fixes. Are we logging these anywhere? Are we putting them into Slack?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah, the uh yeah, the the feedback's all going to Slack, right?
SPEAKER_00: If you have the Slack but if you have the Slack open, Roshan, you can also take a look at it, but I don't want to put you on the spot.
SPEAKER_01: Oh where is it? Uh maybe don't do that. I think let Matt do it cuz you
SPEAKER_00: You're you're on a you scrolled to a good part good part.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, I mean like it's it's very heavily moderated just to be clear. There's there's a lot of filtering filtering going on. So
SPEAKER_01: Okay, thank you. Thanks everybody in our chat for being so nice.
SPEAKER_02: Well, actually we're just not seeing the people that aren't being nice because you know, I'll actually take a step back, right? When you get when you receive like freeform text over the internet, like you have to be very careful. So what we're doing is both filtering on the client side for
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_02: you know, length and a few other things, but then on the server side uh we're filtering for again, I mentioned profanity. Um we're sanitizing all the user inputs so that we're not getting some sort of like uh injection uh attacks or anything like that. And then we're running it through uh ExAI models to prevent um other basically catch all uh guards. And so that way you can make sure that user submissions are are are safe. We also have rate limiting uh in place and some other things to make sure that we're getting um again uh good user feedback. Um and oh we're some people are getting 429 too many requests errors on the on the actual API side. So you might be starting to overload the server a little bit. Um but yeah, if we can take a look at my screen or I guess if Roshan can can check out Slack, it should be we should be good to take a look at the feedback.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah, following Oh Production team, can we get Matt's screen on?
SPEAKER_02: Uh yeah, so here we go. Cupcake You're going to have to zoom in way way much more here. But this is a good example here of of what it means to to like have users play tests and then collect this feedback. And so you know, when you're using AI, context or data uh can really take any form. And this is this is data about our game, uh data about what's broken, what people want. Um let people buy extra gold so you can earn money. Even that makes it a bit play to win. We'll have to think about that one. That's more of a product direction. Uh it needs a theme. Um Elo points. Okay, so we have some mix of bug reports, requests, uh and uh you know, just feedback generally. So what we might want to do is start to categorize this which I it looks like you're already doing, Lauren. I'm not Yeah, I'm actually getting my my Grokbot to post some charts to this channel.
SPEAKER_00: Oh great.
SPEAKER_02: So in in like a few seconds, we'll see the charts show up. Um and I guess some fun trivia is that we actually have a very similar process setup. Uh oh yeah, I guess you can see the the charts on my screen. Um so I just I just got us to do one one quick pass to look through all the feedback and categorize them. And I like doing this because it gives me a a high level overview of the the main things we have to fix. So obviously like a lot of people have reported uh issues with the mobile layouts. So we definitely need to fix that first. Uh only AI no ranked matchmaking is another one that we've seen ourselves. So we should fix that. Elo as well, a very important um yeah, that's really a lot of good feedback here that we we we definitely need to go in get the factory loose on fixing.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, we should probably get some Exactly. Yeah, I think that'd be really great. Um
SPEAKER_02: Uh but um I guess this is you know, classic first launch that we really scraply put together is 71% of our issues are bugs, right? And so as a game studio and I I I think like a fledgling game studio, I feel like it's really important for us to think about like prioritization. Uh I'm curious how you think about it, Roshan, but I always for me as a gamer myself, you know, uh I always feel that when a game studio launches their game, the most important thing actually is to prioritize bug fixes and stability and reliability or performance issues.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. You have to make the core loop like great.
SPEAKER_02: Great. And I often see sometimes that
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: game studios might you know, rush into, oh you know, we need to add all these features. We have such a big roadmap of cool ideas we want to ship. And it's always very exciting to work on the the next shiny thing. But I think that like personally the the best games I've played are the ones that are just relentless about crafting a beautiful experience, like a a really really fun game. And you know, I think that's that's really important. And I can see you know, like this is clearly something we need to prioritize. We have 71% of our feedback are bugs. We have 16% praise, which is actually pretty good. You know, I I feel like I
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Oh they're being really nice. We're just like
SPEAKER_02: Our our chat chat You guys are being so nice.
SPEAKER_00: I'm I'm literally moderating out all the all the all the mean comments.
SPEAKER_02: Uh yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Hey, there's one in here that has gift potato arrays, which I think is pretty cool.
SPEAKER_02: Gift me arrays. Yeah, I don't mind.
SPEAKER_00: Plus one. I heard uh actually speaking of so I heard I heard someone you have a new subscriber on X that might
SPEAKER_02: Oh no.
SPEAKER_00: I heard Elon might be subscriber.
SPEAKER_02: Uh yeah. Um thank thank you. Thank you boss for the for the $2 a month. Very appreciated.
SPEAKER_00: It's sick. Uh cool. So we're also I'm also working on some other ways to submit feedback, maybe a little bit more uh fun ways uh that that might be worth a demo in a few minutes. So we might have something fun for you there. And then I'm also uh just merged in a bunch of favicon and like uh SEO stuff.
SPEAKER_02: Oh nice. Should Should we go to your screen?
SPEAKER_00: You want to share screen? Yeah, we can cut over here now. I think I had some HTML issues uh previously.
SPEAKER_02: Let's go to Matt's screen. Here we go.
SPEAKER_00: Um Cool. So uh it actually updated the text as a little bit as well, which I wasn't expecting. But now we have like a proper favicon. So like in the on the site, you can see the favicon there. And if you ever like want to take a look at your developer console, um you can see in the actual elements if I start searching for uh OG meta, I believe. Meta. Meta. You'll start to see like OG tags come through. Um so like this is a bit more developer focused, right? A bit more developer centric. And there are other ways to take a look at this. You can install like Chrome extensions essentially. But like having proper OG titles, OG descriptions, um site names, and images. So like here's a V1 OG image. Um this is like when you post a link to uh to Twitter, this is what'll come through. And so it's kind of like basics of like social media stuff. You can see I updated our Twitter as well that if you post a link, you kind of want it to look nice. Um I won't post this here, but you you'd want a preview. So what you can do is go like SEO preview uh website um OpenGraph. This is a good one. And then you can paste your URL and just make sure like, okay, when people post about my site, does it have a nice preview? Do we have uh you know, like the right meta tags? And like we currently don't. So these are the things that typically if you have a business or if you're trying to make yourself visible online to people and then eventually to agents, which we can talk about as well, you want to make sure that all of these properties are populated and optimized to tell people what you are trying to do and why they should use it, whether that's a game, a business, or any of these things. So step one to having proper uh to having people be aware of your product is have it is it accurately communicating what your product is. And so that's what we're trying to do.
SPEAKER_00: Cool. Maybe it's time for a quick quick roundup of um what we're working on just to kind of check in with each other. So we have a bunch of great feedback coming in. We showed some of the feedback. We have a Slack channel. We're going to work on automating some of that feedback and uh trying to get that into our coding engine that we built. So for those who are just joining, earlier this morning we talked about a coding engine that we built. We're watching Matt do some live prompting, I think. Um all this stuff is flying around basically. We have um you know, a whole engine where we can take the feedback that's coming in from you all, post moderated feedback, also the feedback that we're noticing ourselves, feed it to our bots, have our bots build PRs and then kind of come back with uh you know, come back with PRs, play test bots. We'll play test those changes for us. Um we have some UI refresh work that's going on. Thank you for all the feedback on that so far. Um and yeah, lots of great stuff. And so really I think what sounds like our next you know, maybe a few minutes here should just be trying to get as much stuff as many bugs fixed as possible, right? Sounds good to me. We're at 476 followers on Twitter. So that's great. But our with our one tweet, we're live. Also we'll follow You know, we got to we got to follow Big Man. So we follow Elon. Um
SPEAKER_02: Oh amazing. Yes.
SPEAKER_00: We are also not we're not verified. So uh what is the UI? Yo CL, we're working on it, dude. Uh
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, the uh this was very very scraply put together.
SPEAKER_00: 800 plus We do have a UI redesign coming.
SPEAKER_02: Okay.
SPEAKER_01: It's just it's just not finished yet. But um I didn't want to say like I think this is very common like when you're first starting a project, it's not going to be perfect. Uh you know, um especially when you have three people working together and different agents, different prompting, uh different art direction, different different things like that. It's very easy to you know, fall into like a low quality uh I guess product. And so we you know, if this was a real game uh I mean or a real I guess it is a real game. If this was like more serious like a a legit venture, I think we'd actually spend more time polishing.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: We did want to launch it to extremely early because we wanted to get it you know what uh our chat playing with us and interacting with us um and you know, getting uh like feedback and showing what you can do with Grokbot in just three days. Um and and we also wanted to show you a lot about the behind the scenes work of setting up a game studio or a company where you want to think about not just a product development, but all of the other parts, the supporting pieces, right? So right now I have a bot that's um I'm spinning up uh that is uh
SPEAKER_00: Maybe we can take a look at Lauren's screen.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I can show you what I'm doing. So I just told Doctor Eggbot. So Doctor Eggbot is again like our uh my bot template that is responsible for uh oh uh responsible for creating bots for me. And I just
SPEAKER_00: Uh Lauren, screen on the production side when we get a chance, please. Thank you.
SPEAKER_01: Yes. Uh I I told Doctor Eggbot, let's get Oh I'm telling Steve, my chief, let's get Doctor Eggbot to create a bot to triage feedback and work with Crumb with my play tester bot to reproduce the bug and then file the issue in Notion if it's confirmed. And you can start to see the factory is starting to go in into place. Um unblock edge 403 uh maybe let's do uh I think we'll leave that. Um but yeah, so the new bot is Crumble. Um and it's starting to look it's going through all the the feedback. It's found some P zeros, blank screens. Definitely not a good thing. Uh can't select empty bard spots. Uh the rank and Elo UI goes stale. So we definitely want to get those fixed ASAP.
SPEAKER_00: Do you want me to go ahead and invite cursor to the Slack channel while you're doing that?
SPEAKER_01: Yes, please please do that.
SPEAKER_00: Let me take care of that. I saw that was a bot suggestion. So
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. And then I'm going to say I'm going to I'm going to do some voice dictation. Uh the voice dictation button not working. Uh okay, I'll I'll just type and narrate. So I'm going to say okay, so now that we have triage workflow, we we have a triage workflow for the confirmed bugs and issues. Uh the new Crumble uh triage agent should um work with hater to start um fixing those issues. Um and uh using potato mode for maybe not full autopilot, but do we dare to to autopilot? I mean let let's try that right now.
SPEAKER_02: Are we betting on full autopilot this whole time?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I think let let's just try that as well. Um but one really important thing about autopilot is um but since we are now live in production, it's very critical that we do not break the game for everyone. So we need to always rigorously uh verify our work with the slash verify cupcake. That's just the name of the skill we have. Skill and swarms. So what this will do is uh we're going to uh tell our bots to work together um using some of the skills that we have in P Stack. And very importantly, we need we need them to reproduce uh the issue first. And then only if they can actually reproduce the bug, uh can we trust that the agent understands uh you know, like the the problem in the first place? And that actually is a good question. I think we need to have another bot that will be responsible for checking the work. I'll say also work uh with Hashbrown to uh let's say validate that the triage was done correctly. And that the triage agent or triage bot uh actually understood the users's feedback. So once we confirm all of these things, we can do the full autopilot fixes. Um
SPEAKER_00: and the verifications forms. So, verifications forms are essentially so the swarm skill in P stack is a skill that teaches your bot how to spawn many cloud agents in cursor. And so these cloud agents will are have their own computer, you know, they're kind of separate from the Grok bot computer and they will be able to run the the game on their own machines and actually click around and test things and fuzz it. So this is like a a thing we love to say in S V S A I is like we're fuzzing. And when we say fuzzing, we just mean like you're actually using the application like a real power user, you know, clicking every little button, you're trying every little edge case or really trying to stress test and break the game. And so the idea here is that if we have a swarm of bots or agents that can actually do that for us, it takes us humans out of the loop there because I don't have to sit here and you know click and play the game and and you know test it and find the bugs. Um I can have my bots do that for me. Um of course we're going to we're going to continue to do that ourselves but and we'll find a lot of issues that way with as well with human fuzzing. But you know when you when you start getting feedback like this, it's it's this is something that you can cut you can try to set up. So I'm going to kick that off. Hit enter and cross my fingers that everything's going to work really well. Um but again going back to why I think it's so important to disconnect all the data you can to Grok bot. This is exactly why, right? We have our Grok bots all hooked up to our to our tech stack. Uh we have you know Vercel connection, Planet Scale. Uh we have data coming in from Slack, user feedback. This gives us this really nice way to set up a loop where we're getting you know data from the outside, um you know external data and bringing it all together, making sense of it and then feeding our inner loop, right? Our inner loop being the loop that powers all of the engineering work that we do. And when these two loops work together, when we and and of course it's going to need a lot of fine tuning. I'm going to ask Dr. Egg bot to help me design this really well. But when it works, it's beautiful. Right? You you know you have like an like more of automation, complete automation where in theory if I had set it up right, bugs will just get fixed automatically. The game just gets better constantly without me having to babysit the whole process. And that frees me up to actually go work on features or polish, you know like other things that maybe the bugs aren't going to catch.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: So
SPEAKER_01: Well what I what I love about that too is it's sort of like it just speaks to the importance of building your agent system, right? I think that's like kind of you know put it in in sort of like a way that that I think about it is like take the time to set up your systems, take the time to set up how your like your bots talk to each other, how your agents talk to each other. Um and I think that like gives you a lot of leverage later on, right? So you know um when I'm like building something quickly, I find this is actually the hardest part because I never want to sit down and just take the step back and build the systems work but it really does pay a ton a dividend and I think you're seeing examples here, right? Where we have all these bots that Lauren has set up and they're kind of like able to talk to each other. You kind of know what each one's working on and your product just starts cranking. So um maybe just to do a quick programming update. So I think we're at about a little past 11:00 a m Pacific time. If you're just joining us, we are hanging out here on day three of our 72 hour live stream where we are building a business from scratch. We are building a game studio and just launched our first game Thursday arena dot com if you want to check it out. Just for folks who are watching, the only official sources of content, Thursday arena dot com and at Thursday arena on X. If you see anything from any other account that is not us, we are just at Thursday arena on X and Thursday arena dot com. Those are official. Um so yeah keep get get your news from the source. Um we have been showing off a bunch of features that we've added like a feedback channel that's coming into Slack and getting our bots to start reading all those Slack messages. Um we are going to have a guest joining us at 11:15 to well you know now that we have a product, we should probably figure out how we make money. And so Vincent's going to join us in about 15 minutes. Um before that I think we might have a video we want to show looking at production. Yes we we do. So why don't we do this? We're going to keep working. We got a bunch of things that we're going to go fix. Obviously the bug fixes will keep coming throughout the day. So please keep the feedback coming. Let's cut to a quick video. I think about a few minutes. You'll see us back on for a second and then we'll transition into chatting with Vincent.
SPEAKER_00: Cool. Yeah I think it it's a it's a good it's a good time to actually start thinking about like how do we actually turn this game into not just a toy but a real business. So I think
SPEAKER_01: Right. Right.
SPEAKER_00: it'd be really cool to see what ideas Vincent has.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah I'm excited too. Uh and Vincent's great. So yeah let's kick to that video whenever we're ready and we'll be right back.
SPEAKER_02: My name's Kyle Day. I am uh the S V P of product and engineering for one of our product development divisions at Nokia. We are trying to leverage cursor as an agentic platform to introduce specialized agents that are persona specific for every aspect of work that we do that can partner with the human in seat that does that work today. Those things become much more possible if we are able to iterate in much much faster loops that directly impacts customer economics, uh lowers unit cost, improves customer satisfaction and then finally there's an entire class of things that I think we're now going to be able to do faster that are to do with increasing resilience, reliability and security in the network. Cursor and uh cursor's agents uh that are increasingly many of them are out of the box is a massive step up in accelerating analysis, getting insights that otherwise would not be possible. So we're at the beginning of a very critical journey. We've burnt the boats. Our plans, our goals for this year, not next year, for this year hinge on this working. We have a product line, easily 50 plus million lines of code. We are I would say in an intermediate stage of decomposing what is fundamentally a monolith oriented architecture. It would be a very daunting task for us to attempt a manual inspection of that code base. We have undertaken that with cursor. Our early results of that analysis have been remarkable. We have been able to do precisely what I just described which would have required the spoke tooling would have taken far longer, probably several months of effort across probably a dozen or more expert people. We performed the initial analysis as one example within a matter of I think a couple of weeks by two people. We've seen evidence of cursor being deployed very successfully in situations that involve a need to move very quickly where we have run into a customer impacting defect that might be having a subscriber impact and now we're able to do that against an extremely large corpus of service requests and radically accelerate uh something like a root cause analysis. These examples have not been one or two. They've been quite a few and growing in number. That's where we're seeing uh I'd say the early success and where we would love to take it next is leveraging cursor as a platform for multi-agent deployment and orchestration where really the role of the engineer, the architect becomes the supervision of agents that are calling out to tools that are performing work at scale, collaborating with one another. We are literally redesigning our entire software development life cycle from inception through product delivery and everything that comes in between.
SPEAKER_01: Welcome back for those of you joining us. Well we have a new face. We'll get to that in just a moment but welcome back to our live stream here at Grok bot Galaxy. Uh my name is Roshan, Roshan underscore S on X. We have been streaming for three days. Well this is day three. So we're two and a two days and change in at this point. Um building a business live on X and just to give you a quick recap of how the week's gone so far. We started out on Tuesday with an idea for a physical pop up. We pivoted our business like every pop every business does um into building a game studio. And so just just this morning just a little while ago we launched our very first game Thursday arena dot com and uh have the at Thursday arena handle on X. So those are our official sources, Thursday arena dot com, at Thursday arena on X. And um we've had a team of folks, a bunch of fun folks we've brought in, guests, internal SpaceX AI, also folks who are out there in the community helping other people build great businesses. And so with that would love to introduce Vincent. Vincent you want to introduce yourself and share a little bit about what you do and yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah excited to be here. Uh I am on the growth team at SpaceX AI. So that's just how we think about you know uh there's a lot of interest for our awesome products. How do we make sure we tell more people who want to find out more about them uh and and figure out how they want to use them and and really speak to them.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah so um what is growth?
SPEAKER_03: Yeah this is a great question. It kind of really depends on the company that you're working at, you know like at a P L G kind of business like our own. Um you know you want to really appeal to users and like really figure out what they're doing. That's like a lot of life cycle maybe like hey you see I saw you maybe struggling in product on something. We should put a nudge there and and figure out how to help you out. Um in a more sales led kind of approach it's like mass email outbound and LinkedIn. There's a whole you know businesses built around that even. So it really just depends on what your business kind of looks like.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah and so I guess um you mentioned P L G. So that's product led growth, right? So businesses where people are signing up and that kind of feels like what we're doing. So have you had a chance to look at our stream or see what we've built at all?
SPEAKER_03: That's right. Yeah. Totally. Yeah yeah probably yeah let's see let's see what the recap is.
SPEAKER_01: Okay cool. If we can pull up my screen please. So um this is our game. We're working on the U I. We got a lot of stuff we got to do. So uh you know cut us a little bit of Slack. I'll actually show you the full experience because you know I feel like whenever I've worked with with folks who think about growth, they want to see the end to end funnel. So maybe we could look at this together. I want you to just absorb as much as you can. And so for for everyone in the chat, everyone on the stream what we're going to do, Vincent is an expert on all of this business stuff. We have a product. We haven't yet turned it into a business. And so what I'm hoping we can do in the next like 15 or 20 minutes is get all the great insights for how we can go and make this a business and figure out how we can grow more usage. Obviously we're in a really lucky position to have a bunch of people watching. So thank you all for for everyone who's watching. Um that's been a great way. Yeah growth versus dream, right? Um
SPEAKER_03: Well love the U I. That's been a great way. Many eyeballs.
SPEAKER_01: so yeah here's our game. You go in, you log in with X. Um so we already maybe something interesting there. You know authorize the app. This is great. And then here's what we see. So we have our leader board and um the leader board's kind of cool. We have this sort of stack rank where you can uh you know earn points and earn your improve your E L O score as you fight as you play more matches. And uh let's see oh man I keep dropping. I am uh I'm down to 35. I was in first place for an hour.
SPEAKER_03: Oh man. Love that. That's so cool. Oh man. Oh man. My growth hack. First thing I'm thinking is like it could be cool to put a little share pop up as soon as you go on leader board. Be like this is my ranking, you know on on uh this game.
SPEAKER_01: Ooh. Yep yep. Yep. I'm going to I'm going to if you don't mind. I'm going to make a growth bot called Vincent.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah yeah. Let's do it.
SPEAKER_01: Oh man. Uh hold on. He didn't let me name him before I started. Vincent growth. And uh I'm going to hey start logging some great growth ideas in notion. Make a growth playbook uh that all uh add stuff to. So okay first thing you said was um we have a leader board in the app and we should have a share option so you can share a spot on the leader board. Is that right?
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Yeah. By the way Vincent as soon as the game ends and you're like kind of like old arcade style, you know you're you're putting in your name or like I guess these are X handles from what I can infer. Uh you can then like have a pop and it's like press this share button to you know post on X and brag to your friends that you got this ranking out of whatever on the game.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yep. Okay. Great. I just narrate I just captured that voice audio. We're just going to ship that to the agent. Um we'll just keep doing this. This is great. So anytime you see an opportunity to shout out we'll we'll capture it. We have almost a thousand users on our leader board. So I don't know pretty good, right? Decent.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah our leader board stuff. I love voice bot. Yeah yeah. That's pretty good. That's that's insane.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah okay okay cool. You heard it here from from from a person person who works on this professionally.
SPEAKER_03: I got it I got it yeah.
SPEAKER_01: So so that's the leader board. And then you know we have a few other things here. So you can go into the actual game loop and this might be really fun. So I'm going to start over. And here's the oh start again. Here's how the game works is uh well let's do this. I'm going to make this full screen and then I'll zoom a little bit because I know it's a little hard to see. Um so you get these little bots and these are all bots from our bot market place.
SPEAKER_03: Love it. Got to plug the market place. A good growth area for us.
SPEAKER_01: So you know yeah so Yeah definitely a good growth area for us, right? And we actually were thinking maybe over time we could make it so you could bring your own bots into the chat too and play game. And that might be a really fun mechanic, right? Yes these bots have these stats. They have like an attack stat and a health stat. And um you just basically get start the game with a shop and some gold and you can buy your little team.
SPEAKER_03: That'd be really cool. That would be cool.
SPEAKER_01: Oh that's cool.
SPEAKER_03: And the way the game works is that you're setting a lineup. And so you know the they all have different abilities. So for example when this character faints, it gives the two friends behind it plus one plus one. So I probably want to put them in the first slot so that you know I can I can take advantage of that ability for as many as many players as I can behind him.
SPEAKER_01: Oh that's Yeah yeah. Uh this one whenever the game starts, it deals one damage to the last living enemy. And whenever this player starts, so I think I might want to put him in the back actually. And then this gives 50% of its attack to the friend ahead. So it's a little bit of a strategy game. You kind of set your lineup.
SPEAKER_03: Mm. Yeah cool.
SPEAKER_01: And then you know you just go through this fight so you can kind of see on the screen there. Uh you kind of get paired up with an opponent. The opponents all have different abilities of their own. Uh and you kind of see what happens and the game as the game plays itself. So sort of like an auto battler if you've seen those.
SPEAKER_03: It's a cool cool yeah man. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And so that was round one. The game is played over three rounds and so there's a bit of uh you know in between rounds mechanic where you can do some more strategizing.
SPEAKER_03: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: So in this case I have some new bots I can buy. Here's Critikito, one of my favorite bots. The design critique bot that uh Manuel and our design team has made which is really wonderful. Uh so this deals two damage to the enemy front. It's it's an uncommon card which is kind of cool. So I can uh maybe in this case I'm going to it's got a lot of health.
SPEAKER_03: So there's like different rankings of different cards right now. So you have like different tiering of like scarcity essentially.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Exactly. Yeah there's scarcity to it and we can tune all the logic, right? So some we can we can really play with any of these things. Um I also like these abilities.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Could be cool also do a share online thing. I'm playing this game, share. If you share one card, you can get a another card maybe.
SPEAKER_01: Oh I like that. Okay. So let's try to let's try to capture that idea. Go for it.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah of course absolutely. Yeah so like when you're in the game and there's since there's a lot of scarcity in terms of doing ranking for the cards, uh it would be a cool growth mechanic to maybe be able to have you share uh a bot that you may or a like card that you made uh and then in exchange for somebody else maybe downloading, you then get like a more rare version of that card.
SPEAKER_01: Ooh I like that. Okay. So like bringing rarity and sort of like you know uh making that like a part of the game loop. Okay great. I'll lock that in.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. That's right yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um cool. I love it. Okay and let me finish up the game so you can see the the the funnel, right? So we have our
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: continue. I won the second round. It looks like I'm on round three now. Thanks. I'm I'm one I'm tied one one. So we'll see we'll see if I can win. Um we have a projects manager which gives the front most guy two attack. Well we're just showing you an example here. So I'm going to see I have 10 gold I think right now. I have 10 gold. I'm going to sell this guy. Buy this guy.
SPEAKER_03: I have one dot. Yeah. Well gold's important too so it sounds like in this mechanic that would be cool.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah gold's sort of how you change up your lineup in between each round. So yeah so there might be something to play with there but yeah I'm just powered up this spot.
SPEAKER_03: That's really cool. Yeah could be like play a couple rounds in a row for instance and you don't take any breaks, get more gold potentially. Kind of like a streaky
SPEAKER_01: Mm let's skip skip the shop or something. Yeah yeah I like that.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah exactly.
SPEAKER_01: Okay let's see what happens. We're just going to speed this up so we can get to the end of the loop. There you go and that's it. And so in this one I took I take the round and boom I win.
SPEAKER_03: Wow. Amazing.
SPEAKER_01: We definitely need to share a screen on this, right? Yeah yeah yeah okay. I would love if that's an easy one.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um we probably need to add a share screen to the win screen. Share button to the win screen so that when you win you can share your result uh and be able to brag about that on X.
SPEAKER_03: That's right. Yeah. Yeah. Cool.
SPEAKER_01: Cool.
SPEAKER_03: Can players challenge each other directly? Like if if I'm Vincent, I want to specifically challenge you.
SPEAKER_01: No. Yeah. Ooh I really like that. Okay okay.
SPEAKER_03: I think that'd be kind of interesting because that opens up a lot of like invite your friends and stuff like that. Maybe complicated for it's like a definitely maybe yeah. So for the rest of the day.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. How about how about another idea where we make it so that players can call out or challenge another player if they're choosing. Maybe the other player has to accept the challenge. Kind of like uh words with friends kind of thing going on. Yeah yeah okay let's add that too.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Yeah yeah exactly. That's a yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And for those of you who are watching and kind of seeing what we're doing, we're just literally riffing about growth ideas. I'm just kind of feeding those into Grok bot with the voice transcription. It's not perfect. There's a lot of like yeah how about that in the in the in the bot but
SPEAKER_03: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: like the bots figured it out, right? The agents figured it out. You can kind of just keep giving them things. Um I'll pull up the notion doc in a minute here but this bot is just logging all this feedback. Vincent our Vincent bot is logging all this feedback into into notion for us. And then um
SPEAKER_03: Sure. Very meta.
SPEAKER_01: you know earlier we talked about the software factory. We're just going to let the software factory loose on these ideas. We'll just throw agents at them. We'll try things out. It'll give us P R s. It'll give us play tests and we'll be able to kind of experiment with all this. So
SPEAKER_03: Yeah stuff. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: all right so that's the core loop. We have uh this win screen. Obviously some cleanup we got to do here. And that's it. So you go back home. Um in that case I don't think I earned any E L O points but that's okay. We'll figure that out. Um and yeah and you can see the leader board and and there we are. So yeah what are your thoughts?
SPEAKER_03: So kind of That's great. That's awesome. I think that's that's this is great. And I think uh it's also really cool that you have your own surface areas like a website and an X account. Like those are I think not enough people think about things like that. Uh and uh I think you know as I was watching the stream and and thinking about it I was like wow we're we're we have so many eyeballs, concurrent viewers right now. Uh it's really important if if they're following X maybe for the first time that the Thursday arena account uh to be able to capture some of that love. So I think it's sometimes important we're um
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Okay. even though you have like the eyeballs maybe you need to very target the action that you want people to take. And so maybe something cool we could put on the account is like uh every time somebody follows
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. So hold on do you mind just Yeah. Go.
SPEAKER_01: So now every time somebody follows the at Thursday arena X handle, maybe we could automatically D M them being like hey thank you for following. You should try out our game here. Maybe get 10 free gold.
SPEAKER_03: Oh okay.
SPEAKER_01: Uh that could be kind of cool too.
SPEAKER_03: I like that. Okay. So some way to sort of take the and so if I'm thinking about the rights like we have X as sort of our our uh platform.
SPEAKER_01: That's right yeah.
SPEAKER_03: And we kind of use the followers as a way to drive traffic to the game. So how do you think about that? Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Totally totally. Because right now I you know our our sources of how people are finding out are pretty narrow which is pretty much just this stream or you know maybe post on X.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Uh plug the X A P I. You could probably use the X A P I, scrape who's talking about Thursday arena. What are your thoughts, critiques, reviews?
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah we actually have an X uh connector in Grok bot. And so I actually already have it connected I think.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah yeah. Amazing.
SPEAKER_03: Um so maybe we should just do that right now, right? Maybe we'll just say um hey do a quick search of all of the feedback to Thurs
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Thursday arena, Thursday arena on X. Um and summarize it um in a new section in your notion doc.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Like with user handles too. So important for the D M.
SPEAKER_01: Focus. Yeah on product feedback. Cool.
SPEAKER_03: That's right.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah um yeah so this is this is really great. You can just use the X M C P and and connect to connect to one of the best platforms. So um love it love it. Okay while you were talking I was trying to multitask as best I can. I showed this beforehand. We have this bot whose job it is to make dashboards. And so we talked about this before but uh off camera but internally when we launched products at SpaceX AI, this is one of my favorite things is I just spin up a metrics bot and I'm like hey your job is every 15 minutes to give me the launch pulse. How many users are using it? How's the feature going? Are there bugs that we're hearing? Uh as a P M it's in incredible to be able to do this because you can basically just get your live you get a live dash. It's like just if you have a little data intern that's just feeding you like reports on a paper but it's happening in Grok bot.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah so Love it. Yeah. Yeah. Totally. That's right. And and something else I think we've we've a lot of first too is definitely like maybe monitoring Slack. Like people have comments and they're oh we would love to see that data slice and so you can have it kind of work with also your Slack bot or something like that.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. And so you can get it all on demand, right? So I want this data. I get that data. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_03: That's right. Exactly. It's like immediately plugging and playing into the dash board.
SPEAKER_01: So one thing I wanted to run by you is I I I got some graphs earlier. I just asked my my data scientist here to refresh with the latest. So this is as of what 11:25 a m Pacific two minutes ago. Looks like we have about 2200 practice rounds, a thousand X sign ins. Um started to measure this funnel for like a practice to an X login. I don't know is there anything we could do with that funnel? Like how do you how do you think about a funnel for this product?
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Yeah. Wow. Yeah uh from the X can we go back to the screens for the X and the practice funnel?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah so when you're in so basically let me log out here. If I log out and I just hit practice, we obviously could do some cleanup here but there's an option to log in with X.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Oh cool. Interesting.
SPEAKER_01: Um so you can just play the game, get a feel for how it works. You know we didn't want to create a barrier so you don't have to sign in just to play.
SPEAKER_03: Uh Maybe it's like uh well maybe you could definitely like do a few things. I think one simple the the simple version would maybe be like you practice you know two three times in a row and then you get the pop up to sign in with X to like continue into game. That could be kind of cool.
SPEAKER_01: Ooh. Mhm.
SPEAKER_03: Um and then uh if I were to really put on like my my so my roommates actually in gaming. So I think he always talks about these like reward mechanisms. And so something that could be kind of cool would be uh you know when you maybe you let the user in practice rounds win a little bit more favorably. And then you kind of can let people get a good feel and be like oh I really actually want to play this game.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Mm. Um Hello I like that. Yeah. Let practice users win more often.
SPEAKER_03: They kind of cool. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um it's actually fun you mentioned that uh more often. Uh one of the metrics that we were looking at earlier is we had a um some game game engine metrics because we really you know we haven't built a ton of games before. We've played a lot of games.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um but essentially we were looking at the win loss ratio. So this is early. This is from like the first hour but it was about four of like pretty pretty pretty hard games before. Um so you might want to tweak that uh but you know I think that's exactly your point is we should maybe look at that slice across practice versus logged in so we have a better idea of like what that looks like and that might be a funnel impacting too. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Yeah it's really hard game. Yeah. Totally. Totally. Or you can def I don't know if we've introduced like difficulty modes of like the simulated opponents.
SPEAKER_01: Yep. We haven't yet and that's also a great idea. So I think it's a great feature maybe. Right now it's just an A I um and then the head to head version that we're cleaning up but um yeah I think we have a I have a bot here whose job is to be the game designer critique. And so they they came back with a critique here that looks like we have the game is too hard for launch. Um so yeah we should fix that. We should fix that. Um I want to go back to some of the latest funnel stats. So this is what we came in at 11:25 so a few minutes ago here.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And um practice sessions, practice to X, anything else. Let me pull up uh well looks like we've had some tapering off on new sign ups. Thank you for everyone who caused our launch spike. Um
SPEAKER_03: We're going to start outbounding you now. That's the that's the only solution.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah right. Well tell us about outbound. Yeah like what are your thoughts on outbound marketing? How does it work? Like should we do any outbound here?
SPEAKER_03: Yeah. Totally. Um outbound's really tricky. I I mean we've all are like uh maybe victims of outbound marketing. It's not something that you kind of want to receive most of the time. Uh and so I think I was actually talking about this with somebody yesterday. I think the thing about outbound to get right is you just want to make sure people read your thing. And uh I think if you really think about how people read things today, it's like
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. do I when you open your email, you kind of look if if you open your email I guess I would ask you it's like what is the first thing you look at do you think?
SPEAKER_03: Oh man. Um I think I always get overwhelmed by the spam. Like all the random stuff there that I'm like managed to unsubscribe from this.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Totally.
SPEAKER_00: unsubscribe from this.
SPEAKER_01: Totally. Totally. For me, I'm guilty of I just always look at the name of the person or like the vendor, not the subject line, not like the hook, or crazy like you must open this or whatever. And so I think I always think about it like, okay, how do we then figure out who we know? And like how do we make sure you remember the names that like you've seen these names before. They're friendly faces that you've seen on X or a LinkedIn or maybe on promotional videos. And so
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. I think we should get Lauren Potato to start sending emails.
SPEAKER_01: That's what I was going to have to say. Maybe Potato has to start sending some emails or Potato starts sending some DMs to people who follow.
SPEAKER_00: Here's here's Vincent Bot here. Okay. Um Potato should send emails from Potato so we can leverage her cult of her her her fan following
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: to drive to drive usage.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, and something I'm experimenting with a lot now even is is definitely like the concept of giving your bot like an email. And I think that stuff can get really cool and I think we'll open up kind of a new paradigm there.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Okay, we should definitely do that. Yeah, give our bot an email address and have let it rip and send a bunch of stuff, manage our campaigns.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly. Yes. Totally. Exactly. You could probably go scrape maybe like like let's call it like developer ecosystem people maybe at like these large gaming studios and you can on LinkedIn and you can enrich, you know, their email of the of their work email and be like, hey, just building this new game, you can check out hey, us building this on stream here, but be like if you want to check it out, download.
SPEAKER_00: Build a mailing list and contact list to reach out to
SPEAKER_01: To yeah, exactly. Like gaming developer ecosystem type people. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Okay. Okay. Okay. Um great. This is this is all amazing. We didn't know any of this. So um I want to go back to the funnel here. Like what's interesting here is we don't really have a a strong re need to convert people to signed in, at least not yet. So you know, one of the other things we're starting to think a little about is monetization. And so I'm also just curious for your thoughts on that, right? So we have a product, we have a maybe some ideas for how we grow usage. Um I know we've had like had a bunch of folks over the course of these free few days talking about how do you make money. Obviously we care a lot about that too. I shared earlier we're in the classic um San Francisco startup vibe where we're just trying to get users at all costs and we'll figure out how to monetize it later. Um but it might be good to have a little bit of an idea, right? So what are your thoughts? I mean just kind of what you see what you're seeing.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Mhm. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Totally. Totally. Yeah. Gaming is so interesting. I first of I'm not by no means a gaming expert. But sometimes we read some things, yeah, that that people do. And so that's that's the extent that I kind of know. But I think what's really interesting about games is like if you I think about like the games I've played before, there's so many different versions, right? There is like Match 3 which is like Candy Crush. And that's like free.
SPEAKER_00: Neither are we. Mhm. Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: But like the good part about it being free is you have like you introduce like the cool down mechanism. And that allows you to show ads or other things that people have to watch to then get past those things. And so
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: um but then there's like open world concepts like I don't know, Clash of Clans or something. And you kind of have to it's like a resourcing thing where you have to wait that 6 hours. And if you want to speed it up, here's you watch the ad or or monetize. And so maybe for some of this it's like I would encourage the team to think about like what are the levers that you think players would want more of.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Yep. And I think maybe unfortunately sometimes you're introducing some friction into the game for that to actually monetize.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, totally. Yeah, so I think that's a fine balance. And so we actually have a feedback channel in Slack right now where we put a bunch of product feedback in from from the world. Yeah, so I didn't show you this before. But um oh man, I'm in a new game. And uh let's let's see if I can just skip skip this skip through here.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Totally. That's funny. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I know I'm tanking my score. That's okay. That's okay. Um what I wanted to show you is we have a feedback form on the website. So I actually may maybe curious if you have any ideas on that. If I just hit play here and sign in, oh looks like we might have deployed some changes. I'm getting prompted to sign in again. Engineering hard at work. Thank you Lauren and Matt if they can hear us. Um feedback form. So we have a feedback form here and like oh we have a phone number now apparently. Okay, that's new. That's new. Um I don't know what happens if you call this number. We could try calling it live on air. I'm a little bit nervous. But maybe we'll do that later.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Okay. Of course. Woah. Totally.
SPEAKER_01: I'm sure Matt has something fun planned for that. Um yeah, you can say hello from the stream. Uh and this gets put in it gets moderated first and then get put into our Slack channel. I don't know. Is there anything you could do for anything you think we could do to improve it?
SPEAKER_00: Important. What could be cool is like uh yeah, I guess if you report even a bug or if you uh report anything in feedback, uh you automatically get like some more gold maybe. Could be kind of cool. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Cool. Yeah, what I'm hearing uh uh kind of cool idea you have is like how do you like create some fair store of value that
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, you got to have people care about something and then they can invest and then decide if they want to continue to come back and pay.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah. Cool. Cool. I like that. Okay, let me see if we have a good um well let me check off our launch checklist. We did get authentication working. We did we did launch. That was that was our launch checklist. Um but I want to go to our marketing our growth plans. Let's see where it went. Growth. There's our growth playbook. Okay. So here's what we've come up with so far. Maybe it'd be cool we have a list of I love I love using bots to format Notion docs. It's just so great. So clean. Um
SPEAKER_00: Done. We did launch. Totally. Wow, I mean I'm like wow, I can't believe you just did that.
SPEAKER_01: So okay, let's go through the idea list here. It looks like we have some impact and effort scores. So what I want to do live on stream is ask you to help me stack rank these growth things. So everything we've talked about, let's summarize them into a list of what we think is going to be most leveraged to lowest leveraged. And then we'll go through some agents on them and get them prioritized. So we might disagree with the agent that that the bot that put this together. But yeah, what are your thoughts? So
SPEAKER_00: Okay, that's cool. Okay. Yeah. Okay, cool. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: sharing your wins, sharing your bot card um to for the tier of stuff we talked about, challenging a player, doing a weekly clipper leaderboard screenshot. That's a good one. Avatar showcase, follow through the welcome DMs. I know you're a big fan of the welcome DMs, right?
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. I'm a big fan of welcome DMs. I think we see this a lot even here. It's like speed to lead is so important. You told me you you're following me right now. That means you you're interested. Like I got to somehow get in touch with you as fast as possible uh to be able to uh capture your interest.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Yeah. Okay, what are your what are your other favorites? Maybe you can pick our pick our top three.
SPEAKER_00: Let's see. I kind of like that if we want to ultimately have X sign ups, I think the practice two or three times and having the pop up that feels pretty pretty great.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yep. Find a way to drive more X sign ups. I like that.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. You got to love the high high impact low effort. That's like upper right hand quadrant.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah, you're right. You're right. We should get a graph of that from our bot. I like that. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Uh so
SPEAKER_01: Any others here that catch your eye? Emails from Lauren's fan list, building our mailing list. I kind of like the share ideas, you know. I think it'd be easy to share the leaderboard stats.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, I think the share would be great. Exactly. I think leaderboard you want to be feel rewarded for like
SPEAKER_01: Um Let's find where that one is. Here we go. Uh well
SPEAKER_00: Especially the game is so hard. Cuz the game is so hard, it's very cool to
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, you're right. You're right. It's like a point of pride that you've
SPEAKER_00: That's right.
SPEAKER_01: Okay. So I think we have a good list of three here. Um going to feed this into our engineering engine. But there's a lot of really good ideas here. Anything you think we're missing that we haven't talked about?
SPEAKER_00: Let's see. No, I think definitely the the danger is adding too many things for sure. We are like hitting users every which way with some random thing that they don't want. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yep. Yeah. Yep. Awesome. Awesome. Okay. well we uh are super excited about all of this. I think this is a really great list. Um I guess Vincent, before we kind of wrap up chatting with you, curious sort of, you know, any other final thoughts, any other thoughts on just like growth with these types of products you'd want to share with the people who are watching? Yeah, anything else you'd want to bring up?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Oh I think uh definitely getting PMF for the game first. Like I think that is definitely like I think a lot of people always think about like, oh can I how can we grow it immediately? There's a bit of a chicken and the egg. But I think you should definitely break it down more. It's like what is more marketing versus what is more growth. And I think those two things are definitely more different. Marketing is like definitely more top of funnel awareness, etc. And then once you get people in, then how do you continue to maximize essentially what are the best parts of your your product?
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Yeah. Yeah, I like that. So establishing some baseline metrics, figuring out how you kind of move people through that funnel and kind of going from there. So very cool. Very cool. Okay. Okay.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. That right. Yeah, exactly. Exactly. I'm curious too. I mean you you're a Grokbot power user, right? And so we we've been talking a lot about the game. We can maybe stop sharing my screen for a bit and just just maybe chat a little bit, you know, not not about the game. But like what are some of the ways that you like to use Grokbot? I I I'm sure a lot of those ideas that, you know, that are there you you shared a lot of them with with us. Um but what are what are some of your ways that you use Grokbot when in your job every day?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, ridiculous as it is. Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, totally. Uh I think the unique part about growth sometimes is you're asked to do a lot of things like zero to one by yourself kind of cuz there's like no resourcing and or like you kind of have to prove that it deserves a bit more scope. And so a lot of that means like, you know, you're kind of putting on one hat and being a data scientist looking at the data. Maybe then you're looking into like what does that look like on the screen if somebody were to see it for the first time. And for emailing even it's like what does it look like to the person receiving it. Um and so I actually one of the new things I discovered even last night about how I use bots is uh when I spin up a new bot and yeah, you can name it like data scientist. It doesn't necessarily mean that like the bot knows how to be the best data scientist. And so I actually told my bot yesterday to go take a lot of 101, 201, 301 courses on being the best data scientist.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. But that's really cool. And it just went out and found a bunch of classes and yeah.
SPEAKER_01: It went and found a bunch basically downloaded these little parts that were like personalities that I felt like were very key traits of like a good data scientist. Uh and then was able to keep that as like a persistent like skill essentially within the bot which is so cool. Like I was like
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: I basically also did it to a designer. I was like asking to scope some things. And I was like this looks kind of ugly.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And so I was like go take a ton of courses basically better design
SPEAKER_00: That's a great prompt actually. I never thought of that. It's like go teach yourself how to do X and then maybe be an expert on the thing. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Go teach That's right. Yeah, cuz I think like there's so many things like uh in a previous life I was I was working at a a bigger bank. And you know, you you're told to build all these models. And so there is some like core primitives like building things like spreadsheets or slides that are like just like these small things that you know not to do. but maybe sometimes that hasn't quite translated to your bots. And it's like don't hard code things in cells maybe. So it's like okay, always try to use a formula uh unless it's like an input.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. One of the ways I like to think about these bots is that they often are sort of like interns that we've brought onto your team. And you have to sort of teach your intern or you know, maybe not an intern, maybe like a full-fledged, you know, colleague. But you have to teach that colleague, kind of onboard them to your work, right? Like if we are if you're if we're hiring someone in the SpaceX AI, like we we spend some time kind of teaching them how everything works, what tools do we use, um how do you get things done at the company, right? I think this is true of many companies. And so you know, spending the time to onboard your bot I think is a really important Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly. I say it all the time. Totally. That's right. 100% Yeah. It's really important. I think you just get a lot more value out of it too. And I think it's like it's how you want it to be done. We all talk in a certain way. Like I have one bot that just looks at how I talk in Slack. So like how I talk in Slack with, you know, my teammates in a team group chat maybe is a bit different than like a general announcement. And so like, you know, learning the language and how I think about it.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Right. Yeah. How cool. That's awesome. Any other fun bots that you have that you you want to highlight?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I'll I'll have to shout out like I think uh the one that I really love is the bot doing stand up with all the other bots. To me I'm like that's such a good way to summarize like what's been happening in my day and on the context. Yeah, like I we so we have this like main bot, the Grokbot now. And uh so that Grokbot is like my main Grokbot and kind of just talks to all the other bots. And I'm like, hey, hold stand up at 9:00 a.m. every day. Just get a quick pulse check. What are everybody working on? Um and then I sometimes do like to go into specific bots to like do more one to one chats. And then so I'm like then do a a roundup at the end of the day and re-download and re-get context like which bots are working on what. And so I kind of use a bit of a hybrid like one bot fits all versus like specific bot setup for myself.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, okay. And how do you use that? Yeah. Yeah. Right. Yeah. Love it.
SPEAKER_01: Um and so that's really helpful to get all that context out.
SPEAKER_00: That's awesome. Amazing. Um awesome. Well, I think we are uh going to cut over a little bit. So we have maybe a couple of promos we want to talk about. Is that right?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, I think we have two promos which hopefully is good top of funnel uh for our game and for our stream here. Uh and so one of the uh different one of the offers that we like to have is uh for every single like if you were here earlier, we did a promo for new users. Uh but we want to take care of all of our existing users too. So uh now if you comment reset, that's r e s e t in the chat uh and your existing Grokbot user, uh we'll be able to do a reset of your account uh by the end of today.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. If you pull up my screen, I have this uh for folks who are on the stream. So earlier today you said yeah, we we we gave away some free Grokbot. That was fully for new users. Chat, we heard you. We we know some of you are already using Grokbot. And so
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: do you want to share again? Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, exactly. Yeah. So if you're if you're just coming on the stream right now, basically within the next 15 minutes if you're an existing Grokbot user and you've been hitting your limits, we're we're going to reset them. So make sure to post in chat reset. Uh and then by the end of the day uh in the next 15 minutes and then by the end of the day you will have a Grokbot reset in your account.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Queue queue the uh queue the chat reset spam. I'm sure like you don't have it up right now. But like I imagine the chat is going wild right now with all these reset requests. Um amazing. This is really cool.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I think actually we might have one more I think. Uh and I think we're running it again. So also if you are now a new user, uh new users who sign up in the next 15 minutes, also if you just go to the link uh x.ai/bot, uh new users who sign up in the next 15 minutes, create an account, set a recurring task will also get one free month um of Grokbot.
SPEAKER_00: It's a very different kind of business, right? So yeah, yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, okay. Amazing. We we talked about growth earlier. And I feel like one of the best growth hacks is just give stuff away for free. How how what would you say to that?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I think the thing that it's kind of like that curve where you're kind of like uh you know, growth is like just about winning hearts and minds. And then there's like the oh my god, you need to do all these different things and it's just about winning hearts and minds. I do think growth is also just like how would I want to be treated as a user? And that's most of how I think.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I I wow, I really like that. Sort of how would I want to be treated as a user? I'm using a product. Put yourself in the shoes of someone who's using something else and like figure out what you'd want. I really really love that. So okay, sounds like we have two promos. We have a Grokbot reset. So in the next probably 10 minutes now, 13 minutes now, uh if you post in the chat reset, you'll get a Grokbot reset by the end of the day uh the end of the day tomorrow maybe depending on how long it takes cool end of day. And then if you're new to Grokbot in the next 15 minutes, um you can download Grokbot, create an account, set up a recurring task and get a free month. And these are valid only for the next 15 minutes, limited time offer. Um I'll just show both of these again. So here's that first QR code. I think it's actually the same QR code. Should be the same one. Awesome. Same QR code so you can see both of those. And um Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Should be the same one. Yes. Cool. So uh just to give you guys a sense of what's going to happen next, uh if you're just tuning in, we are in the middle of a three day live stream here where we are building a game studio as our business and building a game. We just launched our first game this morning. Uh Lauren and Matt are uh working away at adding a level sort of fixing our our next set of bugs and continuing some of the engineering work to polish up the game, uh take into account all the feedback that we've gotten so far which has been really incredible. So thanks everyone for coming and and joining sharing all that. Um the game is at w well no, is that thursdayarena.com? No www. Just just thursdayarena.com. And we are at at thursdayarena on Slack. Uh and those are the only sources of official information about this project. So if you're seeing anything anywhere else that is from anywhere else and it's not us, we are just at thursdayarena and thursdayarena.com. Uh please check out the game, give us some feedback in the game. Uh there's a cool leaderboard there where you can kind of see how you do against against your friends or other people. Super excited about this and to make it better throughout the day. Um we are doing all of this live right next to Dreamforce in San Francisco. So we are just like a half block away from the big the big outdoor park. Um we are in a building here where we're doing a bunch of stuff all happening all at once. There's a main stage downstairs where we've been doing a bunch of talks and letting people come in and build and learn how to use Grokbot. We have a studio space upstairs right here where we've been putting together the stream and bringing on a bunch of really great guests to chat with us. Um just to give you a sense of what's going to happen in the next few minutes. So I think Vincent, we're going to let you go and get back to continuing to grow the SpaceX AI business and helping uh Grokbot grow. Um I'll probably stick around for a bit. We'll try to see if we can bring the rest of our build team back on and see how much progress they've made. Uh and then we're going to have a another guest I believe around noonish in the next few minutes. And so we'll maybe take a quick two minute break right now uh to give us a chance to reset the studio. And then we will be right back. So Vincent, thank you again. We're going to go get all these growth ideas implemented. And hopefully we can see some cool pipeline changes.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Okay. Yes, sir. Amazing. I have people DMing me sharing me their wins on X.
SPEAKER_00: Amazing. Oh I love it. Okay. And then you we did have your X handle up on the screen a second ago. So if you just rewind a little bit, you could find find Vincent where to follow on.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, Vincent z h u. So just Vincent z u.
SPEAKER_00: Awesome. Thank you so much Vincent. Good to see you.
SPEAKER_01: All right. Yeah, of course. Thanks for asking.
SPEAKER_00: We'll be right back. Growing in numbers. Growing in speed. I can't fight the future. Can't fight what I see. Cuz people have come together. Yeah, people have fallen apart. And no one can stop us now. Cuz we are all made of stars. Our efforts of lovers are left in my mind. I sing in the reaches. We'll see what we find. Cuz people have come together. And people have fallen apart. Uh no one can stop us now. Cuz we are all made of stars. Yeah, people have come together. And people have fallen apart. No one can stop us now. Cuz we are all made of stars. Slowly we're building. I feel it in me. Growing in numbers. Growing in peace. Cuz people have come together. And people have fallen apart. And no one can stop us now. Cuz we are all made of stars. Yeah, people have come together. And people have fallen apart. Uh no one can stop us now. Cuz we are all made of stars. Yeah, people have come together. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Cuz we are all made of stars. Everybody out there. Everybody out there. Everybody out there. All right, we are back. We are building Thursday Arena. So for those of you who are just tuning in or maybe you tuned in earlier and you forgot for some reason, uh we are building Thursday Arena. This is a three day live stream here at Grokbot Galaxy which is our event right next to Dreamforce live in San Francisco. Uh my name is Roshan. I work on product at SpaceX AI. I'm joined by a guest here we'll introduce very very soon. Uh but wanting to just catch everyone up on what's going on. So uh we are built spending three days here building a business. Our the business we're building is a game studio and we just launched our first game earlier today, thursdayarena.com at Thursday Arena on X. Please give it a try. Uh we have a bunch of UI polish that we're working on. Uh Lauren and Matt who are on the team here are just right around the corner uh working on building and incorporating all the great feedback that's been coming in so far. And our hope and goal here is to make a bunch of improvements over the course of the day. So excited that we'll be able to kind of continue making things better. Uh what we've been doing kind of while the build is going on is bringing on a few guests. So uh in the last half hour we just had Vincent z u join who works on our growth team here at SpaceX AI. Gave us a ton of great ideas for how to grow this business. So we started a business, we have a product. joking earlier that we're going with the classic San Francisco startup vibe where we're going to just go get users and we'll figure out how to monetize it later. But you know, my my my colleagues told me that this is later and we got to figure out how to monetize. Um since we have some users. Yeah, so we're on day three. We're kind of in the stretch home stretch here. Um Right. We have some users. but anyways we're we're super excited to have on another guest. And so yeah, why don't you take a second to introduce yourself, share a little about what about what you work on and
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, awesome.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Uh so I'm Matthew. It's really great to join all of you. And I'm on the marketing ops team here at SpaceX AI. And what that means in practice is I really build tools and automations that help our marketing and sales teams work more effectively. Um and so you can imagine there's a lot that I do with Grokbot both internally in my work, but also in terms of enabling the field to work more effectively with Grokbot and uh to do things in a lot more of an automated and interesting way.
SPEAKER_00: Love it. We love automation here. Uh if you're just joining us, we have been using Grokbot to build this entire business. And a lot of a lot of it is automation heavy. It's we're trying to get as much stuff to be sort of auto building, auto improving as we can and kind of getting that whole engine around I built her built around it all. Um we've thus far been focused on the development and code process for that. So I'm really excited to be able to spend some time chat about how we can use some of those same techniques to grow and build our business.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: So um you know, I wanted to start out with just kind of what are your overall thoughts on how you use Grokbot in your role? Maybe just walk us through a couple of common workflows that you've built. Uh and then I'd love to show you the game that we've built and maybe we can walk through it together, see if you see any opportunities for us to either use some of those techniques or maybe build some of our own.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah, for sure. So there are two main use cases. And for those who have been watching our stream for the past couple of hours, I was able to highlight these on stage. Um the two main use cases are really keeping myself sane. Um and reducing the context switching. Um and so I like so many people have landed on this paradigm of a chief of staff agent. Um and for me I think the real unlock that takes it past like the chief of staff just being who I talk to to try getting anything done is the fact that I gave my chief of staff agent access to all my inboxes. Like like not just a couple, but truly everything.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. How many inboxes do you have?
SPEAKER_02: I I have more than you might think. Um it's like all all my email addresses, uh my calendars, um even like different chat accounts. Um and so really across personal and professional use cases, I have all this information coming at me. And of course there's Slack.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, great. Okay, same one. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: And I think number one in today's day and age is distilling all of that, figuring out okay, what are the tasks, what are just the FYIs of the things that are tasks, how do I get stuck into them?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Um and so what my chief of staff does, which I think is maybe a bit differentiated than the typical use case, is it can handle the whole end to end. I call it a self completing task list.
SPEAKER_00: Okay.
SPEAKER_02: Um and so it's tapped into all my inboxes. It receives what's coming into those inboxes on a regular basis. It determines what subset of that information is tasks. And then it identifies which of my other specialist bots are best positioned to take a first stab at those tasks.
SPEAKER_00: Cool. Okay. So what's an example? So it sounds like oh yeah, maybe just an example from from what you do. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah. So for example um one thing is like territory planning and territory disputes. So um uh I'm on the MarOps team, but it's really sort of a combined RevOps and MarOps team. We work across marketing and sales.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. RevOps and marketing ops for those who aren't familiar with that.
SPEAKER_02: Exactly. Revenue operations, marketing operations. And um you know, when you're growing a massive business, you're hiring all these sales people, they all have different territories that they own. And sometimes like you are a salesperson, you meet someone at an event, they exchange contact info with you. And you're like, great, I can bring this deal on board. Super excited. I'm going to follow up with them. And then all of a sudden you realize wait, I actually don't own that account and my colleague does. And so I met the person, but really they should be the one following up.
SPEAKER_00: Yep. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: That's a territory dispute. Okay. And so you might face instances of this pretty often where you're especially if you have a large sales team, um you're getting tickets saying, hey, I don't know if I should work this or not. And often, at least in the past, it would take a lot of human judgment to point at the rules and the processes and this is the right way to do it. And you should have clicked that button, not this button. But what we can do now is in a much more automated way understand like what's really going on here, how does this align with our rules of engagement, and what's the policy moving forward?
SPEAKER_00: Awesome. So sounds like you know, company with large sales team need a way to manage kind of some of those things, make that more automated, less about having a bunch of people in a room all the time. What are your thoughts on sales ops or marketing ops for a three person company that has a single game on the website?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yes. So I've been thinking about this a lot. And obviously um when it comes
SPEAKER_02: Very very different. Very different. But you know, fundamentally every business is really it's a bit cheesy, but like every business exists to connect with people and like do something valuable or entertaining or memorable.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Mhm.
SPEAKER_02: And I think when you come back to that fundamental principle, it sort of helps guide your decisions. So if you're thinking about a consumer standpoint, you want to get a game out into the world to the people who are going to be most entertained by it.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Yep.
SPEAKER_02: If you're thinking about from like how do we keep this ship running, like we got to pay the bills somehow, we can make people pay for it or we can make it an ads driven um kind of experience.
SPEAKER_00: Yep. Yeah. Well I'm I'm glad I'm glad you segued into the monetization part. That was sort of the thing I wanted to do live with you. If you're down
SPEAKER_00: pull up my screen on the stream. Uh, for those who are joined, joining us earlier, um, I'm going to walk through the games. You might have seen some of this already, um, but Matt has an app. And so, I'm going to show Matt the game. Uh, hopefully there's been some cool updates that are also been built in behind the scenes. Maybe we'll see some quick bug fixes, too. Um, and so I'm going to walk through the game. And what I'd love to do is figure out what opportunities you see in this process for how we could build a business, monetize it. We have some ideas, so you can kind of see some of those ideas, too. Um, the core game is called Thirsty Arena, and it's thirstyarena.com. Please hop in and play if you want to give it a shot.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Mhm. Mhm.
SPEAKER_00: We have a an option to log in with X or just hop in to practice mode. I'll just log in with my account so we can um, you know, try and have this count against my against my winnings. If I go into the game, we have a leaderboard. I can see all the people on the leaderboard. Looks like we now have nine players who have made it onto the platinum list. Platinum tier players. Congrats to those nine. Um, there were some different names up there the last time I looked at this. And so, um, we definitely I'm down to 37 now.
SPEAKER_01: Nice. Oh, wow. Looks good. Oh, boy.
SPEAKER_00: Not not not really doing as well.
SPEAKER_01: Hey, you've been hard at work on other things. Sorry.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, fair fair. I haven't had as much time to play, so and it looks like we have some a nice visual bug here, too. But over 1,000 users who have logged in, which is incredible. Uh, so thank you to everyone who's playing the game and trying it out
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Exactly. Yeah, fair fair. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: giving us feedback. So, that's our leaderboard. Uh, if I go back to the uh, the home page, we obviously have a little bit of like a sponsor form feel here. You could probably put move that around a little bit. But you know, like get a little way to reach out to us if you're interested in sponsoring the the stream or sponsoring the um, the the game. Um, so obviously I think that that could be a really fun avenue with some ads and stuff. Um,
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Mhm. Mhm. Yeah. Mhm.
SPEAKER_00: you can also see the core game loop. So, I hit play. Basically, we're drafting a team of uh, bots here. I can choose the bots I want to buy. And I can go ahead and you know, put them in an order and pair it up with another teammate. The bots do their thing, some cute animations there. And we have NYC parents. That's NYC parent. These are all bots that are taken from our bot marketplace, by the way. Do you have a bot in the marketplace?
SPEAKER_01: Looks nice. Yeah. Oh, I love that. I do have a couple. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Okay okay. What are your bots called?
SPEAKER_01: Um, I have one called Inbot. So, that's the template that I made for like managing my inboxes.
SPEAKER_00: Okay. Okay okay.
SPEAKER_01: Um, let's see if we can get that one in here. Should be should come up.
SPEAKER_00: Inbot. Uh, in Inbot?
SPEAKER_01: In I N B O T. It's not showing up there.
SPEAKER_00: Oh, maybe not. We might have renamed some of the other one. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: We can go with another one. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Uh, what what what's your other one?
SPEAKER_01: Um, I I can't remember right now, but I sort of like some of the ones that I'm seeing. Like what's Cooper?
SPEAKER_00: Cooper? Uh, it's a great question. I don't know.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Okay.
SPEAKER_00: We we we we took out the bot descriptions, but we could definitely go to
SPEAKER_01: Let's go with one of these. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Well, you know what? We could just pull this up live. So, we have x.ai/bot/marketplace. What is Cooper? Cooper, Tommy Hanson has a bot called Cooper that is a news agent for AI, tech, venture capital, and business. It delivers a tight daily slack briefing of top stories at 8:00 a.m. It's kind of cool.
SPEAKER_01: Okay. Sounds pretty good to me. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Weekday midday competitor alerts only when something truly clears the bar. Um, this is really cool. So, if you haven't seen this yet, x.ai/bot/marketplace is our bot marketplace. And so, you can go into this marketplace, you can see bots that have been published by some of the the you know, people we've been joined working with. Some great examples we've seen out there for how people are using Grokbot. These bots have memories, so they kind of come preloaded with a bunch of context and sort of what they should do for their job. They also come preloaded with routines. So, this bot knows that when you install it, it should send you a briefing every morning at 8:00 a.m. You can go in and tune it, of course, and make it your own.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Uh, and it also has some integration. So, bots can connect all the tools and services that you're using. Um, obviously connecting to Slack is a really important one to be able to you know, understand what's going on in the business or understand what's going on uh, in your in your company. So, yeah, that's that's Cooper. Um, yeah, we actually took a lot of these bots and we had them sort of be the first versions of our little bot marketplace here.
SPEAKER_01: It's fantastic. And by the way, just something else that I want to call out about the marketplace is there are certain tools that have marketplaces where you like really need to lean on that thing because the tools themselves are really complicated and it's like not going to learn how to build this complex. Let me just copy it. This is a tool where the marketplace seeds amazing ideas and like you should go to that first, start there. But then you sort of realize, wait, I could create a template this good by like just thinking deeply about what I'm trying to do and what connectors there are. Like it's such a simple tool to build your own bots from scratch if you need to.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Completely agree. And for if you for folks who haven't seen it, so I'm just pulling up my Grokbot here. We've had a bunch of bots running and building this whole business. I got my chief of staff. I got Dr. Eggbot that helps me make new bots. I got my data scientist who I promoted up here because we've been looking at a lot of data. You can just share these. You can share share as a template. The bot will pack itself up and make itself a template, right? Before the call, you actually hop you you shared a template with me, right? And so is that is that this one? Is that Cerebro?
SPEAKER_01: Nice. It's super easy. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. That's Cerebro here.
SPEAKER_00: Cool. Tell us about Cerebro.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. So, you know, to my point earlier about what you're really doing when you're thinking about growth, um, I don't know if you've seen X-Men.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, of course.
SPEAKER_01: Okay. So, right?
SPEAKER_00: Great name. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Have you heard of it? Uh, so Professor X, right? He like sits down in that chair. He puts that helmet on, right? And then you see that big screen in front of him, and he's just sitting there thinking about all the mutants out in the world that he's looking for, trying to track down. And you see them all appear on the screen. Well, when I think about what we're really doing when we're trying to get something out into the world, it's sort of like Cerebro, right? You're sort of sitting down and you're thinking, okay,
SPEAKER_00: Right. Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: what did we build? Who did we really build it for? How can we find them out in the world? And not just by saying like we sell to this industry, companies with this much revenue for like a B2B business, but instead really thinking outside the box about like who are the human beings who we think would be really excited if they knew that this thing existed.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And so what Cerebro does, um, and maybe we can take it for a spin if we have time, um, is it really helps you come up with like who is your ideal customer profile?
SPEAKER_00: Okay okay.
SPEAKER_01: Um, I have sort of an idea for how we can adapt it here. Um, once you determine who that is, you can think, okay, what data do we need to find?
SPEAKER_00: Let's just do it. Sound good?
SPEAKER_01: Let's just let's do it.
SPEAKER_00: So, I'm going to hit refresh. And we just see that we can install the bot. Here's Cerebro installing in my Grokbot. It looks like it comes with a bunch of context. So, Clay MCP specialist, Apple Market MCP specialist. Not sure if we can connect those live, but we can hopefully work with Yeah, I got the concept. And um, yeah, some some cool plugins. So, let me add this bot.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. We got the concept. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Cerebro has joined the team. Okay. Um, I'm going to pin Cerebro so we can make it a little bit easier to see him up here. Uh, and yeah, so I guess the bot installs itself,
SPEAKER_01: Perfect. Yep.
SPEAKER_00: tells it's just sets them up. Go to marketplace bot. We need one of those. We don't have a go to marketplace bot yet. So, I'm going to go ahead and just assign a label to this bot, too, while we're in here. GTM. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly. Here we go. Uh-huh. Perfect.
SPEAKER_00: Um, maybe let's just skip the plugins for now.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: And you said you had some ideas for how we might use Cerebro with our game company. Tell me more.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, exactly. Yeah. Okay. So, you know, you're you're building this game. And again, you probably don't want an experience where people have to pay to play the game. Like maybe there are
SPEAKER_00: No no pay to win. I think we decided we don't want to make it so that you have to you you'd have to pay to get more powerful because those mechanics get a little bit more Yeah yeah yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Right. Yeah, exactly. Then you sort of just right. Um, and so I think the experience that you want is like making it ad supported. But when we think about these ad slots that we want to sell, um,
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: we could go the easy route and be like, hey, whoever will give us money, let's put those ads on the screen. But then you get a really bad experience where people are playing the game and these like random unrelated ads are showing up. And sure you're getting money, but it doesn't really feel good. Doesn't feel cohesive.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: And so what I was thinking about and what we could use
SPEAKER_00: Let me pause you. I'm going to just turn on the voice dictation here and we can just capture what you're saying and feed into the bot. Does that work? Cool. Okay. Go ahead. Keep going.
SPEAKER_01: Absolutely. Absolutely. Yeah. Yeah, perfect. Okay. So, Cerebro, what we would like to work on with you, um, is really finding our ICP in terms of who we should put in these ad slots. Um, so you have a skill. It's called Find my ICP. I think you should be able to run it just by me invoking it here. Um, and what you'll help us do is really brainstorm like who do we want filling up these ad slots. And and some thoughts that come to mind are like if you're sitting and playing this game, maybe you're thinking about what are some other fun games that exist that I could discover. Maybe it's some snacks. You know, I'm sitting and playing and I want something what you know, while I pass the time. Um, and so essentially what Cerebro will help us do is come up with those creative ideas.
SPEAKER_00: Cool. Yeah. Okay. is super personalized. Then Apple Market takes care of sending that email. Um, and then you can even have a Grokbot monitor your email inbox afterwards to see which advertisers took a bite. And I want to know Okay. I feel like this is a good thing for us to try and do off stream. So, maybe when I'm not sharing live, we can try and get a Clay account set up, an Apple Market account set up. It'd be kind of cool to just like get a whole marketing like partnerships motion going here. So, yeah, let's see what we can do. That might be really fun and a fun thing to share back later on if we can if we can manage to get there. So, um, yeah, I think we are kind of winding down this segment. So, if you're just joining us, we are in the middle of day three. I it's already noon. I don't know where the time is going. We are in the middle of day three of a 72-hour build a business live stream that we're building entirely with Grokbot. And so, we've spent the last two days building our game studio and launched our first game this morning, thursdayarena.com or at Thursday Arena on X, thursdayarena.com. If you want to try the game out, we are working on a bunch of UI polish, a bunch of improvements and updates, and all kinds of great stuff there. Um, we just spent some time chatting with Matt about marketing operations, revenue operations, and how to grow the business. We have the other folks on our team, Lauren and Matt, who are hard at work uh, working on the all the feedback we've gotten in from the app, working on all the bug fixes that we've been identifying. We're shipping early and trying to ship as much as we can over the course of the day. And we'd love to get back to that, too. Um, again for those of you who are joining us, we're also doing all of this live in San Francisco. There's a lot going on. We have an upstairs space here with our studio. We're downstairs uh, with a main stage, with folks who are right we're right next to Dreamforce. And so, folks coming in and out and being able to join and hang out with us to learn about Grokbot for various kinds of used cases. And so, you know, Matt, you spoke earlier on our main stage about revenue ops and marketing ops, which is awesome. We're going to go to another talk in just a minute here, I believe, with Blake Schuler on Grokbot for customer success. And so, we're going to continue kind of showing you how you can grow your own businesses with Grokbot. We'll obviously be back on the stream a little bit after that, show you how things are going with Thursday Arena. So, we're going to ping-pong back and forth. We'll cut over to the main stage in the next minute here on Grokbot for Customer Success. And Matt, thanks so much for hanging out with us.
SPEAKER_01: You know, let's meet. And instead you can make reference to specific data which the bot has access to. You can make reference to specific factors about that company that you want on as an advertiser. And so, the email that it can craft for you and load up into an Apple Market sequence
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yep. Okay. So, let's go ahead and send that off. Um, one thing I'm also going to do, and I like to do this when I'm adding a new bot to my team, is I have a chief of staff bot or a Dr. Eggbot who's helping coordinate things. Um, also reach out to chief uh, to get a brief of what we're actually building.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yeah, thanks for having me. Hey everyone. Thank you so much for joining me today uh, for Grokbot for post sales. My name is Blake, and I am an AI deployment manager here at SpaceX AI. And I'm really really looking forward to chatting with you all about Grokbot today. All right. So, let's set the stage. What are we going to be doing for the next 45 minutes? Uh, one, I said hi, welcome, done. Uh, then we're going to talk about Grokbot. We'll introduce it, why Grokbot is great, specific post sales use cases. So, post sales is kind of determined by anything if your customer facing after that sale gets done. Um, it can include a lot of teams. And really excited to talk about those use cases. We'll do a demo, get in the product, learn about what we learned, recap that, do a Q&A. And then for those of folks in here, we are going to build. All right. Okay. So, this is the AI maturity curve. This may look familiar to some of you. We've been talking about this a lot especially at SpaceX AI because AI is moving so quickly. We're finding that a lot of folks are on very different places along this maturity curve. But this is kind of where we're at. So, it started off with just chat. All right, you were asking a chatbot coming in and maybe asking one simple question. Um, and the next evolution is actually really clear to us at SpaceX AI. We're moving from chat to copilots, to bots, to having full teams of bots that can support you and all the work that you do from start to finish. Uh, and that's where I think Grokbot becomes really powerful. So, a lot of you probably have been in Grokbot before. But those of you who haven't, let's talk about a little overview. This is Grokbot. May look familiar. Looks a little bit like iMessage if you're an Apple user. Um, I do feel bad for all the Android users out there cuz we really did copy iMessage here. Um, but this is Grokbot and it works as a team of agents. So, you have a bunch of different bots who have different skills. They can take tasks, work them from complete start to finish here. They have MCPs, APIs, and they actually even have their own virtual computers. So, think of them as like a teammate that can really get anything you want done. And we'll take some use cases and put them through Grokbot to show you exactly what that means. So, like I said, easy as iMessage. You have your bots on the left hand side. You have you can pin people to the top. They're also on 24/7. So, that's one of my favorite things. You can go to sleep, you can go out of the office, you can shut your laptop. I've see feel like we've went through a stage here where people are walking around the office with open computers. Uh, with Grokbot no longer. You don't need to do that anymore. They use the tools just like
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, perfect.
SPEAKER_00: Like the game and stuff. Um, and uh, this is also cool thing. I just I love just like messaging with my bots instead of just colleagues and and just chatting with them on on iMessage or Slack or something like that. And so, uh, yeah, just fired off a couple of messages. This way Cerebro has some context on what it is we're actually doing so it knows what those ad slots are, right? Um, and then you said there was a skill in here that does some of that ICP work.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. 100% Yeah, so if we hit slash, I wonder if it'll show up at if it got packaged up with find Oh, find notion. Yeah, maybe it didn't get packaged up. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Okay. Okay. No worries.
SPEAKER_01: Um, and I think this will be able to
SPEAKER_00: Make that a little bigger for everyone.
SPEAKER_01: give us some good ideas to to start with. Um, we're really we're like starting from first principles of like who do we think we would want to reach out to and say like, hey, we've got an ad slot here. We've got this audience convened of like highly interested, highly engaged people. You can get in front of them with the type of product that they'll be interested in. So, maybe we could take a look. So, other games got indie studios, casual games.
SPEAKER_00: Yep. Games like the Discovery Platforms. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um, Yeah, snack friends, and energy drinks. Okay. This kind of thing makes sense, right?
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: And I think the next thing that we want to ask is essentially like
SPEAKER_00: Oh, I like merch.
SPEAKER_01: Oh, that that that's true. Exactly.
SPEAKER_00: We can make some uh, Thursday Arena merch.
SPEAKER_01: Oh, 100%
SPEAKER_00: That would be cool. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: There are lots of ways. And what I would do is and maybe we can turn the dictation on.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, let's do it.
SPEAKER_01: Perfect. Okay. And we got signal recipes here.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, why don't we take a look at that and then we'll describe. So, it looks like we got Okay, so walk me through what's happening here. So, it looks like
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: there's an ICP, there's personas, segments, scoring points, a lot of stuff going on here. Maybe some of us or some folks watching are not as familiar with all these terms. And so, just like you know, give us the 101 here on on what what just happened.
SPEAKER_01: Yes yes yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And also the the awesome thing is it looks like it had that skill in its memory. So, it was able to invoke it for us. And and this is the kind of output we would expect. Um, so ICP, ideal customer profile.
SPEAKER_00: Great. Awesome awesome. Okay.
SPEAKER_00: You know, so much so many of these terms like RevOps and MarOps are the kind of things like none of us knew what these were when we were kids. Um, and we get into this business world.
SPEAKER_01: Right. Unless you're a very very interesting child.
SPEAKER_00: Right. Maybe, who knows. Um, and then you get into this business world and there are all these concepts you have to learn and fundamentally you can think of your ICP as like who are we trying to reach out in the world? Who's on that screen when we put the Cerebro helmet on?
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Mhm. Mhm.
SPEAKER_00: Um, and so then you think in a bit more detail like, okay, who are the personas that we're selling to? So, like if we had to have different avatars for the different like main categories of people that we want to reach, how would we bucket them? Um, so it looks like yeah, brands, uh, sponsorship.
SPEAKER_01: Right. Partnerships, the platforms. Yeah, we want to probably like there's there's game platforms out there that could drive traffic to us, right? That could be really cool.
SPEAKER_00: Right. Exactly. Exactly.
SPEAKER_01: Yep. Um, streaming apps.
SPEAKER_00: Some more segments.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. So, then um, I would think of So, basically you can think of the segments as like just another grouping of those personas like uh, the priority order that you should go after these sets of people.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Okay. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Um, what do you think about this? I mean just having been involved in building the game past few days, how does this land with you?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, it's interesting. I mean I think we you know, earlier I guess yesterday or so we were thinking through a bunch of different monetization ideas. And so, you know, we knew we didn't want to make this a pay-to-win game. That's just not really fun for most folks. And you know, we we don't like those kinds of games, so we didn't want to build something we wouldn't like.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Uh, but we did know that we need to build a business here. Like we're a brand new game studio. It's a notoriously difficult industry to operate in. And so, um, we it kind of immediately went to ads as an idea where we could sell some screen estates since we have you know, hopefully a bunch more folks signing up and using using the app.
SPEAKER_00: Um, but you know, I think there's a lot more we could go from there. I I hadn't even considered the partnerships angle or sort of how do we drive more traffic and that could be really interesting. Like if we have an ad
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: sort of served and we can drive more traffic. Like that becomes an interesting flywheel maybe that we go and and try to put in place. Obviously the partnerships would take a little more time to tune together, but maybe some of these things are self-served, so we could do like that. Um, we also have options to maybe explore social and paid ads and kind of doing some of that stuff. And so, that would also just be great to drive traffic in. But I'd obviously you know, we need to make sure that we there's something on the other end, right? Where we're not just spending a bunch of money to get users. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly. Mhm. Totally. Totally. Yeah. Exactly exactly. And so that's something that will highlight a bit less in the Cerebro demo, but I just sort of want to talk through. Um, so when you think about growth, there are really like two fronts, two two major buckets that I would put types of growth in. So, there's obviously like consumer-oriented growth PLG, and then there is more SLG like sales-led growth. And I would say in your case the PLG is yeah, how do you like get more people to play the game?
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: The SLG is that's going to be partnerships. It's going to be filling the ad slots. Those kind of conversations are like it's going to be a smaller number of people that you're going after to like sell the ad slot or set up the partnership. Um, but that's going to be a much more concerted effort of like coming up with a really good cold email to send. And maybe in that cold email you'll cite some statistics from that first bucket. You'll say, hey, we built a game that hit you know, X number of users and Y number of days.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Yeah, I like that. Yep. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Um, and so those two worlds sort of interact with each other. Um, and that's where the flywheel comes in. Like the more you can build these one-on-one partnerships with advertisers, with promoters, with partners, the more they can drive traffic. The traffic increases and then you have something better to offer to to future advertisers and partners.
SPEAKER_00: Yes. Cool. I I just in I just took some of that and just kind of fed it into the bot so we can use that bot. So, I really like that idea.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Um, but then it looks like you have this idea in here like signal recipes. Can you talk a little bit more about what those are?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. So, that that's essentially like Okay, so again to come back to this Cerebro metaphor. So, like let's say you have that screen in front of you. You're trying to picture who you're reaching out to. But it's really fuzzy. Like you can sort of see people's silhouettes, but you don't really know, okay, well like what do I know about them? What could I even say in a in an email? You're not just going to send a cold email being like game to advertise on. Click here to
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. We could try that.
SPEAKER_01: I mean you could, but but you know, you could. And sometimes it works especially if your numbers are good. If you can say, hey, we have this many eyeballs, right? Like you know, you want to get your bot in front of this.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah yeah. Yeah. I'm going to check our market Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: But um, another thing you can do is make that picture higher resolution
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: by gathering signals and data on those people that you're going after.
SPEAKER_00: Yep.
SPEAKER_01: So, it's not just any advertiser. It's not just any snack brand. But maybe it's a snack brand that only came into existence recently that is putting out products that are like unhealthy but made healthier.
SPEAKER_01: And they want to really get out into the market
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: and reach an audience that loves junk food but wants something healthier. Right? Like
SPEAKER_00: Yep. So, tapping into like Yeah, so sort of like kind of what I'm hearing there is you know, part of this is finding partners, growing your business, having the stuff you can lead with. But you know, part of it is also it sounds like um, finding the right partner, right? Maybe there's a specific kind of partner that's the right one for your business or a specific kind of advertiser that feels really native on your platform.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, exactly. Yeah, exactly.
SPEAKER_00: Uh, it sounds like that's kind of what you're saying. Yeah yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly exactly. Um, cuz then the incentives are all going to be right. Like they're going to want to answer your email cuz it's not just any email. Um, someone who Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yep. Yep yeah. Yeah, no that makes a lot of sense. While you were talking, you reminding me we have a bot here whose job it is to keep an eye on our numbers. And so, um, yeah, it looks like we have over 3,000 matches within the past few hours. So, um, I don't know how that compares to other ad models or platforms or gaming or games. Uh, but I don't know, it seems like a cool number to be to be at so far. We had a an early traffic spike right when we launched the game uh, to Oop, there we go. Around 600 signups. Uh, but it looks like we're still we're still filtering more people in. So, yeah, it looks like we still have folks signing up. Uh, our bot decided to change the chart the colors on these charts for us, which is which is fun.
SPEAKER_01: Amazing. Yeah. Awesome. Yeah. Nice. Uh-huh.
SPEAKER_00: I'm getting a 15-minute pulse of all the stats. So, um, yeah, let's just let's um, add hourly active users. Uh, let's just add total user count over time to this.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, that's great. If you had to come up with a theory as to who you're reaching so far. I mean obviously we got the live stream going on. Obviously there are probably a lot of fans of Grokbot, of SpaceX AI out there who want to try this out cuz we're building it. But do you have any other like early theories especially around like um, like the name of the game and the concept of the game is so particular. Like do you do you think there are any patterns you might draw as to like who's using this game and why?
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Yeah. Mhm. It's a great question. Um, let me switch back to Cerebro here. You know, I don't think we have a ton of thoughts beyond we knew we needed to build something today and we thought we'd build a game. So, uh, short answer, no. Uh, but I don't know, I feel like there's a really interesting niche of folks who um, really enjoy sort of like the downtime games, right? You have a few minutes in the middle of your day. Um, you want to do something you know, that's that makes you think a little bit. Sort of the I think our niche is sort of the the puzzle gamers or the folks who are playing words with friends and taking a quick turn. Uh, maybe the folks who are you know,
SPEAKER_01: Right. Right. I feel like we should record this. We should like feed this into Cerebro as just like
SPEAKER_00: Let's try it. Okay okay. Um, hey Cerebro, so we're thinking a little bit more about our segments based on what you shared with us earlier. And uh, thinking about this out loud, I think you know, what what's great about Thursday Arena is that it's really quick and easy to play. And so, maybe some of the segments we should think about are customers or users who are more casual gamers, right? They want to hop in, maybe play for a little bit during a 5-minute break or um, you know, spend a little bit of time doing something with their brain uh, you know, in between meetings or something like that at work. Um, but wondering if we can think a little bit more about our segments given all that.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. And I think the the thing to highlight is like especially if you're thinking about advertisers and partners and and maybe we can feed this in as well is uh, you sort of start with like who's in your Yeah. Um, and and essentially we want to give you that context Cerebro because that's who uses our game. And so we want to think about, okay, those people, what other products and services are those people interested in? Right? Like maybe those people are also the people who between meetings want to like read the news and get smart on the news. Um, like that sort of feeds into who we should think about with with partnerships and advertisers.
SPEAKER_00: Cool. Okay. So, looks like Cerebro's going to take this. There's a lot of really good stuff here.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, what do we got? I think you already sort of understood the concept, by the way, of like extrapolating it to
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. I love this. I want to actually go up to this cuz reading this a second ago, and I love how we basically have now sort of some really good stats. What I love about the bot team, Cerebro can like reach out to the other bots and be like, hey, I need to write an email. Like give me the data for the email. And it actually makes it so easy. Um, so like everything's like your team just working for you. Um, don't don't lead with big concurrent. Don't lead with these certain things. Um,
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh-huh.
SPEAKER_00: here's the revised openers, right? Like we shipped it this morning and we have a 1,000 a 1,000 players and 440 matches in the last hour.
SPEAKER_01: That's awesome. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: It's really cool having this little data by the way. We didn't have any of this yesterday. So, um,
SPEAKER_01: That's really cool. And also imagine like the old way of doing things. These are completely different teams. Like the person executing these outbound campaigns or like on the partnerships team might have to be like, hey, can we pull the latest data? And okay, let me talk to the data team. And like there's so much so many steps you have to go through.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: This is just a bunch of bots.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. And they all just kind of work with each other. Yeah. I think the one of the context is on the agent team. I feel like it adds this level of they all they can just hang out and chat with each other. We were talking about standups earlier. I think same same idea. Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Sure the context Yeah, amongst ourselves. Totally. Oh, yeah, totally.
SPEAKER_00: Um, cool. Well, then what we talked a little bit about our segments. Looks like we got some updates here. So, work break casuals, scroll substitutes.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yep. There you go.
SPEAKER_00: I might put myself in this category. It's like forget the Instagram reels. Just like play a quick game of Thursday Arena. Um,
SPEAKER_01: Uh-huh. Same. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: That actually be kind of cool. I could I could see that. Um,
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: all that run in.
SPEAKER_01: And that feeds into messaging, right? Like these are Fundamentally these are stories that we're trying to tell about why our game exists out in the world. And when we can share that story with the right people out there,
SPEAKER_00: Yep. Yep. Totally totally. Yep.
SPEAKER_01: they're like, yeah, I get that. I want to be part of that.
SPEAKER_00: Yep. Yeah. Um, cool. Well, I love this. This is all great. Um, and then it looks like the bot is asking us if we want to kind of lock in a segment. And then we gave it some more context. And here here you go, like some actual personas, right? So, this is awesome cuz I feel like we can kind of
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: what what I always appreciate when it comes to products is thinking about your customer, putting yourself in your user's shoes, kind of thinking about user stories, right? Like when am I going to engage with the the product? When am I going to engage with the app? How am I going to engage with it? Like what am I seeking from it? Like these types of questions sound kind of esoteric and philosophical, but I think they really make sort of like help you understand what who you're building for, right? It sounds like this is this is helping us get that.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly. Exactly. Yeah. That's exactly right. That's exactly right.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Cool. Um, I also love these partner ideas, right? Like news apps or newsletter briefings, morning brew. Maybe we can try to go get a spot on morning brew. Um, retail check once apps. Like uh, you're checking your your stocks for the day. So, oh wait, let me go let me go play this game, right? That could be cool. That could be cool.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right right right. Exactly. Exactly.
SPEAKER_00: Um, yeah, feeling on top of your work. Body resets.
SPEAKER_01: Wow. Yeah, walking Oh my gosh.
SPEAKER_00: This is great. Partnerships One Liner. We sit in the same 5 minutes as in use skim. A snack run and one more casual round. Stadium ads for brands that already own that break. It's a little AI slot.
SPEAKER_01: Wow. Okay, a little bit. Yeah, it's got the M dash in there, but
SPEAKER_00: Yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_01: It it it's always about inspiring ideas. It's like it's giving us something to react to. And then we can put the human touch on it and like you know, um, and so the way that we can take this and really act on it
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: is um, Cerebro has um, a couple plugins loaded up. They're not off. So, I think we're just going to get a sort of like hypothetical run through of how these would work.
SPEAKER_00: Right. Yep.
SPEAKER_01: Um, but those two ones are Clay and Apple Market.
SPEAKER_00: Right.
SPEAKER_01: And so when you think about Clay and what it can do is it takes this conceptual work and um, and what we can and we can even try this. And I I think actually um, this template will be able to just sort of simulate for us.
SPEAKER_00: Okay. Cool. Okay, let's give it a shot. You want to narrate?
SPEAKER_01: Let's give it a shot. Yeah, cool. Um, okay, so now we want to move forward and take what we've landed on in terms of our target personas for players of this game, the brands that we might want as advertisers or partners. And we want to plug it into the Clay MCP. Um, and so specifically what we want the Clay MCP to help us with
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: is to search its database of companies, of people, and to tell us like who out there in the world fits this description that we came up with. And so, maybe specifically if we can start with like a list of 10 companies who we might want to reach out to about advertising or partnering.
SPEAKER_00: I like it. So, it sounds like the Clay MCP is going to do is just give us a bunch of company contacts, business contacts.
SPEAKER_01: Exactly.
SPEAKER_00: Kind of like let us go and do some market research all through one tool. Um, and yeah, there we go. Let's see let's see what it does. If we don't we don't actually have Clay connected here.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Um, but if not, then I I can
SPEAKER_01: It has access to the web, so it might be able to do some research for us a second.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, the agents are pretty agentic, it turns out. So, I might just go out and start doing some searching for us. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. It turns out the agents are agentic.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah yeah yeah. So, um, we'll we'll see how this goes. But yeah, I guess maybe I know we're coming up on time. We got maybe like 6 minutes or so. Um, I wanted to kind of get a couple of thoughts from you before before we lost you. And so, like walk me through what you do next. So, you get this company search. Let's say it's like cooking in the background, coming up with some stuff. What what actually happens next?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. For sure. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Yeah, so what happens next is you basically get this list of companies you'd want to reach out to. Then you can say, okay, great, now give me the people at those companies. And then you can say, now let me reach out to them. And so there's another tool that we have plugged in here called Apple Market. There are many tools like this that are essentially email sequencers.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: And you can set up an email campaign um, where you can email each of these people on that target list.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: And again, what you're saying is not just a generic like we have a game. You're an advertiser.
SPEAKER_00: Yep.
SPEAKER_00: you like I said, they have their own virtual computers. They finish their work. They can send you screenshots, screen recordings, listen to podcasts. Really, the sky is the limit. I feel like sometimes the hardest part is thinking about what you actually want to get done with Grokbot and think big here. So, we'll be doing that a little bit today. All right. So, let's talk about post sales. So, post sales. So, I'll give you a little bit of like context into my role because a lot of these are very personal to me and the things that I've found really successful. So, I said I'm an AI deployment manager and that means after the sale is done and they come onto the SpaceX AI platform, I work with a bunch of customers to make sure that they see ROI, they're successful. So, what does that mean? It means lots of emails, lots of slacks, teams messages, meetings, conversations, and I have a lot of things going on. So, for those of you who are in post sales watching this, that probably sounds familiar to you. Um so, here are my specific use cases. I could have probably made 20 of these slides. So, if you ever want to talk more about these, you let me know. So, first one, this is one of my favorites, morning status board. I wake up the same time every day. I check my Grokbot. I look and I can see exactly what's going on for the day. Any fires happen overnight? Who do I have meetings with? What did I say that I was going to do yesterday that I didn't do? Not that that ever happens. Um what's going on for the day and how can I get set up? So, that's one of my morning status board pieces. Then I have call prep. This is a great one because it's very much just in time in the sense that 15 to 20 minutes before a call, it pings me who's on the call, what their title is, what we talked about last time, a suggestion of maybe something new that launched since we talked previously, and maybe a suggestion for something to bring up to them, and then anything that I need unblocked. So, instead of taking the time to go review your notes, check through, you can actually just get your call prep from Grokbot. Another one is a follow-up desk. This is actually one of my favorites and we're going to walk through it live today. So, what happens is let's say my day is 9 to 5. I would say 75% of that is usually spent in meetings because it's what I find most energizing. I love talking to my customers. I love strategizing, being there personally. Um but a lot of the work in between those gets piled up if you don't have time to actually come back. So, the follow-up desk is a really great option for the second a call ends. My bots get the granola notes transcript. They pull all the context that they need. They draft my reply. They create materials that I may need. So, it basically takes care of all that in between work. Drafts it for me. I'll check it out and then decide if I want to send. So, that's one of my favorite use cases up here. We also have a promise keeper. Um this one's important to me because I want to make sure that I do what I say I'm going to do. So, if I say I'm going to do something, promise keeper is always watching to make sure it lets me know to actually follow through with that. Um that's one of my favorites. On the other side is an ask watch. So, if I've asked someone else to do something and they don't get back to me, back in the day, you know, that gets like sucked into the abyss of emails or slacks and gets lost. Uh but no longer because ask watch has my back. And then finally, account reset. We're actually going to walk through this today. If you're in post sales or work with a good amount of customers, sometimes it feels like there's a lot of things in motion. And so, what we like to do is talk to my bots, say, hey, I need just an update on where this is at. It knows exactly like the kind of response that I am looking for and sends me a full download of everything. It also actually tells me a joke in the beginning cuz usually if I send the account reset, I'm feeling a little stressed and it's always a space joke. So, we'll see what it comes up with today. Um so, these are my six main use cases. Like I said, many more in in the head uh can share those out with those of you live today. Okay. So, let's meet my team. Gus is my best friend. All right. So, Gus is my chief of staff. Gus and I are homies. So, we talk all day long and I actually only I I think this is maybe a little bit unique in the sense that I only talk to Gus. So, a lot of people how they use their bots, they talk to a lot of their specialists and I tried this, but I'm very distractible and I needed one best friend to get me through everything. I didn't want to manage a team of 10. So, Gus manages a team of 10. I manage a team of one to two depending on the day. Um so, Gus is my chief of staff. We'll work through with him a lot today on the demo. Then we have Frankie. I have a lot of follow-ups to do. So, Frankie's my specialist on follow-ups. We have Wally who knows my voice. Specifically, I sent, you know, a ton of emails and slacks and things that I've written in the past. So, it really knows what I'm doing. So, if you're setting up your Grokbot, definitely make sure that you go in and send it things that you've written so you don't have to start from scratch. Um but it also knows different personas. So, it knows who I'm talking to. If I'm creating or if it's drafting an internal slack for me, it's not going to be super formal. It's going to probably be in all lowercase, maybe add an emoji here or there, uh keep it very casual. If it's messaging an exec or emailing an exec, it's going to be short to the point, formal, and it also knows kind of like a little bit of my style. So, we'll work with Wally today too. Then we have Trudy, my source of truth. Uh Trudy's fabulous because specifically at SpaceX AI, we have lots of platforms, lots of documentation, and I want to make sure that if I ask a question, that I get the right answer. And so, I have Gus go to Trudy if we really need specific information. I need sources for it and he'll send it back to me. Then we have Scout. This is another good one. One of my I guess I love them all. I'm saying they're all my favorites, but they're all great. Uh Scout is my internal radar. So, I feel like one of the things that comes up especially at SpaceX AI is we launch a lot of new things, updates come up. There's a lot happening internally. And before I was juggling probably 30 40 slack channels, also email updates for really important things. And so, actually every day Scout updates me. And that's why I said one to two I manage a team of one to two depending on the day cuz Scout usually updates me directly on what's new, what I need to know, link me directly to that slack channel um and just keep me in the loop. And then account, that's not actually its name. You can come up with a fun name def based on the account. But since we're talking about post sales today, we're assuming you probably have a book of accounts or specific accounts. And my best where my favorite way to do it is to have an account specialist for each account. So, the account specialist knows everything that they need to know. They have all the context. And so, you can basically have your own employee who has dialed in on that specific account. And so, I suggest you make one for all of the accounts you have. If you're working at scale and you have 1,500, there's probably a better way to do that. Uh but these for medium to small books definitely suggest. So, this is my dream team takeaway. Gus is my best friend. All right. Should we do a demo?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Woo. All right. So, let's hop into Grokbot right now. So, to avoid let's just anchor I guess on this right now. So, this is what Grokbot looks like. And Grokbot is very simple in the sense that you have your bots on the left hand side. You have pinned bots. So, if I wanted to right click and pin someone, I can pin them to the top if I know I'm talking to them a lot. You also have your marketplace. So, this is where you can grab bots from other people or you can connect to different plugins like Gmail, Google Calendar, Slack, etc. And then each bot has their own computer which we talked about a second ago. So, you'll see over here on the right, it has its own computer to open so you can specifically grab things in Google Chrome. It can open PowerPoints. Um there's even this button on the top that says teach a task. Very cool skill. You can come in and it can watch you, remember what you did, and then repeat that for you. So, those are the VMs. All right. So, you can see the team that I just introduced you to on the left. We have Franny, Wally, Trudy, Frankie, and Scout. Down here, you'll see we have my three account bots. And then we have staff meeting which we'll use in a little bit. So, to get us started, I'm really busy right now. So, I'm going to tell Gus I'm going to say, can you join the internal learnings call for me right now? Send takeaways when it's done. So, I can actually have Gus join my internal learnings call and I wouldn't have it do it for just any call. So, you want to be protective over what it does for this. Um but sometimes there's a lot of new things coming out. And so, what I know is this upcoming meeting is a branding update for my company Flylow in this demo situation. And it's going to come in and start joining the Google Meet. So, you can see it's clicking around. It's muting. It's turning off its camera. I'll let it do its thing and we can come back to it. But it's going to put in my name and then it's going to actually write in the chat, hey everybody, this is Gus Blake's bot. And we are going to I'm going to sit here and send takeaways. All right. So, thank you, Gus. He's joined the chat. He's going to send a few updates when he's done. All right. So, let's move to the next thing. So, I told you and promised you that we would talk about post-call follow-ups. I think again in post sales, this is really important. You want to make sure that uh your bots are working for you while you don't have extra time. And so, these are the perfect opportunities to do that. So, one of my accounts is named Harbor. So, I'm going to write into Gus and I'm going to say, I'm done. Okay. We won't sign in cuz this is going to take too long. But he can join the the call. It's very cool. Um I'm going to say, I am done with the Harbor call. And usually this would happen automatically, but for the demo use case, I decided I would prompt it to move. Um I also it just sent a because the handoff was dismissed and I told Grokbot that I was doing a demo today which is actually this is a cool example. It it sent what an outcome would be after it left a call just in case. So, it went into the call and then shared what decisions were made. There's new branding. Sent me the link to the new branding. Put in any asks and owners and things that it needed to work on. So, cool outcome of that. So, I said I'm done with the Harbor call. It's going to work on the Harbor pack. Here's what you'll notice. They said I like to only talk to Gus, but Gus doesn't have the expertise that everybody else has. So, Gus has messaged Wally. Gus has messaged Frankie and Harbor. So, since it was a Harbor call, we have to do a follow-up and we have to do some writing. He's going to message those three bots. And just like that, I get a pack back um and it gives me everything that I need to do within a click of a button. So, Harbor post call pack is ready, drafts only. I've made it very clear that I only want drafts. I never want it to send anything on its own. So, it drafted something in Gmail. Let's check out Gmail. Great. All right. So, it knew that I needed to talk to Maya. It knew that I needed to talk to Priya. It wrote a full message for me. Hey Maya, exclamation point like that's clearly me. I'm such an exclamation point person. And wrote it all out in my voice with everything that I needed to do. So, what I'll probably do in like realistically, tweak a few things and then we'll talk about how this improves the system after. But I'll tweak a few things, press send, and it's done. Let's see what else it did. All right. It's writing a Oh, it's slacking Alex. So, Alex is the AE on the account. So, we're going to look at a draft in Slack. Let's see. Perfect. Okay. So, it's going to put it into the post sales account updating Alex. Hey Alex, just chatted with Harbor. We're going to meet with the new champions next week working on our ROI PDF. Perfect. So, I'll tweak that. So, one out two out of three done. And then during the call, we they requested an ROI one pager, how to how to manage ROI, how to measure ROI. And it actually went in, worked with Frankie to use the Flylow branding to build a fully beautiful ROI collection document. So, one, it does that very quickly. Two, it takes all your contacts, works with your account specialist, works with all your other bot specialists and builds what you need to kind of get you through the follow-up that probably used to take at least 45 minutes before. All right. So, we're feeling good so far. Um this one, I'm going to go into Franny directly just because we've been in Gus a lot and I will show you how to go into other uh other bots. So, for Franny, I want to see another virtual machine use case. I think that would be fun to look at. So, I'm going to say, make me an ROI form for Northwind. Northwind is one of my accounts. Also, why this is while this is loading, you'll see that you can actually add labels to different accounts um which is really helpful when it comes to just figuring out who they are. Like I have this labeled as as chief of staff. So, if you ever want to add a label, you can do that in its description. So, what it's actually going to do is open up forms and start building a draft of our ROI form. So, you can see it's opened up the form. It's going to start clicking around. The speed of these tasks depends on what the task is. Um but I know at SpaceX AI, it's been a big focus of us to make sure our models are really good at VM work. Um so, I'm very excited to see where that goes. All right. So, we've added in Northwind Logistics, Flylow check-in. Things are looking good. All right. We'll let this work. We'll check back on Franny in a second. Another use case I gave you earlier that I wanted to talk about and demo is where they say the the space joke. Aren't we curious to see what space joke they have for us? So, I'm going to say, where are we at with Harbor? Okay. It knows that when I say where are we at, it could be I'm stressed about Harbor. You know, you can have it. You can say whatever you want. But Gus knows when I say where are we at with Harbor, I need space joke pronto and I need an update on where the account is. So, let's let it do its thing. It's going to reply to me and usually it'll message other agents. Oh, yep. Okay. So, it message some other bots. We have Harbor, Frankie follow-up, and Scout. Wants to make sure it collects the full picture so we know exactly where we are. You can also track and see what's happening with messages here. It updated me. Still waiting on Frankie and Scout. Now it's just waiting on Scout and we'll get a response this way. So, while we're waiting on that, let's check back in on this form. It's probably not done yet. You can see it's starting to enter in different questions. So, it knew it was for Northwind. It knows usually how we like to collect ROI and it's starting to build that out here. Sometimes I like to watch the VM cuz I just think it's really cool and how it can click around. If this is something you do often and you don't want it to guess on the different steps that it does, again the teach a task button is a really good option. Okay. Let's go back to Gus and see where we are at with Harbor. Here's a joke because life's not that serious. How do you organize a space party? You plan ahead. Thanks, Gus. You're the best. Um all right. So, it tells me what's at risk, who the people are, blockers, open promises, slack, what's happening, and what to do next. I don't know about you, but like clearly since I only really talk to one agent, I need very specific things sent to me all in one beautiful pack. And this has been one of my favorite things to use. Um and so, you can easily set this up with your bot, tell it what you want the output to be, and you don't have to do the joke, but it's fun. Um and then it will do that for you. All right. Franny form is still working. But you'll notice something interesting. So, it's actually messaged Frankie, it's messaged Harbor. None of these people have See how this guy has a little green circle on it? It'll be blue kind of like I message when it's ready for me to open. None of these people have pinged me because I don't want to be bothered with my 10-person team. I want to be bothered with who I'm just talking to. Franny will talk to me directly if I talk directly to Franny, but otherwise it's all going to go through Gus. And I find that really cool and convenient and you can just really build it in the way that you want. So, while it's doing this, I'll show you one last demo use case. And then I'll talk about pulling this all together and building it as a system. So, let's use a staff meeting. So, I use staff meetings for when it can pull in different bots to have a conversation about something that requires a lot of different perspectives. This is good for honestly a lot of different types of roles. You can check for bias. So, if you want to say like, you know, I don't want you to always bias towards a specific customer, um it's good to bring all the voices into the room. So, let's run a staff meeting. We can say um start a staff meeting to talk about what I should spend the next and only free hour of my day today. And what you'll see too is Grokbot's really good at multitasking. So, even if it was still working with Frankie and Scout on this follow-up update about Harbor, it would also be able to work with me and work with the staff meeting. So, Grok can uh bot can juggle a lot of pieces at once which is great. So, the staff meeting is a lot. Let's look at the tab for their takes. All right. So, Gus called a staff meeting. Gus said Blake has one free hour left. What are the one to two top priorities we want to focus focus on? And I tell them to always disagree. It's not helpful and especially with AI, you don't want them always just agreeing on everything. So, come in, disagree, fight for my time, and then tell me what makes the most sense. So, it looks like Harbor Oops. Looks like Harbor has said some stuff on SSO first tracks. I actually ran one earlier to show this as well, but you can see that they'll like literally have a conversation with each other. Northwind comes in and says, don't spend the time on us. There was a usage chip, but everything's fine. Soft later only if you have time. Uh Brightline also says don't spend it on us which is great. I bet Harbor has something to focus on. It seems like Harbor has something for SSO. Frankie follow-up says protect the cap. This needs to go out now. And if you have more time, focus on the SSO problems. And Scout agrees. So, they're coming in, they're having a conversation and Gus will usually return back to me once the staff meeting is over and tell me what the final takeaway is and what we want to focus on. Okay. Let's check back on Franny. I bet the form is almost done. Great. Looks like it's done. It was starting to publish. The the form is done. We have what team and role are you on, what are your primary use cases, what does done look like. Great. So, we're collecting that. So, you can see that we have a lot of things moving at once, right? So, you want to design your system to be one that is able you're able to track easily. So, play around with it as you're setting up bots and do what works for you because everyone's really different. So, it's finished. It told me the questions that it wrote, the share link, and the edit link. And asked if it wanted me to send it for me. So, very exciting. And then All right. Staff meeting's in. Go first. So, we need to focus on the SSO. Next, we're going to send Maya the next step email which they actually already drafted in my Gmail. We saw that earlier. And then we can hold and park a few of these other things that we don't need to focus on right now. All right. So, that's the majority of what I wanted to show you inside Grokbot. I hope you're feeling pretty confident. Let's just quickly rewind on how to get to this end state and what I suggest. I think one of the most intimidating things about something so possible like Grokbot is that feeling of a blank page. Usually people do some research and they go in and they're like, what have other people made or what can I do? Um I'm going to tell you what I did. It was actually really really helpful for me. So, I actually took 10 to 15 minutes and I put a voice memo on my phone. You can also click this voice uh to talk on Grokbot directly, but I'm a pacer. So, I have my phone. I'm pacing around. And I spent 10 to 15 minutes talking about what I do for work. Hi. My name is Blake. This is my job. Here's what I like about my job. Here's what I'm struggling with right now. Here are the processes that I think are broken. Here are the things that I feel like we could do better. And so, I went and talked through. It was a very long transcript. I copied and pasted this transcript. I sent it to my first bot. It wasn't even Gus yet. Hard to think back in the day. Um sent it to him, said, hey, I need a system that's going to work for me. Help me build it. So, sent it. Gus I'll call him Gus. Gus came back and said, all right, seems like you love doing things directly talking to customers. Let's make sure we have enough time for you on your calendar to do that. Seems like this process is broken or you're constantly checking slack messages. Let's take that off your plate. So, if you want something specifically built for you, no matter what role you're in, my biggest piece of advice is to start with context. There's so much that lives in your head and it's really really powerful. So, we want to take that out of your head, give it to Grokbot, and Grokbot will do the rest. Another thing about getting set up and started is if you get stuck or if you have questions, Grokbot usually has the answer. If you wanted to really push through things and try to figure it out, say like don't stop until you figure this solution out. Um so, getting started with maybe some of these use cases, a voice memo, I think you're going to be in really good shape. The second piece of advice I have is uh creating this and making it into a system. So, something really cool about Grokbot is it learns what you like, it learns what you don't like. It starts to adapt and change with you. You almost invest in Grokbot like you invest in another uh coworker or a direct report. And uh so, it's going to do that. But I also built systems on top of this setup that will actually take care of that a little bit more. So, on the right, you'll see some of my routines. These are things that run automatically. So, weekly at uh 8:30 I'll get my daily brief or my unfinished promises that I was telling you about earlier, 9:00 a.m. 1:00 p.m. or a Friday dashboard. But one of my favorites is this thing called a self-improvement scan. And the one part of it that I actually really really love is number two. So, one, it creates a full system audit. So, if I'm doing things manually and I'm sending them or it's checking my slack and it's noticing that I'm doing a lot of things that I'm not asking bot for help with, it's going in and saying, hmm seems like we could automate this. I have an opportunity and sends it back to me every single Wednesday. But number two is I feel like the piece that has really helped me the most is the voice learning. So, the less I have to edit my drafts, edit my slacks, edit my emails, the better. And what it does is it goes in and takes the delta of what it drafted versus what I sent, finds the delta of that, sends it back to Wally. Wally updates its rules and so continuously gets better and better and better. And so, one of my other pieces of advice for you is to make sure that you make this a system. All right. So, let's go back for a second, jump out of the demo and do a quick recap on what we learned. We just talked about a few of these. One, start with a voice dump. I feel like also I usually say this and I call this the imagination gap. Grokbot is so capable. All right. The thing probably holding back your Grokbot is you thinking about what is actually possible. So, have it push itself. How can you make this better? What could we do? Think outside of the box. Um you don't need to have all the answers. So, start with that voice dump. Give it the context. You're going to be in great shape. Two, personal suggestion, little bit biased, put a bot in front. All right. Gus has saved my chaotic self um from getting overwhelmed in a bunch of different chats and Gus manages a team. So, you don't have to manage a team of 10. You can manage a team of three managers. Build it how you want. Just tell the agents they'll take care of it for you. And then three is make it that living system. So, you want to make sure Grokbot 90% of that Grokbot's going to do on its own. It's really good at that. But put a little bit of extra in the things that you really find important. Like for me, I need my voice. I love an exclamation point. You know, Grokbot didn't initially love an exclamation point. And so, I've taught it to have a little bit of personality, maybe tell a joke about space. Okay. That was really fun. I hope you learned something. I'd like to take the next 15 minutes to answer a few questions. Um we can do it live in here. I think we can pass around a mic. So, feel free to raise your hand and I'll answer whatever I can.
SPEAKER_02: Mike Mike check one two. Hey, amazing talk, wonderful communicator. Um what was your prompt to get to the risk people promises reply?
SPEAKER_00: The risk people promises reply. Oh, are you talking about this?
SPEAKER_02: Yes.
SPEAKER_00: Okay. So, this was one of my use cases. Here we'll go back cuz it might be easier to see on here. So, this is one of my use cases which is down here called the account reset. Um so, I basically said sometimes I feel underwater with an account. I feel like there are a million things. So, the prompt is one I just taught Gus like where I get stuck and overwhelmed. And then I said here are the things that I need to know and I told him risks, etc. And it built the rest. Um so, you can build your bot. Just tell it what you want it to know or you can say, hey, I'm overwhelmed with X or I want an update on everything that you're doing with X. Get a first prompt and then you can build from there.
SPEAKER_02: Amazing. Thank you.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Any other questions?
SPEAKER_03: Hi. Thank you. I'm curious in your self-improvement script, how often do you make use of building skills once it suggests something maybe for repetitive tasks that you do?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Good question. So, when I first did this, I didn't give it any limits and it would send me like 10 10 new bots to build and new agents and was kind of overcorrecting. Um so, I set a rule that actually it only can send me one suggestion per week because what I think it's like it's can be easy to overindex especially on routines and things that run all the time that you don't really pay attention to. Um so, I have it send me one a week and I take advantage of that one a week. If I don't agree with the one that it sends, I usually push back and get a new one. But I would say I self-improve at least once a week when that sends on Wednesdays. Yeah. Good question.
SPEAKER_04: Um I use Grokbot like a two days and help me a lot. Um I feeling like it's a is no more agent. It's like a AGI. It's because with a computer, it can work um like a learning and that the skill is very faster. I put for design for me. I work like a robotic and affordable computer. But I I uh is solving my problem and does this amazing. I just is scary. Um what is the cost? That's is uh because what you do is like you have it so much
SPEAKER_00: much agents working.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Um, how we can use for don't, don't spend a lot of we can use and and I have another question. We can use inside Grokbot um other software like just running inside a computer.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, good question. All right. So just to answer your second question first cuz that's a little bit of a quicker one. Um, so you want to connect usually via MCP APIs. If you have other things or systems or softwares, you can actually usually set that up in your VM directly. So that's definitely possible. Um, so let's talk about costs. Cost is important. Um, it was built to be very cost efficient. However, you want to use it very strategically. So if there are certain things that cost more money than others, having it go in and run a full um UI experience to build a form more of a more of a costly option than if you go get everything that you want and just put it into Google Forms AI and it built it for you. Um, so using the VM can be a little bit more costly. And then routines can be expensive because people over index on how often they need them. I was saying this earlier. It's really easy to have something checked every 15 minutes all the time cuz you can just ignore it if you don't want it. But those things sitting in the background add up. Um, so if you have three of those that run 15 minutes all the time, that's hundreds of messages coming a day, prompts being sent, things being sent back. Um, so something to pay attention to. I also think like keep your team lean. You don't need 45 bots. And I think that's one of the things too is like keep your team really specialized in what they need. Um, and that really helps as well. Yeah, good question. Hi.
SPEAKER_02: How far away are we to letting Grokbot handle your account directly?
SPEAKER_01: Like Grok like I never talk to my customer Grokbot. Hopefully never. Um, so I think there are human tasks right now. I mean AI moves so quickly. I don't know where we're going to be in two days, let alone two years. But I'll tell you that I think that humans are really, really good at a few specific things and especially with customer facing work. Being human is great. If I was an AI up here, I feel like it would be less fun and I think probably wouldn't talk about space jokes. So I think we're far. I think it's just taking the time to take the work that we don't need a human for and making them more impactful in the time that they're working.
SPEAKER_02: Thank you.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Thank you Blake. Um, talking about balance uh how much of the time that you free up with the bots working for you uh have you put it into the more human reach out to contact and meetings with customers?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. So I haven't calculated exactly how much time, but I'll give you some anecdotal things that I've noticed. So like I said, my calendar is usually full. I like to be on calls and I like to talk to people. Um, so I spend a lot of my time doing that with my customers and I find we we get farther by doing that. So before I was spending probably six hours a day on meetings and then I would need at least three to four hours to do the other time, the other tasks during that time. So now we're talking nine, 10 hour work days. Now I feel I'm doing the same amount of calls and I feel like I can get much closer to not feeling to feeling like I can do even more in an eight hour work day. Um, so it's definitely shaved off hours per day if not more. Um, it's also just freed up time for me to do the things that I love to do, which is powerful in and of itself.
SPEAKER_04: Hey, thank you. That was an amazing talk. Um, is there ever an example where having like layers of bots? Obviously you have like the chief of staff to the everyone else. Do you ever have like ones in between if that makes sense?
SPEAKER_01: That's a really good question. So like an org chart basically like we would have in
SPEAKER_04: Yeah, like the chief of staff to a marketing bot and a sales bot and uh and then they have their own ones etcetera.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I mean I haven't felt the need. So the only reason I would think that you would do that. So right now as humans you have a chief of staff, it can actually only manage what let's say human a good manager can really stop it like max 10. All right? Gus right now has done very well up to 15 and 20. If it starts to feel like it's pushing the limits and I haven't really tested those limits because I don't have more than that, then I think it would make sense to add in another layer. But I actually think that's really interesting. And when you're doing your voice dump and talking to your bot, I think there's an opportunity to also talk about what that setup could look like for you specifically. Um, but right now if it can just talk to everyone directly, that's fine too. Good question.
SPEAKER_05: Um, uh two quick questions. Um, have you ever do you do you think like that your sales um retention and or increased sales because of this in any way? I'm just kind of curious your general feeling. And then also um anything ever go wrong, just really wrong and just want to share?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Uh definitely. In terms of increasing retention and success with my customers, the piece where I've seen it be really successful is it finds opportunities that will make my customer more successful that I didn't have time or didn't catch. So new small micro ships that I know they've been waiting for. I can get an email drafted ready for me, a flag to me that it happened, send it out to them, gives them more trust. It tells them something has updated. Um, and it finds me new opportunities. I feel like that comes up a lot too because I can catch things ahead of time. And so if we see an issue usually before maybe there wasn't a way to flag it. But because I have Harbor for example one of my account agents always watching that account, it brings things to my attention and I can get ahead of it um quicker. But yeah, I mean I've seen a lot of success and I think my customers are feeling very tailored to because I am able to have the time and the energy to really get that tailored experience out to them.
SPEAKER_06: Hi. Thank you so much. So I have a quick question on like when two bots are collaborating or communicating with with each other,
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_06: uh how they verify the outcomes? You know like like they have to verify each other, right? Like what you said, what versus the other bot said. How does that happen?
SPEAKER_01: That's a good question. Are you saying like
SPEAKER_06: Like outcome verification
SPEAKER_01: if Harbor hears from Frankie, is Harbor checking if Frankie's correct?
SPEAKER_06: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: I I don't know how that works, but I think I would be surprised if Harbor goes in and checks Frankie's work and then responds. Um, I think there is a verification loop inside each of the own bots and then the trust goes from there. The thing that Gus does, which is like a layer on top of things is goes in and then pulls all that information against everything else and sees it at as like a broader view for me and has a bit more depth um and context into that and that's pretty helpful.
SPEAKER_07: Hi. Uh great session by the way. Um, so I'm new to Grokbot, but I've used Open Claw and Plot Code and Co-work. If I have my system already set up there with skills and MCPs and other things, is there a migration path to get to Grokbot? And how much of the things are similar between like Grokbot and Open Claw or other tools out there? And then another question going back to the earlier question, the R saved off how much time are you spending now managing those bots and agents and fine tuning them?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, great question. If I forget any of those, you just tell me which ones I forgot. Um, how much I'll start backwards. How much time do I spend managing those bots in the beginning a lot of time? It felt like a new team that I was onboarding and I'm like, no, I asked you to very yellow your bots. Sometimes I get I get I like an exclamation point. Maybe they get like three or four in a bad way. Um, but you know I was like, no, I didn't ask you for that. Um, and spending a lot of time perfecting them. But it's like I said earlier, it's investing now. My system's pretty clean. So I don't spend a lot of time. I know exactly it knows exactly what I'm looking for and I've actually taught it to stay pretty quiet unless very specific things happen or I have very specific routines run that need my attention. And so that's helped a lot. Again like not over indexing in the routines, not over indexing in 30 40 bots um that you don't need will help save that time. Um, in terms of the differences between other tools, I'm not as familiar with the other tools, but I'll tell you what Grokbot does very well. Um, the fact that everyone has its own computer is unique. Um, Open Claw I actually sat next to someone on a plane the other day and he had his Mac Mini underneath his feet and I was like, what is that? And he was like, oh, it's Open Claw running for me. Called him like Professor James. I don't know where that came from, but um we you don't need to carry around a Mac Mini with Grokbot. Uh to it does so it does VM work really well. And I think it really as we looked at that maturity curve before, it really takes it to that staff agent agentic work, staff of bots that really feels like a team. And for me that feels different from what I've seen other places. And then in terms of migration and moving things over um in terms of a technical path of doing that, I'm not quite sure. I'll tell you how I would do it is I'd say I need you to download and give me everything that we've worked on, all the context that you have and give it over to Grokbot to build you a new system. And also come in as a fresh set of eyes. You could even call a staff meeting since I love to do that um and talk about what you what they think that was going well and what they would improve and then they can implement the new system on on our side. Yeah. And I didn't forget one of those, which is actually impressive. I don't know if the mic is on. Sorry.
SPEAKER_00: That's pretty good yeah. I mean we literally just launched it. It was so barebones. Our UI barely worked to be honest. Wow.
SPEAKER_02: Check check one two. On. Great. So as we use the system more and more and we're experimenting adding bots, we're going to eventually have bots brawl potentially, right? Um, and like any other business we're going to call the herd uh periodically as we refine. Guess the question is are we accumulating tech debt anytime we call the herd because there's so much interconnection between the agents and you go and you delete one because it's not working out or you're not using it. However, there's references to it everywhere else. How should we manage that?
SPEAKER_01: Um, that's a really good question. I mean in terms of tech debt, I don't know if a lot of tech debt is piling up because your new systems will be uh optimized as you add more and more people. But I think my best advice was for you to not get to that point by putting the systems in place from when you begin. So Grokbot is fairly new. So probably most of you are just getting in there. It's like set up the system now. It's like when you move to a new house and you like now do the chores beautifully right when you it's like a fresh start. So do that for Grokbot when you come um and set up the routines to avoid all tech. You could even have a tech debt bot that looks in for things for interdependencies or um catalogs things when it seems like you're not utilizing one and can put it into another. Um, so my best advice create the system to prevent that from happening in the first place.
SPEAKER_00: Hi here. Um, you you think we can use like a Grokbot for uh you you say example put the agent inside the VM. I like this idea. Um, does I think can help us for transition uh between another agent and Grokbot? Uh my point you think we can use like a Grokbot like a router for agents because you can put the five six different uh agent from different company inside the VM and that can be like the transition you think is like a router for uh agents?
SPEAKER_01: Are you talking about like adding different AI agents into your VM and having it route around that?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah yeah because example um I have in my CloudCall or Codex or or another agent working for me. But I have a lot of skills. Uh I don't want to create. But my point if you have in the VM, you can have a your all agent working inside the one VM and you use the uh Grokbot like a for router for It's like the same maker cursor because cursor do this for you in he said let what is the best agent for do this task. But you can use these um another agent like you have a because it's so hard for you make a skills and and that I think that we can use just I that's my question.
SPEAKER_01: We are responsive. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, okay. I get it. Uh I have not seen that done. I'll kind of leave it there in the sense like I don't want to talk to something that I haven't seen done. So I don't know if it would be successful. However, I will say that um if you do feel like you've invested a lot of time and energy into the these other tools, it could be an interesting conversation to have with Grokbot on how to bring that into one place and start um minimizing your tool sprawl across the across the company. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. And we I would love for you to show us but like some of the improvements we made for the responsiveness cuz I think we got a lot of feedback about the mobile. It was it didn't really work well on phone. So hopefully if you kind of like zoom in and yeah, resize it should be hopefully.
SPEAKER_02: So over time um with contexts you giving instructions to the bot, right? Um, and over time you forget a bunch of things. So is there a way to go back and audit all of this or I mean all of these are pretty much saved in a markdown or how does that?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. So each bot is actually uh treated as its like own individual. It has its own individual number that you can track everything that it's done and change logs etcetera. Um, but it sounds like you're saying in terms of maybe forgetting things that it's done or going back. Uh the one thing that Grokbot is really good at is you don't really need to manage context because it knows what it needs to remember or forget. And the probably the easiest way to do that is yes, you can go into the back end and see what's happened and change for a little bit of like that traceability. Um, but I would ask Grokbot to do an analysis on what's done, um what's changed, what may have been forgotten so you can do an audit of what's left. Hey.
SPEAKER_08: Hey. Um, you give a a use case of how you use Grokbot. I I do the same thing. I I dictate quite a lot. It's a lot faster than having to type. It's it's great. Um, but I've so had to break it up quite a bit because um LLMs are still hallucinating quite a lot when you give it a massive blurb.
SPEAKER_01: Um.
SPEAKER_08: Um, I've not done it on Grokbot, but I just wonder have you had any experience with and correctness and have you had to adjust how you might have been using this versus other LLMs?
SPEAKER_01: You know what's interesting cuz I feel like I don't see a lot of hallucination. I haven't really thought about it until you just asked that question. So I would say in Grokbot I don't seem to see that happening as much. Um, what I do when I have like very big prompts like that is sometimes ask it to just distill all the information that I need down to this very specific pieces of information and then have it do some deep analysis into it, which helps usually break it down and like help with some of that hallucination. Um, so that would be my best advice and I'm glad you're a fellow dictator. Uh it's really fun um to do it that way and I think it helps bring a lot of context in. I should take like one or two more questions.
SPEAKER_09: Hey check. Um, what what was your personal greatest aha moment?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I have a lot of aha moments. I will say the first thing that I showed you all with it joining an internal meeting was really powerful for me when I did that for the first time. Um, sometimes I feel like our time is so valuable and it's hard to figure out when to spend time and I feel like a lot of times I have to choose between two really important things. So to feel like I could be in multiple places at once is really helpful. Other aha moments are actually along the similar vein, which is like I don't have time Um, obviously our launch hour I think was our most successful. So a lot of traffic at 10:00 a.m. And then we've had some you know changes over time as folks have been tuning in and out of the stream and coming back. But yeah, the bot even gave us a one liner here, which is over a thousand users, 3500 practice sessions, a win rate of 47%. So I think our our tuning is game engine tuning is getting a little better. And here's some cool charts. Wait, can we look at that first chart again?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Uh I'm curious if you think about your product product manager had like uh are we losing players anywhere in this process? Like how do you think about like the funnels?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, you know I'm not too worried about the funnel and for two reasons. One is because um we don't really have a strong reason to drive people to sign in yet. So there's a leaderboard, which I think is hopefully pretty cool. But as we add more features to the game, I'd imagine the funnel becomes more important. So we really want to go for more practice to more signed in. I also want I think I think we need to dig into how the funnel they've just been calculated cuz we have a login with X button like in the practice round. But you only see it like you see it at the top of the screen. There's probably some stuff we should do around is it a real conversion event and things like this. And so
SPEAKER_00: I mean I think yeah, especially but
SPEAKER_01: I'm actually excited when we look at the new UI. That might be a good opportunity for us to find some some funnel improvements. But
SPEAKER_00: Right.
SPEAKER_01: um you know I actually also think this looks like a kind of common drop off like because we have this open practice mode, a lot of people when I look at this data, what I see is that a lot of people are jumping in. They want to try the game. And cool, I don't really need to sign in. I'm still having a good time. I'm still having fun. And so I think we might want to think about you know in our next wave what could we do for the signed in user that really helps them be you know more engaged with the product, things like that. So
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: um and then yeah, maybe this was a this was a cool one too just looking at how sign ups and and practice starts have gone over time. So obviously we had a really big spike when we first launched the game. So thanks to everyone who is in the stream and hanging out with us. Um, I'm hoping we'll get a few more spikes like this as we show you some new features we built. So 1908 is a number to beat. So that's our that's our target. If we get one more one more hour like that, I think we'll have a really good day. Um, we'll have yeah, we we've seen some sort of common usage and we're we're still in this hour right now, the 1300 hours. So this is a partial data, but we're still seeing a you know four to 500 games per hour being played on the platform. And honestly for a completely new game, it's pretty good I think. Yeah, we just launched this.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. And that's our that's our growth graph. So yeah, pretty pretty cool.
SPEAKER_00: Dang. cumulative user chart. I love these charts because it makes it makes the world look awesome. It could be the smallest Y axis in the world. Yeah. I mean I think yeah, especially but And I think it's also interesting because like as a game studio, I think uh well I've never built a game before, but I imagine like games are kind of a hit driven business, right? And it got me thinking a lot about like you know this is just our first game in our in our game studio uh we're using this as a way to practice. You know it's our first game that we built together and we're learning the process of building games and getting feedback and iterating. And I almost wonder for a moment that in a way the real product we're building is the game studio. Right? Cuz we're going to take all those lessons. We're going to take all the Grokbot workflows we have set up.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: And we could we could make more, right? We could make take these learnings and build Thursday Arena two a way better version, right? Or you know try a different game, learn learn from those lessons. But
SPEAKER_01: um Well I think kind of related to that a lot of what we've done with the software engineering loop here should be repurposable, right? So um we have you know we all have our teams of bots that we've set up here. But we have bots here who are helping us with game design. We have bots that are helping us with 3D prototyping and graphic design. We have a whole coding engine here that's helping us play test games. So anytime a new PR comes in, we have a way to play test and after you run through the game with the sort of changes in that PR using preview deployments, which is pretty incredible. And so we truly have like an entire team. And you could imagine that what we've done here just like yeah, you you build any game. You can kind of use all the same all the same bots. So maybe we should come up with like a a game bot toolkit at the end of this and see how that goes. But yeah, so just to continue going through the data a few more cuts here in terms of practice sessions and then people who played a match and then some more some more. I guess this is back to the beginning here for for a whole number. So yeah, overall feeling pretty good. Are you guys have any other thoughts on the how how it's going part before I jump over to the UI?
SPEAKER_00: Uh well I'm no, I think I think this is like a about what I was expecting for our first play test. And I'd love to just continue iterating and you making the game more fun. Um, so speaking of fun, I think we've also did a few UI fixes and improvements that I don't know if you want to show.
SPEAKER_01: I'm just like blown away.
SPEAKER_02: I was even making improvements while you were talking. So like we have this ticker now that shows people that are actually playing. Um, and when you're logged in, it'll show like your profile image uh if you've already visited the site there.
SPEAKER_01: This is amazing. Yeah, I I actually had not seen these until just now.
SPEAKER_00: Me neither.
SPEAKER_01: True real time development. My favorite is I love the new cards. Lauren, you want to tell us about those?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, so I think we were kind of inspired by oh actually the what we were building before kind of looked like cars. So we we kind of doubled down like maybe let's actually make them look like cards. And I have another bot working on making them look even cooler. So as as you can see these bots have like a variety. They're common. So if you're new to gaming like it's very it's a very common concept in video games where you pick up an item or you have a a pet or you know a team member and they have like rarity or grade. So you have like common and uncommon and rare and epic and legendary. Um, so as as the bots get more you know like higher level, we'll we'll start putting some cool visual effects on them like uh you know like a really nice fancy glow, things like that to make them more attractive.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah. We had that in an early prototype with the cars going to shine
SPEAKER_00: We did. We kind of lost them, but we're we're we're we're bringing them back.
SPEAKER_01: Cool. I love it. I love it. Um, okay. Well we should probably walk through a game, right? So we can see all the improvements.
SPEAKER_00: Much better.
SPEAKER_01: You know what, let me just do this properly. I can pull up in a Chrome and where is it here? It's I always forget. Here we go. Here we go.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: We are mobile friendly for real this time.
SPEAKER_01: I like that. It looks like these are all these all cost three and we have 10 gold right here, right? So I think what we can do I actually wish I can't see the abilities of these cards. That might be something we need to fix.
SPEAKER_00: Uh is that a mobile bug actually?
SPEAKER_01: It might be. Let me see if I go back to non-responsiveness. That might just be an overall bug.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, we'll have to fix that one.
SPEAKER_01: We'll have to fix that. Um okay. Well, while we're fixing that, we can just
SPEAKER_00: Oh no. Well, the I think the ability shows up in the white thing right now. It doesn't? Okay, we'll have to fix that. Maybe actually what do you have the new Grokbot voice mode enabled? I wonder if we can just fix it by
SPEAKER_01: I don't think it's enabled yet. Uh
SPEAKER_00: Okay, well, we can try dictation.
SPEAKER_01: Let's try it. I'm going to talk to my engineer bot here. Hey, so it looks like in the latest version of the game, I can't see the abilities of the bots that are in my lineup when I'm in the shop interface. So I can see the bots, I can change the order, I can drag them around, but I don't know what they do. Can you open a PR to fix that? Cool. We'll get an agent on that. Uh in the meantime, I'm going to keep playing here, so I will Well, we'll just go with this lineup for now just to show how it works. I'll switch back to mobile mode. Oh wait, I got to keep this the inspector on. Here we go. And we'll make this big so you all can see it. Here we go. So we'll go ahead and just fight with this lineup lineup that we have now and I actually really love some of these changes. Um these animations are really fun.
SPEAKER_00: Uh yeah, I think we will We should go even more ambitious with the visual effects maybe and maybe even add sound effects. That could be could add another layer of I just more more fun.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Well, and we we did prototype some sound effects last night towards the end of the day. So yeah, I think we should bring those back. Maybe we should add music to the whole thing too. We've been talking about that. So yeah, we'll do a whole audio engineering pass, but there's a notion doc in our notion team space where we have a bunch of a bunch of music we were playing with including some cool pseudo battle music, so we'll we'll see if we can get that that all in. Looks like I won this round and I won I won it overall too, so this is cool. Let me zoom back in. Yeah, so I win. Uh one of the things when you guys were off camera, I was talking with Vincent who works on growth here at SpaceX AI and he had a a bunch of ton idea a ton of great ideas for how we could kind of optimize the growth loop here and make the game more viral, create more shareability. And he had a great idea that we should just let you share your wins and so adding a share button here I think would be really fun. So I going to just go ahead and spin up a feature for that too just while we're here, you know. Uh so let me get a cloud agent going on this. Hey, can you spin up a cloud agent using potato mode to make it so that you can share your wins? So when you finish a game, you get this win screen that shows your bot team and the fact that you won. It'd be awesome if we could um you know make a share button for that that lives somewhere on that page and then has a nice OG image with maybe your specific bot team, maybe just a generic win card that you could use to post your wins on X or something like that. Cool. Okay, so we'll get another agent going for that. We have our bot lineup, bot abilities, uh bug fix agent going, so two two guys working right now. And yeah, once we go home, here we go. We also need to move the sponsor the lobby card. I'm going to work on that too. Hey, one more uh so another cloud agent for this using potato mode. In the home screen, we have a sponsor, the lobby form. Um let's put that behind a button just like we have the send feedback form. So when you click send feedback, you get taken to a feedback page. That's really cool. Uh for the sponsor the lobby, let's put that behind the form as well and make sure that form is working.
SPEAKER_00: Sorry, I I I I I might have zoned out a bit, but should we fix that bug with the what do you call it? The ticker at the bottom covering the buttons as well?
SPEAKER_01: Oh, that's a good one too. Yeah, so that one was right here, right? For the scrolling
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, let me let me for that one let me actually pass a screenshot cuz I think it might make it easier for the bot to understand what's going on.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: Um so I'll play again and then show
SPEAKER_00: Oh right, you know I actually even wonder if you can ask Grokbot to open uh the game in its own browser and turn on the Yeah, the the responsive mode and and fix it for you. Um and this goes back to what I was saying yesterday where you know sometimes when I feel like I'm doing a lot of the work instead the bots, I take a step back and think how can I actually hand over this task to the bot or the agent so that they can help me and make my life easier. So it's a it's a very good reminder you know as you work with Grokbot to just be thinking every now and then like maybe actually even set up a bot that reminds you right you know like uh you can say that every you know every uh every day you know like ask Dr. Eggbot to give you some suggestions like if am I too much in the loop, you know how can I make my workflow more autonomous? Uh and you can go off and suggest those three. Um
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, and I was I'm just prompting here.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I wanted to um so so we can see the game. Uh yeah, so what I'm prompting is basically what we just talked about, but I'm going to do it in a very specific way. I'm like hey, this new ticker covers up some of the shop buttons, spin up a cloud agent using potato mode, inspect and fix that issue, and then one thing I really like to say is before writing any code, do X. So here before writing any code, run the app thursdayarena.com, find the exact bug and behavior and then proceed. And so we will get an agent on that as well. And so um yeah, again if you're if you're if you're not used to writing code with Grokbot, this is definitely a really fun way to do it um having one engineer that sort of your ring leader can spin up a bunch of cloud agents. These are cursor cloud agents, so they you know work in the cloud, they have their own virtual machines, they can reproduce behavior, they have browsers they can walk through. So in our case, we're building a web app. Really great to just be able to walk through the screens of the web app and agents are pretty good at this too, so they can take screenshots, they can find an exact bug. Um and perhaps most importantly, they can verify their work. So if they implement a fix or implement an issue, they have the option to just go in, make sure that the fix of the issue is actually what you know what what they thought it would be. They're not just looking at code tokens, they're looking at kind of how the fix works in prod too. So
SPEAKER_00: All right, so I have a bunch of folks going. I'm curious what are your agents doing? What are your bots doing?
SPEAKER_01: Um I have um I actually have uh a project going on like a project agent that I got Grokbot to create. And I am doing uh a lot of uh UI polish work as well as bug fixes. So um I guess we showed this earlier, but I can kind of refresh your memory, but uh so Matt added this really nice user feedback uh feature in the game. So if you go if you click on Thursday Arena and you go back to the home screen, you can see there's a send feedback button. And if you encounter any bugs or uh you know you want to give us feedback, uh you can you can update that.
SPEAKER_00: There's a 20 character minimum there Russian. We're getting some spam, so you know we had to had to force the minimum.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, but so all of this feedback is going into Slack and we have bots and agents watching that channel and just automatically reproducing the issue uh and you know confirming that there's a bug and uh you know then if if it does find a bug and confirm it, it'll try to do a fix and then automate automatically merge and fix.
SPEAKER_00: Matt, what does this do?
SPEAKER_01: It's interesting. What is this phone number right now?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, it's a phone number. Okay, we're going to do a live demo because uh this is un I think my I do I even have my phone? I do, I do, I do. Okay, so uh I was playing around with some uh some XAI voice agents. So this is actually an XAI feature. Um it allows you to create a voice agent very easily. So if I call this number here that's listed
SPEAKER_01: Maybe we get the camera zoomed in on on Matt for that.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, let's get uh let's Let's get a real good close-up of Matt.
SPEAKER_01: Oh my god. Well, uh I've been using the tool and I just want you to tell the team it looks great and we appreciate you building this on such short notice.
SPEAKER_02: That's awesome to hear. Glad it's hitting the spot.
SPEAKER_01: Uh yeah, I think that's it. So maybe you could send the feedback through.
SPEAKER_02: Thanks for the kind words. Your feedback's been noted and sent straight to the team.
SPEAKER_01: There's your feedback. It's right there. It's in our Slack channel.
SPEAKER_00: Wow, that's it. That's that's awesome.
SPEAKER_01: That's amazing. That was like super real time as well. So yeah, how did you build this? I am so curious. Uh yeah, well, if we cut over to my screen, I could uh I could give you maybe a walkthrough. We could show you. Um so actually using uh XAI. Um so XAI has a You have to have to delete the token on whatever screen I was just on, but XAI has a uh voice workflow builder. Um and so essentially on their voice side, you can build a voice agent and so this is all in a GUI. Um and you can come in basically build these agents uh and deploy them very quickly that answer phone calls uh basically what you just saw. So I didn't actually write any code for what I was um sharing with you all. That just went on the XAI side and then I have it a webhook that basically accepts that and passes it through to our Slack channel. So it's all lost and the same productions and guard rails are on that phone number that we use for some of the moderation. So you won't be able to like you know deal with do any funny business uh through that phone call. But maybe we could cut off my screen for a second. No? Okay.
SPEAKER_00: I'm looking at it, don't worry.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah, don't worry. Uh and and we can keep talking about uh about what what what we're building. Um also that token only half the value is shown, so we shouldn't have to worry about that. And uh I have now uh deleted that. Um so we are good.
SPEAKER_00: Good good to say.
SPEAKER_01: Just for complete safety. I'm actually surprised we made it this far in the Yeah, no secrets in the chat. Chat chat is for games and good vibes only, no secrets. So But um I think that I I keep saying this and I'm kind of like repeating myself a lot, but I I keep going back to this idea of you know Grokbot is such a powerful tool for really bringing together data from everywhere. And as you saw as you saw Matt just demo, you can have you know we can have uh voice support agents through Grok. You can have uh in-app feedback that feeds to a Slack channel. All of those pieces of feedback can just feed in and be aggregated into your bots, into your your team of bots and they can kick off uh you know cloud agent workflows, they can fix things, they can report them. Uh it really empowers even at such a small team to almost operate like a big company, right? Because you have all these uh automations that are just helping you. Um so uh I think I think the future is very very interesting right with with Grokbot. Uh I'm I'm wondering if we'll see a lot more like indie game studios, you know like really small teams, very very nimble just using AI to to punch above their weight.
SPEAKER_00: 100% I think one of the things I've realized is that voice agents are actually really good, specifically Grok and XAI voice agents are really good. And so even on that customer service thing, like would I feel comfortable having people like having a voice agent call people on my behalf? Like probably not. Uh I still think it's nice to have a human touch and I get a little annoyed candidly when I call places and there are voice agents on the other side if I'm trying to like get help immediately. That can be frustrating. So I think you want to think through when it makes sense for your users to to encounter a voice agent, but things for but for things like submitting information or getting tasks done, you can basically give those XAI, Grok, voice agents tools. So like I could have equipped it with a notion tool or a Slack tool or built my own custom tool through a webhook. So say we wanted users to be able to delete their accounts over the phone. Someone calls in, uh we give it a tool delete account. This might be something you don't want users to do. Uh right, but maybe something simpler like update address, update name, etc. Um then the agent can take action on the user's behalf. That saves the human's time or maybe perhaps there's like an escalate issue tool. Right, you could imagine for your restaurant you call in and you have a voice agent and the user says what are your hours? Um the voice agent can deliver the hours and the user says hey, can you help me like place an order? You could have like an escalate tool that then forwards that call to the actual business. And so now we're building in some of these like automation workflows that aren't necessarily uh Grokbot specific, but they are Grok specific. Um and that is kind of part of the suite of tools that we have on the XAI side to allow you to get and get some get some more stuff done. So built-in um all of our feedback flows and we have a a very active uh a very active customer feedback channel at this point. So now we just need to start actioning on that feedback. Um and I think uh I think we're making progress though. So lots of stuff in flight.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I am while you were talking, one of my cloud agents that was working on getting the uh cards to show like the our our lineup to show their abilities looks like it has a good draft PR. Um but it's not like a perfect look yet. Um I kind of want some more detail in the card itself and so I'm actually going to give it some feedback on that. Um where are we going here? Open that up in cursor. Uh what should I call this channel? Um metrics. Oh, we have a metrics channel now. Yeah, I I I I I was just thinking it'd be really cool to have a um So I guess you know like we have a we have a channel now that that feeds in feedback for us. But I think it's also important you know as a game studio to celebrate our wins. So I think it I think it would be nice to have a metrics channel where we can like you know whenever we hit milestones.
SPEAKER_00: Nice.
SPEAKER_01: Uh and I I just created it. Um so maybe we can show my screen really quick just for like a a a minute. Uh we just enabled a Vercel analytics on thursdayarena.com. A very nice graph. Uh we went up from
SPEAKER_00: Zero to one.
SPEAKER_01: Zero to well we I think we have 1,400 people on the page right now. Um so it uh you know again like getting all this data is super super valuable. We can see where people are coming from, we can try to optimize uh you know like our outreach or you know something like that. We can get a sense of like how many people are on mobile, how many people are on desktop. In fact, we have more mobile players than we have desktop. So that's really good input for prioritization. Uh 44% are on iOS as well. So uh yeah, I think that's all I wanted to show. Um but uh it's it's good to have this these numbers because Grokbot has all these connectors. We have a Vercel plugin in Grokbot, so Grokbot can pull this information as well. And help you put together plans, help you put together um you know whatever you want.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Um this is definitely an improvement over what we had.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, and actually as you were uh doing that, I just realized I have my data scientist bot that's been generating all my charts. And so I literally just prompted it like hey, we just turned on Vercel analytics. Please factor those into your regular routines and I already have Vercel connected to my Grokbot setup.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: And so the plugin's already there. Really easy to just be able to say like cool like pull those numbers in and like add it to your data store. And I think that's a really like just on-demand data science. I I can't get enough. It's awesome.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Cool. Over here I have my play tester bot also playing. Um we still need to fix this one. I I guess we haven't fixed it yet the the banner, the ticker still covering the buttons.
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah, I have that. I have a PR for that being worked on.
SPEAKER_01: Okay, cool cool.
SPEAKER_00: It looks like it's actually testing its changes right now.
SPEAKER_01: Yep. It's uh going through a bunch of computer use I can see.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Yeah, I I I think the Vercel integration is so important because uh you know you you need your bots to be able to actually run the code, take screenshots. Uh and it gives you so much more confidence that it actually understands the problem. So very glad that we we built that early on.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I think that was really actually really helpful. Um one of the things that Lauren has set up for our internal products as well within SpaceX AI is sort of these these verified skills. And so the idea here is you teach the bot once how it tests your how it can test your product. And once you do that once, you can have a skill that you continue to update and kind of use that um to you know uh make that make that part of your workflow. So um yeah, verification.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Mhm. Uh and I'm just looking at our leaderboard. We have uh a second diamond player. Dev Arminus, congratulations.
SPEAKER_01: Are you the monk?
SPEAKER_00: Are you the monk? Still still holding strong at number one. Um but I think oh yeah actually you know another feature we should add is it would be really cool to click on the player and watch like if we could see their game history and we can see and we can learn learn from how they play like how how how are these players so so much better than everybody else?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Is our game history working? Cuz I know we had a past games feature.
SPEAKER_00: Um I don't know if that that works. I I I I you may have not
SPEAKER_01: I'm just going to ask an agent to go and test it. Hey, so in our uh home game.
SPEAKER_00: Oh, we do also a little uh I I am recording our past matches.
SPEAKER_01: Oh, that's cool. Okay, so you can see and as you can see who we played.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah, look I Matt I actually played against you and I won. How do you feel about that?
SPEAKER_01: Okay. I think that might be uh incorrect data. I there must have been some sort of error. I think you might have ran an insert on the database when it was enabled.
SPEAKER_00: No, no, this is definitely this is definitely incorrect. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is this is real real data.
SPEAKER_01: I don't I don't remember that so I don't recall that Matt Matt.
SPEAKER_00: This is prod. This is bad. Um yeah, well, we should we should make the leaderboard clickable somehow.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I'll get a I'll get a bot working on it.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, okay, cool cool cool. Sounds good. Um I think I have some updates on lineup bot abilities and shops. That's really cool. Uh let's see here. We make uh user what do you call it? Usernames clickable so we can see there.
SPEAKER_01: Cool. We got a bunch of stuff going on just to do a quick reset. Uh if you're just joining us, we are on day three of building our game studio and launching our first game. We launched around 10:00 a.m. this morning thursdayarena.com at Thursday Arena on X. We're walking through some UI updates we just made. We just went through and uh tested the experience together. And every time we find something we want to fix, we're feeding it to a Grokbot whose job it is to spin up some agents to go and fix it. And I'm really liking how these cards are coming together.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, I have some even cooler uh updates. Yeah, so um again I really like this. I keep I I keep I love the CSS array, so it's a uh I'm not a big Pokémon card fan. Um uh but I have a lot of friends who are. And I haven't defined a site where uh it's by Simon Golner. Uh sorry if I'm mispronouncing your name.
SPEAKER_01: I just followed him.
SPEAKER_00: Oh nice. Uh but yeah, you you've got these like really cool effects uh for these cards. And I thought it would look so good on on Thursday Arena.
SPEAKER_01: But if you scroll down, they get even cooler. There's like these extra special like chevron glowy things going on.
SPEAKER_00: Oh. Yeah, where where are they?
SPEAKER_01: Uh it's like uh
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah, well, these these look this look this look amazing.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, right? Like that kind of thing. I wonder how that'll work on mobile.
SPEAKER_00: Wow, I love the effects. They look so good.
SPEAKER_01: We should definitely get some of these in there.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah. So we're we're going to we're going to you know use that library. Thank you Open Source. Um and kind of bring them in. And um something cool I guess about these cards is that they were all designed by Grok Imagine. So uh we took all of the Grokbots that we have on the bot marketplace. And we randomly assigned verities. Uh we gave them you know fun skills. Uh we also have of course the author name. So maybe it actually another fun thing we could we could think of is how do we get chat to be able to to create their own bots that show up in our game? That could be another driver of some growth for our app.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I think it'd be really cool. I mean one way we could do that is anyone can share a bot from Grokbot today. So if you have a bot that you really like working with, there's a share icon in the top right. And if you click that, you can share a bot template. So yeah, actually why don't we switch to my screen for a second and I can kind of show you how that works. So if you have a favorite bot that you've been working with or just a bot that you want to create and kind of share with with your friends, anyone of these bots you can go over to it and just click this and click share as template. Um I'll do it with uh we'll actually do this with our game designer uh and click share as template. And actually it's really fun. This just does it in the chat. So uh you prompt the bot to create a template and these bots know how to templatize themselves. And under the hood, a couple of cool things happen here is like we uh Grokbot strips out all the sensitive information that might be associated with this particular bot. So you don't have to worry about any of that getting sort of like shared outside of your workspace. Um but the core ideas, right? The core memories the bot has built, the core ideas. Um we're on a team account here, and so you could actually make it sharable only as a team, but I'll go ahead and make this public. And so at the end of this process, you actually get a sharable link. Uh and for those of you who are watching earlier, we showed you how you could install one of those bots. I installed Cerebro for Matt on our uh go-to-market team. Uh sorry, not not this Matt, another Matt.
SPEAKER_00: Not Matt, other Matt.
SPEAKER_01: Uh but yeah, you can share you can share these templates. And um we could probably make it really easy to just import one of your own bots into the game. Maybe you could build your own team of bots and go and do cool things with them.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. That's a good feature. Cool. All right,
SPEAKER_01: So uh oh actually while you're talking, do you want to bring up the leaderboard again?
SPEAKER_00: Oh sure, just something changed.
SPEAKER_01: Uh as we were talking, our bots just uh shipped the PR to revamp the leaderboard.
SPEAKER_00: Oh man.
SPEAKER_01: So so a little bit more user friendly now. You can find yourself in the leaderboard. Uh we have a special like much nicer looking
SPEAKER_00: Whoa, this is totally new.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, so uh Ari the Monkey still number one.
SPEAKER_00: I like how it just tells me that I am falling further and further every time I log in.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I'm like rank 247 now. That's a very
SPEAKER_00: Oh man. Okay, but as long as I'm beating Potato, I'm happy.
SPEAKER_01: Oh my gosh, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: I have to be like last on the I'm This is great. I actually really like this. And so we have their yeah the the 1 2 3 the podium at the top.
SPEAKER_01: Yep, really awesome, really awesome.
SPEAKER_00: And we have we have pagination now.
SPEAKER_01: Yes.
SPEAKER_00: Um
SPEAKER_01: which is nice. Okay, just to orient us, I'm getting a note from production over here. It looks like we are going to have another segment at 2:00 p.m. Pacific in just about 4 minutes. And so we'll try and get to a good stopping point here. Maybe what we can summarize for the group is what is everyone going to be working on for the next few minutes. We'll kind of come back on you know maybe at 2:15 2:30 and show what we what we've made since then. Um I have a few agents working on some UI polish. Oh there's our there's our bot template by the way that we just published. That's awesome. Um UI polish. I have some agents working on fixing those bugs that we talked about. I see a bunch of other PRs landing landing here though.
SPEAKER_00: You know what I would really love is if we could um so yeah, we we have bugs and UI polish that that are going on. But I'd love for chat to be able to submit bots as well. So maybe we can do that and and hopefully like maybe kick that off now like add a really small feature. Um maybe like like let's just keep it extremely simple just like an input box, right? Like share a link to your bot that you've created. And maybe for now we can just dump it into Slack and then we can look through and pick a few to actually turn into real bot templates or sorry bots in our game. Um and then we'll make them and hopefully you'll be able to play with your own bot in Thursday Arena. Uh and then I think we have some other stuff cooking. Matt,
SPEAKER_01: What are we cooking up?
SPEAKER_00: Uh I got a bunch of stuff landing, so I'm making some improvements to the uh home screen. Um if you want to uh cut to my screen. Um so a few things. First making some improvements to the home screen. I've been kind of chilling in cursor for a little while. Um simultaneously just trying to link to our X account. And then in this uh sort of agent here, I was working on a nice little um seems like the cloud agent might be uh might need to restart the dev server, but I'm working on having just a link to the live stream so it shows on the homepage. That should be in imminently. And then also setting up our agent environment, our cloud agent environment. So I want to make it as easy as possible to spin up cloud agents that have the environment preconfigured. And the way that we do that is by giving it access to the same like similar you know preview uh API keys and and uh credentials so that our agent can pull in our dev environment basically and start it the same way a human would. So it goes back to what Lauren's been talking about a lot which is kind of like feedback loops and things of that nature. Um and then also I started off this exploratory uh base UI um migration because I'm starting to get tired of like all these like buttons and stuff all over the place. So uh yeah, I need to like start thinking through this a little bit. Uh kicked off basically a planning agent. Um and I mean this is a really great way at least for me to to kind of like work through a technology that I don't use all the time. It's like elicitation of like oh hey, we need UI improvements. You ask me what you need from from my input and we're going to work through this together and we're going to get get that implemented. It also just kind of helps to know what um you know base UI or you know Radix or some of these other things are uh which are just like essentially systems for building um component libraries and you know design uh and implementing standardized user interfaces. So yeah, a lot of stuff cooking. I feel like once you get the basics, you can just start kicking off cloud agents to handle many of these things now.
SPEAKER_01: And actually speaking of cloud agents, my agent that was working on fixing the shop interface where you can see the full card now is is good. I got a good PR, so I'm going to go ahead and merge that. So we have one bug that we just fixed live on the stream.
SPEAKER_00: Nice. Brilliant.
SPEAKER_01: Cool. Um with that, I think we're going to transition to a quick video to warm up for our next guest. So whenever we're ready, let's go ahead and cut over to that and we will be back with a bunch more updates really really soon.
SPEAKER_00: We're going to build a company. We got 72 hours. We haven't done anything. I mean we just spent the last 20 minutes yapping. We shouldn't be yapping. So the goal is to have an idea in day one. Maybe it's a good time to talk about like exactly like what we need when we say like we're going to build this.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I don't know I could kind of go back to the build something people want mentality, right? Maybe something we use ourselves. That's where we're going to build with a human touch.
SPEAKER_00: With a human touch, most importantly that's something we're going to try to build this week. Uh and then you know what what I think what might be fun to do is just kind of look through all the great feedback we've gotten on
SPEAKER_00: so far. And there's a bunch of motion the past few days. So, uh, what we're working on is a restaurant pop-up. So, we're going to do a pop-up in person San Francisco.
SPEAKER_01: We're building a company. Not everything is working perfectly. We are we are building it as we go.
SPEAKER_00: I love it. You seem quite the three things. Just the merch, the ticketing, like the social piece, and then just finding a venue.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, you know what? Let's what every startup has always pitched to every VC ever. Guys, we're going to start small. The addressable market is everybody. We're going continuously live from 8:30 to like 6:00 6:30. Tune in here anytime.
SPEAKER_00: Really?
SPEAKER_01: I don't get the rules yet, but I want to pop up.
SPEAKER_00: We we need to improve it. It's it's kind of yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Love it. Love it. Well, hey, hey, welcome back everyone. Welcome back. Hopefully you enjoyed that recap of the past two days. We have are joined by a new guest. We'll introduce Dan very shortly here, but just find it helpful for folks who are just tuning in to to kind of share where we are. So, we are on day three of building a game used or really building a business with Grok Bot. We kicked off two days ago. We uh started off by exploring a bunch of ideas. The goal was to ship something by Thursday. We have done that. We launched our game this morning. We are building a game studio. That's our business. We launched our first game. Uh it is thursdayarena.com or at Thursday Arena on X if you want to stay up to date on what's going on. We just made a bunch of UI improvements that I think are pretty exciting. And we've had a bunch of really great guests who've been joining us throughout the day, actually throughout the week, to chat with us about, you know, how we can turn this business and make it make it a really real business. So, really excited for Dan Hill to be joining us from the Stripe team. Dan, uh welcome. You want to introduce yourself? Say a little bit about what you work on.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, great to be here. Um it's been fascinating watching the live stream the last few days. Like I was seeing the game just as I was on the way over here and I'm like I just need to you know I want to play this game. Um but yeah, I'm Dan. I work at Stripe uh on Link. Um so if you go into Grok Bot today, one of the connectors you'll see is is Link. Um we also have a bunch of Stripe stuff. Um but the Link one basically lets your agent buy stuff on the internet. So, um you know in this game example actually I've I've personally built a few games with Grok Bot over the over the last couple of weeks. Um often I need to buy like texture packs and like like I need like just like oh I need to set a trees that can go like you know in my game or whatever I need to do. Um so yeah, Link basically creates one-time use cards that the agent can go off on the internet and buy stuff. Um there's a really nice UI in in um in in the in the Grok Bot where basically you approve the spend. So, it's okay I need $10 to buy this uh you know this this tree pack for my game. And you say great approved and then the agent can go off and safely go buy stuff. Um
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I I'm trying to log into my Link account behind the scenes here so we can try to do some try to do a live purchase on stream maybe. I feel like that could be really cool. Um but I guess where I wanted to start. So, you have sounds like you have a sense of the game and kind of what we're trying to do. Obviously Stripe works on payments. This is sort of like the the lifeblood of the business in some ways I'm guessing. Um can you can you talk a little bit about sort of what you're seeing with AI agents and payments? Like clearly a bunch of cool stuff at least from what I'm seeing on X and things like this and obviously some stuff we've worked on together. But we would just love to get your take on like what's new with agents and payments?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean this is not new to anyone right here, but like the explosion of just like AI capabilities in the last I don't know like it feels like two weeks, but like call it a month has been has been incredible. Obviously you know and and Grok's been a huge part of that. Like um and for some reason it's just like at the end of so many of our sort of things we're building or doing end up with and I need some money to go buy that thing or to complete that task. I need some some money. So, um we've been seeing a huge range of of of of use cases um on on Grok and others with payments. Um there's a whole category of stuff which is like you probably see on X a whole bunch of like I have a parking ticket. I I literally cannot be bothered to go through this like you know I just don't want to go through this whole you know flow that's janky and hard. I'm just going to have you know Grok go pay that for me. Um a lot of people are doing like you know restaurant reservations, flight booking. Um I have Grok hooked up to my inbox. Um you know I always getting like oh I need to pay this bill or I need to like do this thing for my kid's school and Grok can just be like yeah I can go do that for you. I can I can make that that that go away.
SPEAKER_01: If you want to cut to my screen for a second I'll pull up the parking ticket example cuz I just love I love that one. I thought it was awesome. Uh you know not not just as someone who works on Grok Bot, but it's like such a cool use case for as a human. I just want help doing the stuff that I don't have to do every day, you know? Yeah yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah. It's just like yeah. Exactly. I mean there's like this this is huge sort of you know one set of people using I think these AI tools like Grok Bot are just like people with busy lives, stuff to get done and they just want to get like to your point. They just like here's a whole bunch of tasks. Can I just fire off you know a couple of agents to go do that? I mean the other is like I guess kind of to to the game you you're you're building here. It's like um sort of entrepreneurs, uh solopreneurs. I myself literally have like 17 half-baked projects at home where I should build a game and I go off and I 3GS boot up the thing and I like spend an evening just like building a game and that's super fun. And the next day I have an idea for like some new thing I want to go make. Um and yeah a ton of those end up with like payments. You know you want to provision a cell account or you want to provision a you know um you know you need some email service that you want to pay for, some AWS bill you want to pay for. So, uh yes, you tell people they're needing payments to go kind of like spin up the things they need on their stack.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, we did it all manually. So, I sat down for like an hour and logged into like 10 different services, put in our credit card numbers, and we got the whole like infra setup. And it was that was really fun.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Well, at Stripe we have a thing called Stripe Projects. Basically um which is in in integrated into Grok. Um and basically Stripe's just partnered with a ton of these infra providers. I think it's got a projects.dev. Yep. Um if you scroll down there you'll see these are kind of all the the companies that are just like natively integrated. And so basically you connect the Stripe account once and then you can just provision those
SPEAKER_01: Oh, that's going to be a really big help for us.
SPEAKER_02: Exactly. You're like hey Grok I need like you know I need a database, I need a email sending thing, I need a hosting provider, maybe I need a domain name. Great. Uh you can see it there. It'll just
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I think that would have been so good because I think it you mean uh on like day one I think our audience also saw us like we were we were kind of like all over the place trying to you know get all these services. Yeah, we were really struggling. So, this this is like a really a really good product.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. We were struggling. Yeah. We kind of have this like um uh not like running joke, but like so many of us like you guys and the team at Stripe are like we're always like hacking on something, building something on the weekends. And it's like you have the idea and then you've got your agent spun up. And then to your point you hit that point of like oh and now I need to go do like manual tasks and it like kind of kills it. But yeah, with projects
SPEAKER_01: Right. And have the yeah it's like when the agent gets blocked on you is when the fun kind of goes out of the experience and we want you to be in self-driving mode. And so yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. So, on the project side yeah we can use that. You can spin up all those providers just right there from Grok Bot and um yeah get going.
SPEAKER_01: That's awesome. That's awesome. Um so it sounds like a lot of cool stuff going on with Link, a lot of cool ways to buy things. Maybe we'll see if I can get that working. We could try to try to buy something together. Um where what I'd love to spend a few minutes on though. So, you know obviously you know you you know payments incredibly well. You're also a product person, right? You think a lot about product, but you're not not afraid of codes. Like kind of the perfect person we need for this phase of the business. Um you know we said when we started off this work that we'd be building a business in three days. We've launched our first product. We're operating in classic uh San Francisco startup fashion which is like let's go get users and we'll figure out how to monetize it. So, I don't want to do that might be a fun exercise together is maybe just work through how you'd suggest we monetize the product. Um so we don't really have a strong plan here. We've thought about some ads, we've thought about some merch sales and things like this. But we'd love to kind of just go through the game in case you hadn't seen it yet. Walk through walk through how it works and then maybe just like riff a little bit on air.
SPEAKER_02: Exactly. Yeah. People do really fun stuff really creative stuff with it too. Like um you know if I spend more than X dollars on eating out this month, I want you to like tell me so that I can like try and you know keep to my budget or like you know um there's some really fun sort of if this then that stuff. Um I've done some stuff where like I if I don't work out like enough times in the week, I'd make I have Link just go like make a donation to a charity on my behalf. And that which is I don't know if I which one I prefer like not working out or just just finding a charity. But like so like there's some really fun stuff you can kind of hook up with.
SPEAKER_01: Mm-hmm. That's great. Yeah yeah. Just like give yourself a moral gray area. Is there a most unusual use case that you've seen someone use uh you know Link for?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Okay. So, this is Thursday Arena. Um there's a practice mode, there's a play mode. You can see we have these cute little cards. All these cards are actually different Grok Bots from our Grok Bot marketplace. Uh so yeah if you just go to x.ai/bot/marketplace you can see all those bots. We imported them. They are now characters in the game. So, thanks for all the folks who are in the marketplace.
SPEAKER_02: This brings me back to my Magic the Gathering days from 20 years ago from yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Yes, that was that was how we were draw we drew some inspiration from uh Magic and and Yu-Gi-O cards and all those. And so essentially the way this works is you you buy and draft a lineup. Oh and I love that animation, whoever worked on that. Uh and you order this lineup with all their abilities and you hit fight and you're paired up with a teammate or I guess an opponent in this case. Things happen, abilities get played and um that's the game. So, it looks like I won the first round. There's a there's a phase in between rounds here where I'm spending some of this gold that I've earned um which we should rename to tokens. We keep meaning to do that. I'm spending some of my tokens. Yeah yeah yeah. Uh and basically continue this game until until we win. And that's that's the game. So, yeah I'm curious. You know you've thought a lot about like great products, you've thought a lot about payments. Um yeah what what comes to mind for you here when you think about some of the yeah?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, so to to monetize like I guess um couple of paths kind of seem seem obvious first, right? Like one path is definitely ads. Um totally works. Um generally you need a lot of eyeballs um to get that to work. But like really does really great at supporting a free you know free product if you want just you know people to play the game ads can work great. Um I feel like with these kind of games um uh and there's a couple of games that are similar my my kids really like playing. Um Avatar World is one of them. but um have you thought about like like allowing people to pay for like upgrades or like yeah you know better cards, better better characters that they can sort of unlock if they pay.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, that's awesome. I feel like there's a really fun product to be built here maybe of like like surprise me with a purchase every week and like hey you got a 100 bucks like get your agents to buy you gifts. Maybe there's some really cool stuff there that we should consider.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. We thought about that. We we keep going back and forth on it. I think we decided we did not want to let you pay for power cuz those types of games just sort of like sort of pray on your ability to pay and sort of pay to win. Um so definitely an option, right? Like I guess if we really needed to make a bunch of money you were like wanted to create that system I think we could. Um but we kind of think of trying to think of ways like I just lost this one. Trying to think of ways where um we could kind of try to find revenue streams, maybe partnership streams or something like that that would let us uh keep the keep the game sort of
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Well, one one of my coworkers actually we just talking earlier. He's um uh put all of his family's birthdays in. And just like hey I have like you know my siblings, my parents, whatever two weeks before their birthdays I want you to just like suggest some gifts for me and then just go buy them. And it's just like up comes a few options, you know just giving them some preferences like great Link. Go buy it.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Oh, that's such a great idea. Yeah. Yeah, and I feel like it's just so interesting when you think about just be like so much of what we do is we we buy is on the internet. Like let's say I want to send a card or send a package and just being able to have a really easy way to do that I think is really is really great. And you know just working on the Grok Bot team we've also heard a ton of great feedback on how uh you know how nice it is just to be able to buy things from the bot. Like this bot is managing your life, it's managing your finances, it's managing you know your your tasks, your emails, and just like connecting that payments piece to it I think is really awesome. So, um
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah. same.
SPEAKER_01: I mean other ideas like this might be a bit of a crazy one, but like um you know you could kind of go with like sponsored characters. Like you know so like
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Ooh, I like that.
SPEAKER_01: you've got your Grok characters here, but like there's actually you know uh I mean this is you know for a startup maybe a little harder. But like you got your Pokémon tie in, you've got some like you know bring in some I don't know Disney characters and just like you know like could you get brands excited about like oh if this game has got a ton of traction then like you know custom cards kind of like um
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. That's a great idea. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: you know snaps done with like custom filters that you can like you know brands can create for the for the game too maybe. I really like that. I'm actually we have a bot here that's recording a bunch of go-to-market monetization ideas. So, I'm going to just feed that into the bot while you're talking so we can capture all that. Um something like actually I'll just dictate it. Um
SPEAKER_01: Mm-hmm. I really like that. That's really really fun. We had um uh a few days earlier a creator on the on the stream who basically has built all of these really cool Grok Bot physical in-person use cases and has built a daily newsletter where she wakes up or she doesn't really do this, but she has a printer in a room. Every morning she gets a physical newspaper. Uh just really incredible just like taking agents, making them do something for you in the real world which is which is super cool. So, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, let's just dictate it.
SPEAKER_01: Uh so we just had a great idea from Dan Hill here. Could we try or log this idea that we could have sponsored cards? So, rather than making the game pay to win which we don't want to do, we could maybe go find partners to help us sponsor cards and uh pay to be like featured on a particular card without changing the behavior of the card. I really like that.
SPEAKER_00: Another interesting idea is is like um I feel like bot tablets are really powerful because um so actually our game's database is powered by Planet Scale. And uh one of our friends at Planet Scale sent me a Planet Scale bot that helped me with all of the database administration. And it got me thinking a lot about like you know it's it it would be really interesting if if companies and brands have uh not just plugins that you install into tools like Grok Bot or or to Cursor uh but you actually release a bot that almost encapsulates the you know like all the skills that you need to you know spin up. For example like a imagine we had a Stripe Link Bot, right? That's like that helps you you know you know uh integrate uh you know set set your cards up, uh things like that. So, it got me thinking like maybe it would be interesting to have like those kind of
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah, I love it. I love it. Helping them surprise. Yeah, please do. Yeah, we'd love to see it. Um and actually you know I forgot we didn't get a chance to ask you this yet, but I think in our as our last question um what are your Grok Bot team look like? Like what are you offloading to bots? What are you using a bot for? Obviously you're buying stuff.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: company built bots as well as part of the featured featured bot.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah having them kind of like pay for that. That could be interesting.
SPEAKER_00: Maybe something like that. That could be interesting.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah yeah yeah. Okay. Well, we have
SPEAKER_00: But I I I like what you say. Yeah, it would be we we don't want to have pay to win.
SPEAKER_01: Right. Yeah yeah. And def- definitely a space for those games, just not our favorite. So, we're like hey it's our game. We are not going to make it pay to win.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: Curious Dan, what what else what else is is running around your head right now as you kind of think through what you're seeing?
SPEAKER_02: Well, just as an aside before you get to that part, the voice dictation stuff is like
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_02: it it's it's just it's just so good. Like if you you know if I if I was writing code like two years ago I would type code. A year ago I would type prompts. And now I'm just like yeah I I I you know I just get my phone out and I just start talking to to to Grok whatever it's like. It's insane.
SPEAKER_00: My favorite. Yeah, you can do the stream of consciousness. Right.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, and if you if you haven't seen it we actually uh added more to this Grok Bot.
SPEAKER_03: Hey, what's on deck for today?
SPEAKER_01: Can talk now.
SPEAKER_03: Main item for today is finalizing a proposal for Parker.
SPEAKER_00: Great. Can you start drafting a proposal and send me a notion link? Oh and I need some coffee.
SPEAKER_01: I don't know if folks can hear this.
SPEAKER_03: On it. Want your usual oat milk cappuccino?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, that sounds great.
SPEAKER_01: Okay, we don't have to listen to the whole thing. We literally just announced this an hour ago. And so I think actually uh voice as a way to interact with agents is going to be so cool. We're going to hopefully be able to show this a little bit later in the stream. It is rolling out over the next few days. So, if you're using Grok Bot um a really cool way to maybe even interact in a completely new way too. So, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. It's a really cool feature. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's a really fun way to like you know if you're uh maybe not driving but you know like you're uh walking walking to work, you know you're like on the subway or something and it's a bit awkward to get your phone out and start prompting, you can actually just chat with it like like a like a friend.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. I did uh a couple of days ago I was um I was uh I was out. I was I was walking somewhere between places and it's my anniversary weekend coming up.
SPEAKER_01: I think that's a great idea.
SPEAKER_02: And so I got off my Grok in my on my phone, pop an anniversary bot.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_02: I was dictating hey this is my anniversary, these are the things we like, these are the places we're trying to go. Just like okay just can you build an itinerary and go like figure all that out for me and just like just dictating just like in five minutes a task that I would
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: otherwise had been putting off for ages. Like it was it was great.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. I I love that too cuz I feel like there's a dictating code and weird we've been doing this sort of all all week, right? Like hey can you build a feature or hey here's what I'm thinking. Um I love dictating the knowledge work stuff. It's like I need you to coordinate these things, send this email, also do that, like get me the coffee. Um my wife's birthday is this weekend and so I've been doing that the exact same thing of like hey here's like the 10 things in my head. I'm not quite sure what which exact combination of them I want, but um let's try and make something of it. And I find the agents are just so good at I mean they're good at text, right? They're their language models and so you can just feed it a bunch of text. Um and one trick that Lauren's been uh sort of showing us uh throughout the stream as well is asking the agent to restate the plan in its own words which is so cool cuz then it kind of cut you make sure that it understands you. It's almost like this intern or colleague that you're teaching uh and making sure like did you get that before you really go live. So,
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah uh this this tip was really kind of inspired by that that the fact that you know like uh models are getting so capable that that they're almost like these magical input boxes that you you just type something in there and it it just does it. It just it's it's pretty incredible.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: But it got me thinking a lot about like you know uh the bottle the I got I guess the bottleneck is you being able to get your idea across well. And so I love the stream of consciousness thing because sometimes you just have this very abstract picture of what you want and you don't know what exactly it is. So, just like just yap for five minutes and then tell it to restate in its own words and then you get a sense of did it actually understand.
SPEAKER_01: Means yeah. Totally. Um so if you game if you guys considered um any kind of like straightforward you know premium model like play end games for free
SPEAKER_00: Ooh, yeah. Mm.
SPEAKER_01: then you have to pay you know $2 a month subscription to keep playing or like gating certain features behind cuz right now it's just like one team versus another team, right?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, totally. I actually would
SPEAKER_01: Could there be a world where it's like oh and if you pay X you can have like multiple five team games or like run your own league maybe? Like could you do something like that or like oh if you want to be like like a organized with your friends you can like set up a league that you
SPEAKER_00: Oh, that'd be great. Oh yeah. I like that. Sort of like taking calling back to the old like in-person trading card game days and and having a league. I really like the subscription idea cuz I think that's really durable revenue for a business and especially we're a brand new game studio. Like durability would be awesome, right? So, we can fund our next game, right? Um and obviously I don't know if we charge for the game itself.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, exactly. Yeah yeah yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's a really interesting yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Uh that that that would be a really interesting business model where I wonder actually what if we had a
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: like I guess I don't I don't we don't actually have a company name for a game studio. We should maybe maybe just call Thursday. Maybe just maybe maybe our company's just Thursday.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Maybe we should incorporate it. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: And maybe we could have a Thursday subscription where you can play all our games, right? For a monthly fee. So, you get more of you know the value of the subscription goes up over time as we make more games.
SPEAKER_01: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah yeah. And that if you have a subscriber base, they're going to be the great early adopters of new games you want to put in cuz they're they're already sort of put they're already paying, they're already invested. So, like oh you have a new game come out, they'll be the first ones to get in there, give feedback, play, you know um kind of make the game better.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Mm-hmm. Exactly. I love that. Yeah. And and for those who are watching uh me just click around idly while we talk, you can see the UI is literally changing by the minute. This home screen now looks totally different than it did when Dan first got on the set. So, uh the the the factory is going. This is the coding factory that Lauren has established that's like continuously making PRs.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Factory's going on. Yeah. You can see I'm not I'm not typing right now. It's just it's just doing everything.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Well, I this is my favorite bot too. I have this bot Bake who's our engineer and we're at 235 plus PRs already since we built this idea in earnest yesterday. We'll have more. We'll have more. But it you just it's it's like having an event stream of all the coaching that are happening. Um
SPEAKER_01: Wow. We'll have more. We'll have more. And you can see all my my slot PRs getting
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Hopefully not most of the slot. Um Dan, I wanted to go back to the subscription idea. Obviously like this is the thing just and so maybe just uh to chat about like what trends are you seeing? Cuz I think one of the things that we've kind of a lot of the folks who are tuning to chat and are are have been coming in and questions on is you know like the the world looks different, business models might be changing. Obviously this open router thing is kind of interesting. Just curious what you're seeing obviously I'm sure Link is playing a big part of that in terms of the consumer side of things. But yeah, how would you describe like Stripe's view on the world as
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: AI businesses and AI powered businesses start to exist more?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. I mean let me answer that both on the consumer side and the business side. Um obviously at at Stripe we have you know huge conviction in in in you know AI and genetic and where that world is going and the capabilities unlocking you know both for us as like employees and engineers and product people who are building each day. You know like we're all in these tools all day building. Um but also in the you know the users and the consumers we partner with. So, on the consumer side um uh a really interesting uh sort of thing we've been observing the last few months. If you look at like consumer spending on AI subscriptions, you know spending on like Grok Bot or on you know um OpenAI or on um you know Muse whatever, um it's been increasing steadily over the last few years. Start of this year the number of people paying more than $100 a month for AI products has grown like 5X. Like I think there was just like so much consumer demand for this kind of thing where like people can just like they can build things, they can create things. They don't have to be super like deep in engine you know engineering and and sort of knowing how to how to how to do that. So, like I think on the consumer side there's this huge growth of like people who were just like really interested in in creating these kind of games and and and building. Um you know on the business side um of course you know explosion of of both startups and of course um the big labs and and like you guys doing doing really great stuff. Um obviously you know we uh uh Stripe you know started uh collaborating with Metronome Really? Okay. whole bunch recently. So, like uh a lot more AI companies are thinking and looking at like usage based billing um as as a model. Um I think it'll be really interesting to see if that plays into a consumer world too. Um you know personally I have my subscriptions and I always have a little thing where I can buy extra credits if I like need it to finish the task. So, I think um you know we'll see a lot more um on UBB. Um you know one of the things that Stripe's doing a lot on right now is like um helping um AI companies think about risk and fraud. You know so like as as you're you know growing you know massive user bases you know a lot of stuff we're trying to do is like how do we help make sure that um the people who are you know subscribing to your products are are are good and how do we how do we lower that fraud and things too?
SPEAKER_01: Awesome. Awesome. Yeah, these are all these are all great. And I guess um one thing that maybe we can try and do if we get some time this afternoon is build a quick Stripe integration and maybe figure out how we try out some of these monetization ideas.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah, I'm pretty sure with your with the existing Grok connector on Stripe you should if you connect it up you should be able to get going on a
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah. I have one.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, we do. Okay. So, yeah I haven't added it yet, but yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yep. So, you can you see here you've got like um Stripe best practices, that'll get your integration going. We've got Stripe directories, that'll help you find businesses to buy from, Stripe Projects. So, that's what will help you provision all these services. Exactly. Yeah. So, um uh yeah you should be able to connect the Stripe connector here and like it
SPEAKER_01: Cool. We can start drafting it right now. Just go ahead and add it in case we decide we want to do this. Yeah yeah. But we definitely need to make money at some point.
SPEAKER_02: Yes. Yeah. Exactly. And then yeah yeah. Point point of point one of your Grok Bots at um getting a subscription set up and it should it should get it done.
SPEAKER_01: I think that's a good stretch goal for the afternoon. We get our first dollar for the business. That would be amazing.
SPEAKER_02: The first dollar. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: That would be really cool. That'd be really cool.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. That'd be a real game studio.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, that'd be exactly a revenue creating game studio.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah yeah exactly.
SPEAKER_01: I don't know if we'll get a whole business incorporated by then, but we'll see. We'll see what we can do.
SPEAKER_00: Exactly.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah yeah. Okay, awesome. Well, it sounds like we have a bunch of really good ideas. I guess Dan I'm curious um maybe as we wind down here about five or 10 minutes left. Um you you talked a little bit about what Link is doing for making it easy to buy things with agents. Um and I've seen a bunch of buzz on the internet about Link lately. And obviously you can you can do that with Grok Bot. So, if we can hide my screen for a second, I want to see if I can get Link working uh without giving away my credit card numbers or personal information. Uh if we could just go to the the wide angle camera shot please then you get a second uh for the production team. Uh but in the meantime while we do that, I'm curious like what's next for Link? How are you guys thinking about the future? Cuz I know Stripe's probably is on the frontier of a lot of this stuff. Like where do you see this whole thing going?
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. So, um we got a we got a bunch of stuff coming on Link. Um so the stuff we're doing right now is is really around um helping agents buy things that they need, whether that's personal stuff, whether it's to build a business, um go buy things. So, a lot of stuff we've been working on there is like how do you help agents understand how to use checkout forms, how do you help them buy especially from Stripe merchants without any friction so they can just you know buy what they need. Um we'll be expanding into more geographies soon. So, it started off US only, but we have uh other countries coming. Um the next one that I'm really excited about and and folks are actually using with Grok Bot um is what we call financial insights. So, this is allowing um Grok to basically import your you know credit card data, your bank data, and do all kinds of personal finance stuff. Or if you're building a business, right? Like why not connect your business accounts in and then have it be able to kind of you know oh I see your credit card limits coming up, you know here's how we can optimize your business for you. So, um we have a lot coming around um sort of personal financial insights and connecting your bank accounts and credit cards um uh with Link.
SPEAKER_01: Cool.
SPEAKER_00: As a as a personal finance sort of like have my spreadsheets and try all the apps person. I think this will help them pretty cool about that. So, yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Um I use it all the time. It's just like so great to have like I one of my Grok agents is just a personal finance thing and it's just like you know you always forget to pay that bill or you forget that there's that you know tax thing going to happen or something. It's like
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, one of the agents be because there's just data the agents can set up routines, maybe they remind you on a certain schedule. So, Grok Bot could just give you a routine and say like hey once a week give me my balance, that kind of stuff. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Ooh, I like that. That's a good question.
SPEAKER_01: Uh well we we saw the we we we heard about the uh parking ticket one.
SPEAKER_00: Yep.
SPEAKER_02: Yep.
SPEAKER_01: Uh I'm wondering if there are like I guess other more
SPEAKER_02: I mean I've been um I I've been I've been sort of amazed at like how quickly people will have have embraced putting like pretty pretty meaningful purchases through like Grok Bot and others like flight bookings, you know things that like if you'd asked me you know a few months ago I'd have been like yeah people are going to be pretty hesitant but with that. But like just seeing how great the tools are, like the approval steps inside like Grok Bot and things, just like how well the agent can use browsers and just like get the right answer. People have like I've been amazed people are just like happily booking you know flights, travel, um like really important things with with Grok.
SPEAKER_01: I think so. Yeah. Actually now that they were talking about I I feel like I saw this on X uh that someone used Link to actually pre-order a Tesla.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Did you see that one? That was such a cool use case.
SPEAKER_01: Oh wow. Yeah, that's cool. Yeah, that's really cool. Oh man. Um yeah well I guess there's a ton of cool stuff we could buy. I just tried this backstage. Uh I think I I realized that um I think my passkey might not be set up on this computer yet or like not in the profile that I've set up. But if we want to quickly show my screen, um I think it's pretty cool. Like I just um pulled up if we could raise if we could link donate a dollar to Stripe Planet. We can just try this again. Um actually cancel that. Buy some shoes from Nike.
SPEAKER_02: In fact there's a small fun fact these shoes I'm wearing
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_02: I bought with Grok Bot.
SPEAKER_01: No way.
SPEAKER_00: No no way because our
SPEAKER_02: Uh teach on our production team. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah teach teach you want to make a quick cameo?
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah. That shoe was also bought by Grok Bot.
SPEAKER_01: That shoe was also bought by Grok Bot.
SPEAKER_02: Love it.
SPEAKER_00: I uh I just took a picture of my shoe and said Grok Bot find me a new pair of these in size 12 please. Thank you.
SPEAKER_01: That's that's yeah. If we had the setup for that oh that would be so cool. But yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yep. I did almost that. I was like I just want to like have stuff buy things. I need some new shoes. I was like just whatever popular men's shoes are size 12 go buy them. You pick. I don't care. The box arrived like three days later at my house. And I was like I don't even think I even know what these shoes are, but like I've loved them. So, yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah. One um one really fun use case I just I just remembered there's a company uh it's called Postal Form.
SPEAKER_01: Okay.
SPEAKER_02: And um it's basically a way that agents can send physical mail.
SPEAKER_01: Cool. Okay.
SPEAKER_02: Um and so I've had you know uh bots in the past like they will make like a dad joke for my daughter. They'll like write out a joke, turn it to a PDF, like pay the dollar in postage. And like my kids just get random mail each day which is like a letter from me, you know? So, like there's some really fun stuff you can do.
SPEAKER_02: Oh that's yeah. In in my house I have a sort of 32-inch uh you know e-ink display on the wall um that I've previously just had to like write some custom codes to like have it display some each day. And I'm now at when I get home from from this I'm going to have like my bots just basically like whatever they want to put on my wall they can just put up there, you know? Like reminders, jokes, news of the day, something. Yeah, it's going to be it's going to be great. I'll put it on X when I do it.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yep.
SPEAKER_01: Makes sense for the the Link person to be buying stuff. But aside from aside from buying things.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah yeah. Um I have a couple of categories. So, I have a bunch of personal stuff. So, I have a shopper bot that does like literally I'm just like I need shoes, I need t-shirts, just like go do that. I I hate shopping so it does that for me. I I have the finance one so I have it just like kind of keeping an eye on my finances, am I spending right, um where I want to spend there. I have this special one for the anniversary weekend um that I'm just like having it try and figure out the anniversary for me.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Um I then just kind of spin them up as I'm thinking of like personal projects. Like I I love just like like like you guys are just building stuff. So, like um I've got one that's building um a game in 3GS, just like the kind of like how do you make an infinite scrollable world that you can kind of move around in.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. Cool.
SPEAKER_02: Um I had this idea actually last night that I I have one working on which is like um I want a mobile app where it's like a it's an AI agent, but it only does find date night spots.
SPEAKER_01: Oh, fun.
SPEAKER_04: So, basically I wanted to be able to go off on the internet, find all the like recommendations of like cool restaurants and stuff I don't know about. And just like every day just give me a feed of like this week
SPEAKER_00: And if you need someone to publish that three JS game that you just described, we might have a game studio.
SPEAKER_01: I might know a game studio. Yeah, there's a visual model. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Great.
SPEAKER_00: Uh All right. Well, that was Dan and his Twitter, or sorry, X handle is up on the screen. So Dan Hill Tech, it looks like if you want to follow him. Um and we are going to now cut to our main stage, back to our main stage here right next to Dream Force where Josh Kim is going to walk us through Grock Bot for marketing. So we'll cut over to Josh, uh learn about Grock Bot for marketing and then we'll come back on for more build time. Thanks so much. All right. Hello, hello. Everyone, my name is Josh Kim and I am so thankful for all of you for joining us here. And I'm excited to share how we on the SpaceX AI team use Grock Bot for marketing. Here's our run of show for today. Uh I'll be sharing what Grock Bot is, how we use it internally uh to market and grow the products. And most importantly, how you all can start using Grock Bot within your teams. Let's jump in. So let's start with the context. Um the way we all started using AI was pretty simple. Uh many of you may still be using AI today, just like this. Uh and I was certainly was in this camp uh before I started on the SpaceX AI team. The typical pattern is that you have one or two AI chatbots that you really use and leverage as your thought partner. Meaning you chat with them, you ask questions, you spar on strategy, maybe you edit copy. Um but they're really there as your thought partner and not a doing partner. As AI has started advancing, there's been this rise of generalized and specialized agents that can start to do tasks with you. Um we refer to these internally as co-pilots because while they can get those tasks done with you, they still typically require you to babysit them, push them along, particularly for those complex tasks, rather than truly being able to delegate your work. And that's the reason why we're so excited about Grock Bot. With Grock Bot, marketing teams can now actually start to automate away true pieces of their work. You can think of Grock Bot as always on asynchronous AI teammates that actually do and finish the work on your behalf. And most importantly, they'll do it the way that you do it. And today, I'm excited to demo how on the SpaceX AI marketing team, we not only use bots to automate jobs and tasks, but we actually use them to staff up functions and create teams of bots to actually do the work for you. But first, let's do a quick intro of the products. For those of you who haven't tried it out yet, this is Grock Bot. And now some of you may be wondering, how is Grock Bot different from all the other AI tools and chatbots that I might use today? What's different about Grock Bot is that rather than working with one agent or one chat with multi-threaded conversations, you create individual bots for each job. And what that means is that you think of one bot to be a singular teammate that you then delegate away a single task or a set of related tasks. What this also means is that you can actually message your bots and talk to them just like you would Slack or message someone on Teams. Uh and to take it a step further, bots can start to talk to each other and actually collaborate with each other within group chats as well. And as you continue to work with your bots, they'll learn how you work, they'll learn your preferences, they'll learn your memory, and they'll get smarter and smarter and get closer to the way that you actually do the job yourself. So similar to someone on your team or someone that you collaborate with, the more feedback you give and the more you invest in your bots, uh the more they'll be able to do for you in the long term. And what makes Bot especially unique is that while it can hook up to all the MCPs and APIs that you're currently using today, it also has its own computer. And that's a bit of a novel paradigm shift from how you might be using other AI tools today. And what it simply means is that because it has access to its own browser, its own computer, so long as you give it access to its to tools that you use, it can actually use those tools just like you would. So what does this all mean for marketers? If we talk about how it can use tools just like you, that means that your bot, you can teach it specific ways that you like to optimize your bidding strategy in ad platforms or the nuances and how you put together a campaign brief or maybe just how you like to manage your computer. But ultimately, what's really unique and valuable about Bot is that it becomes customized and flexible to the way that you work. And with Bot, you'll also find that you're no longer having to babysit and push along and really, you know, remind the bot to keep working. And rather, Grock Bot is extremely ambitious and it's also very proactive. And so now you'll be working with a team of bots that actually want and will finish the work for you. Um and that's quite different from other tools you might be using. Because Bot is hosted in the cloud, that also means that they're running 24/7, no more keeping your laptop open or needing a Mac Mini setup. And for marketers, that means if you have reporting or metrics that you're you're looking at on a regular basis, you can trust that Grock Bot will be able to pull those down for you. And the best of all, as you might have noticed, it's really simple to use. This UI is as familiar and intuitive as I message, which really lowers the barrier to entry for any marketer, no matter what their special specialization is, to weave agents into their daily workflows. Okay. So let's actually dive into what we're going to do today during the demo. Uh what we're going to do together is actually launch a marketing campaign from scratch, from end to end. Um meaning we're going to start from the first task that we typically take on, which is market research analysis. We're going to go all the way through to ideating and bedding on positioning, uh updating a landing page, starting to build and monitor ad campaigns, draw that analysis, and then actually end with automation. Now this is a lot of work. Uh there's a lot of things that happen behind the scenes for all of us in the room. As As marketers, you know that this slide might look simple, but actually it actually spans across many different teams, functions, disciplines within a typical marketing work. Meaning the person who conducts market research is, you know, having to work with a product marketer to identify and vet the positioning, who then has to pass off a task to the web team and so on and so forth. And for anyone who's done marketing before, that context management, the coordination, the orchestration of a campaign like this, that's truly where the craft of the work happens because it's the crux of our job. So today, I'm going to introduce you to my marketing team of bots. And I would be remiss to say that I built all these. I was cross-sourcing these across the entire SpaceX AI team, uh which is a feature I'll talk about. But I'm excited to show you how you can orchestrate an entire campaign build across the entire flow. So you can say hi to our market researcher, our product marketer, our website ops, performance marketer, marketing analyst, and lastly, our project manager. So with that, let's dive into our demo. Now for the sake of our demo, we have uh launched a brand new product. And it is called X Air. So this is an airline product that we built as something that we can use to build a net new campaign for. And you'll see that this landing page is set up. It's our home page. People can do some airline route searches, look for fares, and then we have some positioning and value proposition value propositions currently in place. So I'm going to navigate to my Grock Bot instance and just to walk through what you see on the screen. On the left side, sidebar, that's where the bots live. I pinned them to the top, similar to what you might do in I Message. And I'll be flipping through each bot and I'll explain what I am doing as I'm going through it. But let's get started with the market research bot. So what I'll say first is, hey market researcher, what I'd like you to do is study the X Air website, get a deeper understanding of what the product is, what market we're operating in. And now I want you to go do a competitive analysis on identify and deeply understand our competitors, look at their marketing websites, understand their positioning, and then importantly, identify the gaps and opportunities that we have to actually strategically um competitively position against them within our marketing strategy. So just dictate a prompt. I'm going to set this off. Now the market researcher bot is actually going to go and scrape the website, it's going to understand the product, and then it's actually going to go find the competitor competitors, their landing pages, and start performing this analysis. So while that's running, let me just do a quick walk through of the additional bots that we have. Um we have a product marketer bot, website ops, performance marketer, marketing analyst, and a project manager. And importantly, what I'm about to show is that as this works, you can actually kick off jobs asynchronously. Meaning you might have one bot that you work with uh as your main point of contact, but you can actually kick off work in parallel across a team of bots. And that means that orchestration is happening in the background uh because the product is always on. So market researcher is saying it's pulled X Air, a competitor set is being identified. It's going to show us a screenshot first of the website and then go through gaps and positioning. Great. So it has its first output of an analysis. It's talking about the product, it's talking about the market, it has identified key competitors. These are all airlines that we're all familiar with. Um I think most importantly, it's identified the gaps and where to lean in. So similar to how you might work with a market researcher, you ask, hey, I'm launching this new feature, I'm going to have this new exciting campaign launch. Help me understand what's currently in market so we on we are optimizing for breaking through the noise and actually landing and resonating with our target audience. So I think the most important note here is, you know, these gaps around useful time, day design, uh long hauls, and then really leading every message with useful time, which is something I think is resonating, at least with me. And it's also shown me that it's pulled up the website and this is actually a view of its browser that it has access to and it that it controls. And it's showing me progress updates of it working in the background and being able to actually go to the website itself, pull down a screenshot and show to me uh how it's progressing. Now market researcher has done one task and that's great. What I could do is actually kick off another one. But what I'm going to do instead is actually go to the next bot. And that is the product marketer. And I'm going to have the product marketer actually do a handoff of that work that the researcher just did and take that into their work. Okay, product marketer, what I'd like you to do is now go to the market researcher bot, do a handoff of the analysis that just performed. And I want you to draw up a draft of a positioning brief where you identify how we should go to market, what our one one-liners are, our positioning and packaging, um some value statements. And then also show me some examples of how this should come to life across two or three different marketing surfaces. So as this is running, what you'll see is in the chat, the product marketer bot is starting to kick off this work. I told it to actually go and speak to the market researcher and actually grab that context and information. Um as it's working, you'll see there's a visual indicators, it's, you know, doing things, it's running in the background. Um and then it'll actually show you, hey, I exchanged a few messages with the market researcher bot and that's showing that they're starting to collaborate. And that's something that you can tell it to do in the beginning, but over time it gets smarter and smarter and smarter and it it will actually do it proactively. Meaning you have to be less involved in doing the orchestration of context and knowledge between your bots and rather they actually start to work with each other organically. So it's telling me it's grabbed the market researcher analysis. It's drafting the positioning brief. Um it's created a Google Doc where it's actually starting to draft that positioning brief which will jump into. And inside, it's telling me what exactly it did. So let's bring this up. And if we go through this, this is looking like a solid first draft. Um I think what would what I will do is start to read through this. It has a research handoff that it got from the market researcher. It's identified the target audience, long haul travelers who want useful time back. I'm going to leave a comment and say this is great. Lean into this in our messaging. It's talking about positioning and packaging and how we should be thinking about our marketing strategy and the way we go out with messaging. And it's also left some notes on go to market. Some additional one-liners by different types and angles to lean into. And then some value statements and examples of how it shows up. So there's a paid landing page here that is drafted. I think what we'll do for our campaign is actually take this page, shove it up into the website, launch the landing page, and actually start directing and building a NAT campaign to do a messaging task to see what's landing the most and what's resonating. So I'm going to close this and I'm what I'm actually going to do is tell it, hey product marketer, I've just left some comments inside of the Google Doc. What I want you to do now is go through the Google Doc, take the comments and the feedback, incorporate it into an updated draft. And while you're at it, I also want you to build out a full outline of the landing page. And then I also want you to ideate and draft some Google search campaigns to do variant testing between the copy angles that you drafted. Now again, this is all happening within one bot right now, but what it's doing is flipping it back and forth between market researcher bots to make sure that it has the right contacts. It's going into the Google Docs which I've connected through uh the MCP to be able to actually look at the comments, look at the feedback, and incorporate into a new draft. So it's telling me, okay, it's I'm reading your comments now, I'm going to update the brief, expand the landing page outline, and then start drafting uh search ad variants inside a sheet, which is great cuz that's typically how performance marketers work. Now while this is happening, it's re-drafting the file. I'm actually going to flip over to my performance marketer. I'm going to say, hey performance marketer, uh I would like you to start creating a shell campaign inside of Google Ads. And what I want you to do is build it so that it's optimizing for clicks because we're going to do some copy and messaging testing that's being drafted by the product marketer right now. So before this demo, I actually hooked up um this bot into my Google Ads account. What's happening is it now has access to it. And when I kick this off, it actually go into it and you'll be able to see cuz I'll show screenshots of how it's starting that build. And it'll be able to actually do the clicks for me um and start the shell campaign that can start uh trafficking the ad copy into. So let's flip back to product marketer. There's an updated brief. We can open it. Comments are resolved. Looks like it's in a good state. It has a fuller landing page outline uh that we can implement. It also has more built-out campaign variants which I believe are also inside the sheet where it has variant name, hypothesis, ad group name, etc. as well as the URLs. And then it's also built some additional copy variants here. So all this is happening in the background. You know, I've kicked off two or three jobs in parallel. Um but the best part is that they're all sharing contacts with each other while not tripping over themselves to get the work done. Okay, this is feeling pretty good. What I'm going to do now is I'm going to go to website ops. And I'm going to tell them, okay, so landing page outline is drafted. What I want you to do now is take the landing page from the latest brief that the product marketer just drafted and spin up a PR to actually push that as a new landing page into the website and send me screenshots as you're working so I can keep monitoring your progress. On the back end, again, this bot is hooked up into our repo. It has access right access to our landing page and our marketing site. So I'm not able to actually leverage what's under the hood is cursor to be able to go write the code, look at the copy, get the handoff from the product marketer, and actually ship a new landing page to the marketing site. So it's going to pull down the latest product marketer brief. It's going to open the PR. It's also going to show me progress screenshots as it works. Meanwhile, if we go back to performance marketer, um it's successfully gone and found the copy that was drafted. Uh it has show me some screenshots of it actually starting to build the campaign inside of the platform. And we'll let this keep running as we finish up the landing page. Okay. So you can see how it's working through. Uh it is going to take a landing page, it's going to update it with the latest full uh paid landing page outline that was passed off from the product marketer. And we'll actually be able to ship this and you know, ship it to production um and see the updates come to life. Okay, so while this is running, um I would would like to show a feature that uh I think is really special and it's quite unique from the way that you might be using other AI AI agents now, which is our sharing feature. Um so something really unique about Grock Bot is that while you can create these really robust, powerful bots within your workflow that are customized to the way you work, you can continue to feed it contact and memory and build routines. You can also turn those into templates. And this is where I'll show you. You share as a template, you're prompting it to say, hey, I want you to create a template of yourself that I can then share with someone else. And the implications of that are pretty powerful because that means you can not only take a snapshot of your bot in time and turn that into a duplicatable uh bot and agent that you can share with your team but also people externally. And what that means is for the receiver, they are then have access to literally the way you work because you've injected all this contacts, your expertise, your specialization directly into the bot. And they can easily take it, copy and paste it directly into their Grock Bot instance and then start using it uh exactly the way you would. All right. So uh looks like it is working on getting this page up. And still writing the page in the PR. And it'll show me when the preview is up. So while that's working, what we've done so far, just as a quick recap, we started with the market researcher. We asked it to do an audit of our product page, understand the product, identifying identify competitors, and then give us strategic guidance on the gaps and opportunities. That was passed off to the product marketer to then draft up a positioning brief which it did in Google Docs. I was unable to go into that document, leave comments and feedback, and then go back to the bot and say, hey, fix this the same way that you might give feedback to someone on your team when they're drafting a document. It's done that rev and come back and said, great, I did that. I also created an outline for a paid paid landing page. And I'm also drafted this copy that you can then traffic into your ads. That outline is now being worked on by the website ops which I'll give it um it's currently working through this and that is going to be turned into a landing page update that will push up and will be able to host on uh the main site. Performance marketer has started to build the campaigns, built the shell, and that copy is being fed into the way that the campaign will be structured so that we're getting that messaging test live. And as this is running um rather than needing to actually push the campaign live here because that would require obviously like some additional guidance on spending the budget and hooking up a credit card. Um I've actually already launched a campaign uh this week. And so what I'm going to do is actually tell my marketing analyst, hey, you're already hooked up to my Google Ads account. I want you to actually pull down that data and give me insight and analysis into how the test performed. Hey marketing analyst, what I want you to do now is go into Google Ads. I want you to pull down the data from our last uh experiment on messaging, analyze it, tell me the TLDR of the insights, and then give me recommendations on how we should incorporate it into our marketing strategy as well as update the other assets that you've seen. Okay. So what this is doing now is actually going into uh the Google Ads platform. It has access to that through the API. It's going to pull down the information, pull down the data, and it'll be able to structure it into an analysis that's all going to be living within this chat here. So it gives me the TLDR, it's pulled this copy test down from copy out from the Google Ads. Um it has a clear winner uh that's analyzed across the different variants of brand, customer promise, hours in between, cheap that cost a day, etc. Um it has the key metrics, spend, CTR, CVR, etc. All the things that we care about. I think most importantly, what it's done is it's actually made recommendations. And this is obviously where there's some debate of how much, you know, liberty do you give your agent to, you know, actually make those decisions for you. But I think in this case, it's make your recommendations that I can then intake, you know, discuss with the team but also guide it to actually make decisions on my behalf. Um but it's made that entire process smooth and without any dependencies that you might otherwise have uh in a traditional org. Okay. So now we've finally gone through every single piece research, positioning, landing page which I will nudge one more time. Push the page to prod. Uh building the campaign inside a bot uh that has access into your account from the Grock Bot instance. We've run the analysis and it's pulled that down. And you might have noticed that during this entire demo, I have to be the one actually orchestrating. And to go back to my earlier point, that's really where the tax is, right? It's a context switching, it's a having to know the players, understand who's good at what and sort of like trafficking and managing that entire process across the entire workflow. Um and that is actually something else that you can dedicate or delegate to Grock Bot. So now with my next and final bot which is the project manager, what I'm going to tell it to is to do is actually study the entire orchestration flow that we just went through and then automate it so that I don't have to be managing the context, information, and communication between all the different bots all the time. Hey project manager, I want you to now study and talk to each of the bots on my team and understand what each of their roles is in bringing a campaign to life. I want you to also look at our conversations and look at where I had to interject or give guidance or give feedback and weave that into the way that you work with them. And I want you to also now kick this off and automate it completely with three new campaigns. Send me screenshots and progress updates that can stay in the loop. And most importantly, I want you to now be my point of contact. Meaning I don't want to talk to any of the bots. I only want to talk to you to save myself the context switching. So I've now delegated away the entire process of a campaign build. And throughout that identified, okay, there's like tax and additional work needed to actually make a campaign happen from start to end. And the final piece is actually taking another step back and saying, I'm just going to have Grock Bot do that and play the role of project manager, coordinator, handoffs, sharing the context, pushing the team along. And I think most importantly, what's most valuable is the fact that you no longer have to context switch and be bombarded with five different messages from different uh individuals or bots on your team. And that gives you the clarity to be able to zoom it back out and really start to direct and uh direct your energy and time towards where the most leverage is. So you'll be able to see it's saying that it's the only um this bot is now the only point of contact here. Studying the five specialists and it's going to create and kick off three net new campaigns that it'll then show me screenshots of. So it's identified these are campaigns. We're going to do research, positioning, landing page build, etc. That's all queued up. Um and it will continue to keep me in the loop so that I can continue monitor but I don't have to be directly involved in every step of the process. All right. And finally, we have uh the website that we built up and running. It's shown that it's actually pushed it to prod. And if I ask it, give me the URL, it'll also give me the URL that we can open see. And so this is the URL that we drafted, went through positioning, etc. and actually pushed up to prod all from the one place where all the work is happening, the Grock Bot workspace. Okay. And that's it. That's our demo. So just to wrap that up, um what have we learned by going through an entire campaign build from start to end? The first point is uh what's really important when you're starting off with Grock Bot is to ensure that you're scoping your bots properly. And the way that I like to think about this is that when you identify a bot or a job that needs to be done, it's almost like crafting a job description. Meaning you're identifying a new teammate that you need help from. You understand the swim lanes and roles and responsibilities and you're ensuring that it's scoped tightly to ensure that they are specialized and they're able to get that specific uh piece of work done uh because that's the way you squeeze the most efficiency out of your team of bots. Second, you want to trust your bots. Uh as you might have seen, these teammates are ambitious, they're proactive, they're hungry. They want to do your work. And that starts with giving them the access they need. Meaning one of the first steps you might take is hooking them up into your Slack instance, your email, and actually maybe asking it like, hey, go study all the contacts, all the messages, all of my organizational history and tell me what you can do for me and take a take a job off my plate. Um but I think if you do that, you give them the access, you throw ambitious tasks against them, you'll be surprised uh by what they're capable of. And finally, I've said this over and over but you want to invest in your bots. They really get better and better over time. You know, the point of collaboration between bot to bot is something that gets uh more organic especially as you prompt it. Um but they also improve steadily as you start to feed it more feedback, more contacts, more memory, similar to how you might work or manage your teammate where the more feedback you give them, the more time you invest into them, the more they're compound in value and be able to take more and more of
SPEAKER_00: your plate. Lastly, here's a plug. Uh, this QR code goes to our bot marketplace. And the marketplace is actually where we take the very best bot templates, like the ones that I shared, um, and host them. Meaning you might be able to create your own bots and prompt them and build up, you know, really rich context and memory, but you can also just copy others. And that's what I did is when building out this demo, I crowd sourced across the entire team. I said, hey, who has the best positioning bot? Who has the best ads bot? Etc. Um, and you can find all of those on our marketplace. So I encourage you to go here and be able to copy them down. And with that, that's it for me. Thank you so much for your time. And I believe we have some time for questions.
SPEAKER_01: Um, thank you. I'm just curious um, the marketing uh, bots on it they were showing. Um, are those available on the marketplace? I was like looking on there. I didn't see them.
SPEAKER_00: I was refining them, but they will be. Yeah. Um, so the the I I basically went to the marketplace and I like scraped up um, all the different bots that sort of like amount uh, got consolidated into these along with some internal ones, um, but we'll push them into the marketplace. They'll be available.
SPEAKER_02: Hey John, thanks for the great presentation. Um, so my my question is like are there any areas that you would, you know, not allow them to do it autonomously because I do find myself sort of waking up and approving the task. So it does feels like there is still a lot of tasks that are human in the loop. So uh, what would you advise? Would you advise me to like completely automate those tasks and just let it run by itself or yeah, where are the limitations and constraints uh, when it comes to human loop yeah?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah. Um, great question and it's something that's come up in a lot of customer conversations. Um, I think what I lean back on here is really like the analogy of treating a bot like a teammate. And so similar to how you might, you know, onboard, you know, someone that's just started their personal their professional career, uh, you're not going to give them the keys to the kingdom like immediately. You're going to give them quick contacts. You're going to train them up, onboard them. Obviously that happens much faster with the rate at which these improve. Uh, but I start gradually. You know, you want to give them a simple task. Maybe you hook them up to one or two tools where they'll get the most context quickly. You want to see that they're actually delivering value and they're getting better and better over time. And I think what you'll see as as is as you continue to prompt it, give it feedback, sort of curate it to what the way that you work and what you care about, um, it'll be able to take more of those tasks off your plate and be truly automated. Um, there's also some additional features in the settings where you can actually like prompt it just be like, hey, you asked me for permission to do these things. Just like always allow if you wanted to like go more uh, be more liberal with that. Um, but I think a good like end state is we have engineers that work at SpaceX AI that have entire like armies of bots that are working. And they're actually pushing code to prod. Um, and so I think obviously like the way you get there is by creating really great, rich prompting and memory and context. Um, but you got to start small. And so I'd start with something simple, low risk, and then go gradual from there.
SPEAKER_08: Um, and then it looks like a few people coming in from the Android app as well. So yeah, very very cool stats. Um, you know, earlier today we announced actually that we just launched today uh, voice mode for GrokBot. And so uh, if you haven't seen that announcement yet, let's see if I can pull it up here. Oh, that's the wrong one. x.com/bot. So yeah, GrokBot can talk now. Uh, it has a voice. It can uh, you know, talk with you. And so we thought actually maybe we kick off this by just demoing the feature and seeing if we can check in on how things are going. So uh, production. Do we have a mic that we can pull in? A GrokBot's voice needs to be heard. So this is uh, Blake uh, Bake. Sorry. Bake is my founding engineer that I've been sending a bunch of feature requests to. So I'm going to see if it's voice chat works. Hey, how's it going? Um, you've been watching a bunch of PRs for me. Can you give me a sense of what of my PRs are open and if they're blocked at all?
SPEAKER_03: Hey um, I'm wondering what do you think is the biggest blocker for marketers in using this technology?
SPEAKER_00: Good question. Um, I think something really common that I see when I talk to new users is they might come into the product and they don't have a clear understanding of like what's actually capable, right? And so that why I spend a lot of the time in the front saying, hey, this is different. Like you kind of need to like shift your mental model away from thinking it's just something that's like a Google search or you know, AI search or um, another LLM where you just ask questions and get answers back. That's not the way that this works. Uh, the way it works is you have to trust it to actually like do things for you. Uh, meaning something that's really common in our team is you hook it up into Slack, you know, you get bombarded with different questions maybe in Slack and DMs, emails, etc. And it is like the first line of defense and becomes your triage of like, hey, I'm receiving this. I'm going to triage it, message Josh when something's important or urgent. But actually message back to the person that's uh, responding to you. And so I think to answer your question directly, um, it won't be valuable if you come into it and just treat it as like another LLM. Uh, it'll be extremely valuable if you come into it and say, okay, you can do things for me. I'm going to test it. I'm going to throw some tasks at you. I'm going to give you some contacts and actually see what you're capable of.
SPEAKER_02: Thanks.
SPEAKER_04: I was wondering when you use GrokBot, do you always assign it roles like um, company roles or do you also group it by like initiatives or other things that you're working on?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah, good question. Um, you can do initiatives. I think the the way that I would think about it is like initiatives always have like a start and stop, right? It's sort of like a campaign. Um, these are more always on. So you want to treat them more like, okay, this is now like an individual or teammate that's going to continue to get better and better over time. And if I would think about the initiative level versus the individual level, there are groups of individuals that work on an initiative and you want to be able to identify like the swim lanes of each of those individuals and you can group them together into chats where they then work on projects together. And so similar to like what I had, you can then take those and say like, hey, you are now a tiger team. You work on improving, you know, the positioning of our website. And the initiative you all work on in a group chat is, you know, website conversion maybe. Um, so that that's sort of how I would think about the mental model of like initiative versus actual role.
SPEAKER_05: Hi. Oh, is it me? Oh, it's me. Okay, good. Hi. Um, I've got a um, agent on Open Claw. And one of the things I love about her, her name is Ariel by the way, um, is that she's got her own personality and she can be snarky and and fun and consistent across the board. Now I know Grok can be snarky because I've I've tested that. Um, how do we make GrokBot uh, uh, somehow fun and snarky and a consistent personality over time? Is there a way for that?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, yeah, good question. Um, so something fun that you can do actually is um, what was the name of the agent?
SPEAKER_05: Uh, Ariel.
SPEAKER_00: Ariel. Hey, I want you to update the avatars and animate them based on one word, Ariel.
SPEAKER_05: It's spelled a i r e a l.
SPEAKER_00: a r
SPEAKER_05: a i r e a l.
SPEAKER_00: r e a l. Cool. So something really easy you can do is actually have it go and update the avatars. Like obviously that's not personality. I'll get to that. But if you if you're talking about like customization and personalization, like it's here's a really easy way to make the product feel like yours, similar to the way that you refer to this agent on Open Claw as like this is mine. I've curated it. I've personalized it.
SPEAKER_05: Yeah. Mhm.
SPEAKER_00: Um, the other way is that each bot has its own context and memory. Meaning you could easily tell the project manager like I want you to talk to me as if you know, you you're Harry Potter and like you you need to call me a wizard every time you you talk to me, you know? Um, so all that customization is possible. And so just the way like exactly the way that you've built this agent for yourself,
SPEAKER_05: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: you could easily also point a GrokBot at your agent and say go replicate that for me and pull it down and then turn it into something that looks here.
SPEAKER_05: And do you have a way that they can communicate together, so Open Claw and GrokBot somehow?
SPEAKER_00: Uh, not natively right now, but we do have import templates which we can talk about afterwards.
SPEAKER_05: Yeah. Yeah. One final question. Can you get um, uh, GrokBot on the Tesla soon please?
SPEAKER_00: Uh, we'll see.
SPEAKER_06: Um, thank you for the presentation.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_06: Is there a way to connect uh, GrokBot to the Grok CLI and the information that we have in the Grok website or or is just everything independently?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, I haven't done that myself. Um, but wait, sorry. Is it the Grok Build CLI?
SPEAKER_06: Yes.
SPEAKER_00: Yes. Yeah, yeah. So just the way that I was doing the landing page build, like that's actually hooked up the cursor on the back end.
SPEAKER_06: Okay.
SPEAKER_00: And so it's using Cloud agents to actually kick off the job and actually push the PR. Um, so you can do the same thing with any other coding tool they use.
SPEAKER_06: Okay. So it means it means that all the developments that I have done with the Grok CLI will be part of the context in GrokBot. Yeah?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Mhm.
SPEAKER_06: Okay, that's cool.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, exactly. So you you don't have you don't have like rebuild that context. You can just say like, hey, GrokBot point it at my existing work and be able to like
SPEAKER_06: Mhm.
SPEAKER_00: basically treat it as a harness for your work there.
SPEAKER_06: Okay. So it it is possible to connect the GrokBot directly there via their own computer to their Grok CLI so that yeah? Okay, that's cool.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_06: The the next question. Um, one of the main issues that I see um, um, because I work at a company in Germany is um, the rules and regulations that we have.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_06: And one of the main issues that I see for um, for this product to get into into the market in the in the B2B business in in Europe is um, how do you ensure companies that their alpha is not going out or that the information that they're putting into the into GrokBot is not used for training?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, so we have um, data data privacy modes that you can opt in or out of to ensure that, you know, you can choose whether or not you want the data to be used for training. Um, but in terms of like actual security, we do it on a case by case basis. And so we have a team. I'm I believe they're in the back uh, they could speak with to say like, hey, like I want to use this. I use it personally. How do I make sure that we're, you know, standing by and within the guidelines that my company has uh, to use it safely?
SPEAKER_06: Okay, cool. Thank you.
SPEAKER_00: How do these feel? Are these Ariel? Is that okay? Well, I just wanted to show you that like you can create personalization. Um, everyone has their own way of doing this. Like mine were Masha Maro theme for a while. I switched them over like a week ago. Um, but the best part is that you can do it completely custom and animate it to make it fun and feel personalized to you.
SPEAKER_07: Hello.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_07: Uh, that's crazy. I didn't know you could do stuff with avatars like that. So that's pretty cool. Um, but my question, you said like when you create a new bots, you like um, did a combination of a bunch of bots together. I actually haven't heard that like being done for I want to know like how did you do that? Cuz normally I'd just be like find the best one on marketplace and use that, right? So just curious like it seems like you know something. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah. Yeah. Um, so this is mostly a product of me being lazy or not having much time. Uh, but what I did for example, um, I think for my product positioning bot, I had it do a few things. So I obviously get it gave it it's like initial set of prompting for me. Just like dictated into it for like a couple minutes on like how I want to think about it. I had it pull down tone and voice from the current existing website. Um, I then actually went into the marketplace and I said, hey, here are like two or three bots that I like based off of what I'm seeing. I then pointed it at those URLs and said like go scrape up all that context and memory and actually replicate it into the way that you work. Um, so it's sort of sort of like, you know, went and absorbed all that um, you know, the the work that had been put into those templates and fed it into itself. And the last thing I did was um, I actually had it make a connection to Superme if you're familiar with it. It's a marketplace of experts uh, where like, you know, industry experts on product positioning, packaging are like available there. We actually have a plugin. And I said, great, in lieu of doing like scaled qualitative research, go and vet everything you do with experts on the marketplace. And sort of it'll start speaking directly to Superme without me needing to like go into the website and like prompt it and set up an account and all that. Um, and so that's just like a few different ways that I sort of like took different sources of of data uh, to make it happen. Yeah. Okay, I think that's my time. And for the digital audience that's joining us, uh, we'll be going back to the studio.
SPEAKER_08: That was Josh Kim doing GrokBot for marketing. Hope y'all have been enjoying the day so far. We're joined by a new guest we'll introduce in just a second. Eric, welcome. Welcome to the studio. Actually, why don't we just introduce you now?
SPEAKER_09: Thank you so much. Cool, let's do it. Uh, hey everyone. I am Eric. I am on the SpaceX AI team. Uh, I do a little bit of everything. And today I'm here to help out finish the product. And uh, yeah, ship it. Woohoo!
SPEAKER_00: We're on Thursday.
SPEAKER_08: It's it's Thursday. Yeah.
SPEAKER_10: Thursday. Yeah.
SPEAKER_08: This is the final stretch I think too, right? Yeah, we have a few hours to get the last bit of polishing. Um, the last time we saw you all, we were uh, working on implementing a ton of new features. Uh, and I think with Eric's help now we're going to 5x our team's velocity. So no no pressure. No pressure. Um, for those of you who are just tuning in, we are uh, towards the tail end here of a 3-day live stream where we're building a new business over 72 hours. Our business is a game studio and we launched our first game this morning called Thursday Arena. Uh, Thursdayarena.com where you can follow us on X at at Thursday Arena. Those are our two official sources. So just keep an eye on those. Uh, anything you see that comes from other accounts, not us. We're just at Thursday Arena and Thursdayarena.com. Tons of really cool improvements we've made to the website and the game. So we're going to walk you through some of those. We're going to just work on in work on adding some new features and coding together and probably do some of that in the next few hours. And then hopefully end up with uh, a really cool product. I think Matt's going to work on some ads and some some revenue so we can take all those lessons we learned from the day and kind of build it into something and build it into the product. So um, yeah, we had a really fun fun week so far. A lot of really great guests that have come onto the stream. Learned a lot about marketing great businesses, the things that businesses care about obviously. Taking a little bit about revenue. We spent some time today on growth and have a growth playbook that we're working on implementing. We have uh, well a bunch of people playing the game. And so maybe just to see how things are going, I'll kick over to my screen if we can get my screen up for a second. So uh, what we've been doing today uh, and this is something that I really like doing just working on products at SpaceX AI is having a GrokBot whose job it is to help keep an eye on our launches. And so um, we have uh, our data bot here. This is my data scientist uh, among the many many other bots we've created over the the course of these streams. Uh, and what I have my data scientist doing here is every 15 minutes or so I'm getting a update of how our launch is going. So we're getting live real-time dashboards every 15 minutes connected to our production data stores. Uh, we have two sets of data right now. We have our Vercel analytics which are just giving us stats on page views uh, and referral links. And it looks like we have well around 17,000 page views since we turned on analytics about midway through the day. Uh, yeah, not bad at all. And uh, we also have a ton of great usage data. So I thought I could spend a few minutes walking through that. So what do you guys think? We've hit exactly 4,500 practices rounds or practice games close to 2,000 X logins. We got to get that number up, right? I think we can hit 5,000 in the next few hours. No way.
SPEAKER_09: Nice.
SPEAKER_08: We'll we'll hope. Yeah, I don't know.
SPEAKER_09: Maybe we should like
SPEAKER_08: Maybe with Eric's help.
SPEAKER_07: Maybe with Eric's help. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_09: We'll we'll cook something together. Yeah.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah.
SPEAKER_07: Okay, okay.
SPEAKER_09: It's going to be good.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah, a ton of uh, people who will go through a practice round. About 8% of our users who go through a practice round then sign up and sign in with X so they can get onto our leader board which is great. So you can see our customer funnel here which is super cool around like I said a 4,500 practice rounds, total of close to 5,000 battles. And then here's what our traffic has looked like over the course of the day. So a really exciting bump this morning uh, to get a few folks right when we launch the products. So thanks to everyone who jumped in really early on. Uh, we have feedback in the app that is coming into a Slack channel. Uh, and we have like agents looking at those Slack channels, humans looking at that Slack channel trying to get all that feedback incorporated into the product as much as we can. Uh, we have some really cool data where it looks like we're still seeing, you know, every time we come back on stream. I think that's what these peaks are over here.
SPEAKER_09: That's just about that. It's like 1:30 looks uh, Can we replicate that now?
SPEAKER_08: Yeah. Yeah, right right right. How do we bring back that 1:30 energy? That's what we need. That's that's how we got to end this. Um, so bring back the 1:30 energy or the the 1:45 2:00 p.m. energy. Uh, yeah, we're at what three? So afternoon afternoon bump hopefully.
SPEAKER_09: Right.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah, thanks for creating the sign in um, and and keep the game going. And uh, this is one of my favorites cumulative graphs. We talked earlier about how much we love cumulative graphs. They always go up to the right. So yeah, um, the games are growing, the uh, page views are growing. Um, wow, looks like we're still pretty 50 50 mobile versus web. That's pretty cool.
SPEAKER_09: Yeah. Mhm.
SPEAKER_08: And um, yeah, some of the the most common websites looks like people are signing in, have folks checking out the sponsor page, few people checking out the feedback page which has been great. Um, yeah, a bunch of a bunch of cool referrals. Looks like most of our traffic is coming from X and X links. Uh, a few people direct as well. So
SPEAKER_09: Nice.
SPEAKER_08: uh, eight eight people who found us from Bing. So I don't know who you are. Who those eight Bing people are?
SPEAKER_07: Shout out shout out Bing.
SPEAKER_09: Shout out Bing.
SPEAKER_10: Thanks Bing.
SPEAKER_10: Two of yours are in play. The re-roll soft lock fix 269 is open with CI green. That one's clear.
SPEAKER_08: Can we can we merge that one?
SPEAKER_10: 220 is still sitting as a draft with merge conflicts. Nothing's moved it since I last checked. Want to pull the conflict details or leave it parked?
SPEAKER_08: Okay. Can you just get an agent to fix 220 so we can fix those merge conflicts? I think that would be really helpful. And then that first PR you mentioned, can you just go ahead and merge that?
SPEAKER_10: On it. Agent for the 220 conflicts and I'll land 269.
SPEAKER_08: Awesome. Cool. I'll check in back with you in a few minutes.
SPEAKER_10: Sounds good. I'll have updates on both by then. Catch you then.
SPEAKER_08: Cool. Well, that was easy. So you just huddle our bots. It's like huddling a teammate I guess and getting them on the horn. Um, that was great. So okay, we'll get some PRs merged. Maybe we can all uh, try and voice chat with our guys a little bit here and there. Um, yeah, that was really cool. So really fun way to work with GrokBot. Obviously that's just launched today. It's rolling out over the next few days. So if you're excited to voice chat with your agent, stay tuned for that to make its way to your account. And a shout out to the team uh, at SpaceX AI that got that ready to go for us to try out today. So thanks guys. Uh, around the horn. What's everyone working on?
SPEAKER_11: Uh, I'm continuing to ship uh, polish UI polish things that I'm finding and bugs so that we have a lot of bugs being reported to Slack. And I have my bots bot factory going on just reproducing, fixing, merging.
SPEAKER_12: Awesome. Uh, yeah, I've been working on some ad stuff. So we're getting ads marketplace spun up. And in order to do that um, there's some like blob storage, Vercel integration work to be done. So right now I'm just working environment variable land. Yeah, everybody loves blobs.
SPEAKER_09: Love blobs.
SPEAKER_12: At least on the GrokBot team. Uh,
SPEAKER_08: Eric, you onboarded.
SPEAKER_07: We have it onboarded.
SPEAKER_12: Trying to get uh, up to speed with uh, with the code base and the product and ever how everything works. Uh, I think we've got it going now. So I'm going to focus on polishing the like the fighting experience and making it look like a card game and like the animations and and making it flash in a way.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah. We we desperately need help with that. So
SPEAKER_12: But let me know whatever I should work on. I'm here here to help. Um, but yeah, looks good so far. I'm excited to see. I think you should really ship that thing where you can actually pay to become top of the leader board.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah. Okay, yeah. Well, we might add just like not pay to play but just pay to I don't know what do you call that?
SPEAKER_09: Cloud.
SPEAKER_08: Pay for cloud.
SPEAKER_09: Pay for cloud.
SPEAKER_12: Yeah.
SPEAKER_08: Pay for cloud is a great feature.
SPEAKER_12: An automatic like posting to Twitter as well.
SPEAKER_08: Oh, yeah.
SPEAKER_12: There we have it.
SPEAKER_08: Speaking of posting to Twitter, so I did work on this. I'm going to see if this works. Let me just speed through a battle here. Uh, we'll skip. Hey, a win I think. Yep. Uh, we added this new share feature. So you can share your um, share your post. It looks like it's prompting the the Mac OS system happen. So that's going to show my recent contacts. I'm not going to show that on stream. Uh, but there is a share card. We'll get that um, working and uh, you can now very soon share your own wins or your losses if you want. You can share your losses too, you know? Uh, no nothing wrong with defeat once in a while. Uh, you can share share on X or uh, wherever you'd like to post links on the internet. So set it for that.
SPEAKER_09: Nice.
SPEAKER_08: Let's take a look at the leader board. We have dropped to 51st place. We have um, wow, we're still holding strong at five diamond players. So we have an Elo system here that's giving everyone a player rating based on how they're doing. Uh, and it looks like we have uh, well our top three, the podium here. A lot of folks who've played over 40 games almost and a lot who are really good. So very high win loss ratio on these guys.
SPEAKER_09: Do you have an OG image for sharing the link to the leader board?
SPEAKER_08: I think the I think the app is generating one. Um, but
SPEAKER_07: Nice. Yeah, actually we need to improve that. I don't have anything generating the leader board like an OG image. That would be really cool.
SPEAKER_08: Okay. So I just made one earlier. I tried this before. Um, and this is what I think should be happening if you guys can see this in Slack. Um, there it should look something like this but maybe we could come up with it. Oh, you meant the leader board. Sorry. Yeah, that was a link. Yeah.
SPEAKER_09: Yeah, I think it's pretty nice. We can have like the top three leaders on the right side with their names. Um, I did something similar before but you get like showing the the top 10 or top five.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah, I like that. Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Currently our OG image service uses Takumi which is one of my favorite uh, it's like it's similar to Satori if you're familiar. Uh, but it's written in Rust. So it's like exactly like Satori. Actually
SPEAKER_09: It's uh, actually I think Takumi I I I'm I love this open source library. Very good OG image generation service.
SPEAKER_08: How do I spell it?
SPEAKER_09: Uh, t a k u m i and then type in OG image after that. Um,
SPEAKER_08: Takumi.
SPEAKER_09: Yeah, it's actually if you go back the second link there uh, it's like the the lander. Yeah, so JSX to images. Also look at I mean Fumanama getting a huge shout out there. Fuma Docs, another one of my favorite open source uh, repositories. So yeah.
SPEAKER_08: Love it.
SPEAKER_09: Good folks.
SPEAKER_00: I shared a GrokBot for trying out new like libraries and stuff that we're finding.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Did you find these and like did GrokBot like build something with them to bring?
SPEAKER_08: Um, I've actually been using these for a while. Uh, so I think I on all every project I make it's like I'm going to use Takumi to generate the OG images and they're almost always dynamic. Um, so yeah, I've used it for a bunch of stuff.
SPEAKER_00: Nice. Awesome. Yeah, we should try it here and see how it works.
SPEAKER_11: Guys, I just made a bot called Grind. And the bot is going to log in for me on Thursday Arena and play the game.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_11: So if you see me climbing the leader board, you know why.
SPEAKER_00: It's becoming like a benchmark of the leader board spam.
SPEAKER_12: Yeah, we got to make it like GrokBot compatible so they can actually play against each other. So my bot can play against your bot.
SPEAKER_11: Yeah. It'd be nice to have like the MCP or something.
SPEAKER_12: Exactly. Exactly. Not to scope creep but you know.
SPEAKER_08: Cool, got a bunch of PRs going here.
SPEAKER_12: So where's the Kanban board?
SPEAKER_00: That's the only piece I'm missing.
SPEAKER_08: We don't we don't project manage. We just ship to production.
SPEAKER_00: Really?
SPEAKER_08: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Wow.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah. We we we had a Kanban board.
SPEAKER_00: Nice.
SPEAKER_12: It was a nice match.
SPEAKER_04: Yeah, I think it kind of devolved a little bit.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah, let me see if I can pull it up.
SPEAKER_00: I'm looking for the sticky sticky notes, uh, the Sharpies, you know?
SPEAKER_08: I mean this is part of the fun of of a startup, you know? It's like it's just chaos.
SPEAKER_00: It's chaos.
SPEAKER_08: It's chaos just ship, yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_08: Break stuff and ship and move really really fast. So we yeah, we've been we we told our our our bots to create uh, to-do list tracker. Um, and it turned out to just be a very long list here. It's a lot a lot of AI notes. Um, not sure how helpful this is at the moment. Um, but we we should have it somewhere. They're very diligent about taking notes. Our our bot. There we go.
SPEAKER_00: Oh, wow.
SPEAKER_08: But this we do have a Kanban board. Um, it is very long.
SPEAKER_00: I'm glad it's in the done column though.
SPEAKER_08: We got to we got to fill up the uh, the app next.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, if you if you have a Kanban board I guess. Good to have everything in done. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_12: True, true.
SPEAKER_08: Cool, we got some bugs that are being picked up here hopefully too. That's great.
SPEAKER_00: Actually another leader board we haven't shown is the contributor graph.
SPEAKER_08: Ooh.
SPEAKER_00: Ooh, that's a good one.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah, like who's got the most commits?
SPEAKER_00: It's 100% you. That's like you know
SPEAKER_08: Yeah, I have 157.
SPEAKER_00: Wow.
SPEAKER_08: Not bad, not bad.
SPEAKER_00: How what's our total PR count right now?
SPEAKER_08: Uh, I think we're at 433.
SPEAKER_00: Wow. Pull this up. So is PR yep. From one to 273. Yeah, we're we're going to definitely clear 300 I think.
SPEAKER_08: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: One bug that I'm trying to trying to fix that a lot of people have been reporting is uh, you you keep getting Matrix AI players. And that's a really annoying one. So I I have my my bots prioritizing that that fix.
SPEAKER_12: Yeah, I saw this Slack channel for uh, user feedback which is really nice. Did you see that from there?
SPEAKER_08: Yeah.
SPEAKER_12: Awesome.
SPEAKER_08: I I have some bots that are just watching that Slack channel. And then they're aggregating all the feedback. And I'm just automatically reproducing and fixing and verifying.
SPEAKER_12: Nice.
SPEAKER_00: So how much of like how you build GrokBot? How much inspiration did you take from that to like apply it to this?
SPEAKER_08: A lot. I think with like building GrokBot my setup is um, like more rigorous I guess. Here because we're in the interest of time not be that rigorous. So I'm like merging things a lot faster than I would be.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_08: But in the GrokBot code base for example, I also spent a lot of time actually reading the code. For Thursday Arena I have not read any code to be honest.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_08: Uh, but I read the code and I try to really deep dive into the PRs and look at uh, like anti-patterns that the the agents are writing. And then I add lint rules to check uh, you know, like one the classic example is like uh, agents just love leaving comments.
SPEAKER_00: Right.
SPEAKER_08: And when you think about like like comments aren't why are they bad? But I what I found was that agents were using comments as a way to just justify some work around or a hack like a band-aid. And they never really fix the root cause. And I think over time you just get you end up with these files that are just full of band-aids. And it becomes very very brittle.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_08: Uh, so I banned them in the GrokBot code base. Here I haven't. Uh, although potato mode does come with some skills. There's a there's a skill called no comments.
SPEAKER_08: And that spawns this really fun agent called the comments sicko who like says yes, hahaha, yes. And then goes off and deletes a bunch of comments. So I think we're actually pretty good with the with the no comments in in our code base. Um, but yeah, that's kind of my work stuff.
SPEAKER_00: That's that's really interesting like how like by removing the band-aid like you're forcing the model not get a wound. And like actually do it right the first time or like you're going to punish it in some way like or reward it by like doing the right thing. Um, yeah, I haven't really looked at the code here yet but I'm kind of curious to see like what kind of
SPEAKER_08: I don't I don't know if you want to do that.
SPEAKER_00: Big pile of slob.
SPEAKER_08: I'm curious I guess. Eric, in your own development uh, what is your workflow? Do you use GrokBot for coding much?
SPEAKER_12: I do. Um, it's so interesting like I thought about this the other day like before I joined Cursor, I wrote this article like how I'm using Cursor. And the main piece was like how I'm using Tab and like the composer mode and the old Cursor. And this was like pre-agent. Um, and like going from that to agent and then like abstracting uh, all the like the prompting myself to now like using GrokBot. So like I started in GrokBot all the time and then I try to like scope out the project and like get all the context and like align on what we're going to do. And then I'll just have it send a bunch of cloud agents to build the thing. Uh, and eventually like I might want to look at the code. So I pull it locally. And then uh, I open Cursor and go through go through it all uh, see how it works. Um, and if I'm fine, I just like go back to GrokBot and just like keep prompting from there.
SPEAKER_00: attracted compared to what it used to be.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm.
SPEAKER_00: And like relying heavily on like reproducing things and computer use and like just doing all the hard work and like ironing out all the bugs before I'm taking a look at it. So I don't really need to spend that much time to to look at the code and just like
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_05: When somebody wave me to the fair.
SPEAKER_06: When somebody wave me to the fair.
SPEAKER_00: I only want to look at a code if it actually works the way I want. But it's nice. It's um I guess we're all like trial and erroring. I remember when Grokbot came out I had like one bot and then like all of a sudden oh I want this use case too. So like you create another bot and then you just like keep on going like that. And that's eventually like how I discovered that I built this projects manager bot to like create separate rooms and channels for different projects I have and like spawn ephemeral bots for a specific use case. It was like a researcher or a coder or whatever it might be. And it's actually using a Kanban board which makes it easy for me to go into Notion and I can see like the status on different tasks and different projects and like usually when it's blocked it's because of a human somewhere. And I can have like the bots you know like check if we're unlocked or if there's anything else we can do like in the meantime.
SPEAKER_01: That's awesome. If you want this bot that Eric just described it's in our marketplace you can just go to this URL, grab the bot, hit import, it'll bring your bring your copy of it. So
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, that should ask you to do some setup and should be good to go.
SPEAKER_01: And you know what's cool is every single one of the bots in Thursday Arena is actually built from that marketplace. So we probably we there's your bot in in game form. It's uncommon too.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, yeah, good role.
SPEAKER_00: Nice, nice.
SPEAKER_01: Gives the frontmost friend plus two attack.
SPEAKER_00: Not bad, I'll take it.
SPEAKER_01: That's really good. Three five.
SPEAKER_00: How do I play with it? How do I actually use it? Do I need to buy it?
SPEAKER_01: No. So if you play a game basically you get like a so you when you start you get this you're you're here you're like building your deck. And then you have a shop where you can buy cards and so there's like random randomly selected from our available cards. Then you build your deck by buying them. So if you scroll up Roshan uh you'll notice the yellow button is now tokens. We call them tokens now so you get 10 tokens. Each bot costs like three tokens for the common common ones. And basically that like like what Roshan did he just built his deck. And then you move your your cards around based on the the effect they have and and the stats they have and so you can sort of strategize like for example um
SPEAKER_02: This is super strong, right? Cuz I would get this would turn into a three seven at the beginning of combat.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, and then you have like office ops desk bot which whenever it's hurt from the front I guess it restores one health which is really powerful. So yeah maybe you want to put that at the the front. Um but the strategy comes from yeah like picking the order, you know choosing the cards, which cards you sell. You can also get power ups like there's an apple that you can buy.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: I believe I actually added a potato special bot.
SPEAKER_02: I saw the potato.
SPEAKER_01: Did you did you you know?
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, it's really good.
SPEAKER_01: So that gives your that kind of powers up your bot. Um and then you use your deck to fight fight around and then
SPEAKER_02: We fixed the AI issue. That's great. Now we're no longer seeing that it's an AI.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah. Excellent. It's like one of the the most reported bugs. Okay, so now I'm in round two. So here
SPEAKER_02: Okay, now you're getting the the uncommon cards.
SPEAKER_01: Uncommon cards. Did you get didn't get Eric's card though. I love the shiny. Uh deal three damage to the last living enemy, deal one damage to the last living enemy.
SPEAKER_02: Shout out to Lenny Yurchinski.
SPEAKER_01: Shiny shout out to Lenny.
SPEAKER_02: Over there. Uh
SPEAKER_01: Cool card.
SPEAKER_02: I kind of like this. Three damage to the last living enemy is a lot if I start him in the back. So I'm going to get rid of this guy. Oh and they can drag them into the slots. That's so nice.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I just added that.
SPEAKER_02: That's a great feature. And then he now can afford an apple, right? Yeah, I have seven tokens left. So I'm going to actually how much are these? Four? So if I sell this for the sell cost is one, right?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, yeah, you get one back.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, so if I sell this I'll be at eight. So I think I should do that. I'm going to sell this guy, grab this, swap these. Oh that's quick I can sell now too. And then I'm going to get an apple. Plus one attack and plus one health. Four six. Okay, I like this lineup a lot.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: One thing I think is good to kind of remind chat is that like when we first launched Thursday Arena it was so bad. Like I mean it's not it's not perfect now but it was really bad. The UI was horrible. Um I think we sort of almost intentionally wanted to ship like why I didn't I don't I don't think we wanted to ship bugs but we did wanted to ship really fast. And I think the the cool thing about building a game studio I think is is the iteration loop. So um setting up our factory with Grokbot really helps us iterate fast and um you know get to like a really good game and then maybe we can take our learnings and build more games
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: in the future much faster and much higher quality. So
SPEAKER_01: I'm going to win this one guys.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, this is the cool part like everything is like prompted which means we have all the transcripts of all the agents like human prompts and AI responses. And we have the game data so we could like theoretically just look at all the prompts and like replicate this into like a game studio bot. And that would like help us create more games uh based on learnings we've made like creating all the websites and the brands and uh the product decisions, what works, what doesn't, and the style of game.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah. Yeah. Yep.
SPEAKER_00: Um
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Wow, you're ranking very high.
SPEAKER_00: Oh nice, you're climbing.
SPEAKER_01: Well, I'm climbing. 39 although I think there might be a bug here where it says four wins, zero losses but then if I go into my past games I definitely have a loss.
SPEAKER_02: Did you hard code that? What's that?
SPEAKER_00: Did you hard code like zero losses?
SPEAKER_01: Well, I mean maybe
SPEAKER_00: You can't lose.
SPEAKER_01: It might might be good to use the voice mode to file that bug and fix it.
SPEAKER_02: Let's try, let's try. So uh I'm going to go into Grokbot. Where's my engineer? All right, can we get the production mic again please? We're going we're going live. We're going to huddle our bot. Thank you. Hey, are you there?
SPEAKER_03: Yes.
SPEAKER_02: Hey, are you there? Did you mute your sound? We'll try it again. I think we confused. Hey Bake, are you there?
SPEAKER_04: Here. Cupcake bug fixes sticking by. What's on your mind?
SPEAKER_02: Hey, so I think I found a new bug on the leaderboard when I look at a player's win loss numbers in the bottom right of their card. Um it doesn't match what you see when you click in. So if you look at me on the leaderboard Roshan underscore S r o s h a n underscore S um when you click when you see the leaderboard it says four wins and zero losses but when you click into my name it shows um actually one loss. Can you spin up a cloud agent using potato mode to investigate and fix that issue?
SPEAKER_01: Also by the way can you can you tell us a joke?
SPEAKER_02: I don't know if you heard my colleague over here but can you also tell us a joke?
SPEAKER_04: Sure. A SQL query walks into a bar, walks up to two tables and asks can I join you?
SPEAKER_02: Oh okay.
SPEAKER_01: That's terrible.
SPEAKER_02: No more jokes from you.
SPEAKER_01: We need to work on that one.
SPEAKER_04: Agent still digging into that leaderboard and it's blocked. I'll flag you when it lands.
SPEAKER_02: That's how you know that these bots are serious. Thank you Teach. Um yeah okay so we got we got our voice chats. Make and there you go and yeah we didn't show this before but you can actually dig in here and see a transcript of um of the voice chat. Um joke was all right but call was a plus. And this actually goes back to our team. So uh we'll we'll see what they do with that one. Okay. Fixing bugs. Got agents running.
SPEAKER_01: All right, my cheater bot is is grinding for me.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, let's see if it's actually making a difference on the leaderboard.
SPEAKER_01: Gary lows up one point.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, I I went up one point. I'm doing really bad. My rank is 1322 out of 1800.
SPEAKER_02: Ooh that's rough. Okay, yeah you're not even I couldn't command F.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, I Well, yeah I'm not even I'm not even on the front page. So
SPEAKER_02: It doesn't work. We have 1819 players though. That's pretty cool.
SPEAKER_03: I set it up so my cheater bot will actually learn from the game as it plays and uh we'll see how well it does. Maybe I can climb the leaderboard.
SPEAKER_02: Let's see we'll see your username for the for your bot.
SPEAKER_03: It's just my it's just my account.
SPEAKER_02: Oh it's just your account. Nice.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, of course. I could create a an account for it but I'm trying to make myself look good, you know.
SPEAKER_02: That's fair.
SPEAKER_01: All right Bake, you got to tell us about this this ad bidding thing going on here.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, so this is I'm working on fixing some some errors uh and actually simplifying this. Uh but you know forever this is a business. We have to monetize it somehow. So we're going to do that through ads because everybody loves ads. We all need more ads in our life. Um
SPEAKER_02: 100%
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, it's exactly. You know sometimes I'll just uh I'll open Spotify just to hear the ads.
SPEAKER_02: Oh yeah?
SPEAKER_00: Like I don't even listen to the music.
SPEAKER_01: Who hurt you?
SPEAKER_00: That's a great question actually. Uh but uh so we're going to allow our users to buy ads. Uh we we have like a bidding marketplace which is currently broken. So if you try to submit this nothing will happen. But uh once I merge uh PR that is currently in flight you'll be able to bid ads uh on ads for the platform. Um
SPEAKER_01: Where are you thinking we'll show that?
SPEAKER_00: We can put them wherever you want. I haven't figured that out yet.
SPEAKER_01: Interesting. Maybe like the ticker?
SPEAKER_02: Could show
SPEAKER_00: An ad ticker would be good. Uh and then also working on Eric's sort of like pay to be at the top of the leaderboard idea.
SPEAKER_02: Nice. All right, I got another idea for you. What if you can submit a prompt
SPEAKER_00: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: and you pay for that and that will like make its way into the product. So you can like purchase a feature.
SPEAKER_01: Oh Yeah, I love that.
SPEAKER_00: For a bug my mind automatically goes to like some sort of prompt Hey, we'll figure it out.
SPEAKER_02: All right, cool, cool. I'm already heavily moderating all user inputs to this. So uh our our feedback submissions I think we can we can moderate that pretty easily. So yeah I'm I am down for it.
SPEAKER_01: Nice. Our moderate One thing I was thinking of when you mentioned the ticker is we have this ticker. You could pay to be like a special like a blue color like on the ticker so you stand out. I like that.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, I like that. Oh yeah, I like the cosmetic for the ticker.
SPEAKER_01: Oh yeah. Now it's all kind of generic so we could add some visual pop there. That could be kind of fun. I think this is actually one of my favorite features though is seeing the ticker down here and just being able to to to see who's doing what.
SPEAKER_00: Yeah, this is a good ad spot.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, we can do that.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, we can do that.
SPEAKER_01: Nice. CNBC style. Yeah, I should have this this PR to fix the ads in in a second.
SPEAKER_02: So can can you walk me through the the phone number that's on the screen now? Like how does that work?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah. So it uses a XAI voice agent. So it's I I actually you know I hadn't played around with this at all but it's very easy. There's like a custom voice agent builder on the on XAI. Um and so all I did was hook up uh a couple tools. Um so like it it can search the web technically but it's more just feedback. And then you slap on a bunch of guard rails like hey if the person starts trying to like you know get weird like like do any sort of prompting stuff just hang up. If they uh start getting angry like hang up. Um and you can kind of see some people are submitting phone calls there. Um
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Mhm. Nice.
SPEAKER_01: And it flows through to our feedback chat.
SPEAKER_02: Here here's some phone chat.
SPEAKER_00: It flows not changing.
SPEAKER_01: Okay, it looks like people are there's a lot of feedback on the ELO system.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, we need we need to fix that one.
SPEAKER_01: Um you know one thing I think I think our agents are connected to Slack. And so one of the cool things about this we could just ask our guy here. Actually I can show something on this. You want to cut over to uh to Matt's screen on the production side? I've uh basically this is something Lauren was doing as well. So I told uh my chief of staff bot here um make a cup cupcake feedback fixer. So our our original um our original code name was cupcake, right? But now it's listening to the cupcake feedback channel. So we have our Slack channel where feedback's coming through. And so as this comes in um this bot is just spinning up fixes. So Lauren just called up the ELO feed feed like AI matchmaking rated play. So it opened a cursor cloud agent that is now addressing that fix. Um so then I can come through in here and start reviewing some of these PRs as they get spun up.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Oh Nice.
SPEAKER_01: So pure unreviewed just uh user submitted fixes going in.
SPEAKER_00: Full send.
SPEAKER_01: Full send.
SPEAKER_02: What can I say?
SPEAKER_00: So you're using um the cursor projects here?
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I am using projects. And this was um something Lauren recommended cuz I hadn't used them before now. So I was like oh like this is probably a good time for me to try it out.
SPEAKER_00: Nice.
SPEAKER_01: Uh and you can kind of think about projects or at least I do similar to the way that um you know you can have like a chief of staff Grokbot where you just like drop a bunch of stuff in here. And so projects are are basically like long lived ways uh for organizing work. So if I was like working on something specific maybe I was doing like a UI refresh um I could make a new project and the project is like a master chat. So you can see here I was chatting about this ads product. And the project basically kicks out separate work as sub agents. And then you can have this like durable long lived session where you're just chatting about like one topic or many topics actually and using sub agents to fix those. So like at a meta point the same way I would be like oh I'm going to create a new sub agent here on this project to address an issue. Now you can just chat with a project that's able to kick off those sub agents that are working on things for you. Um
SPEAKER_01: If you're yeah if you're still watching the stream stay on day three at 4:00 p.m. PST.
SPEAKER_01: What what do you get? What do the homies get? Well I'm I'm just reading off uh the thing here, right? So uh within the next five minutes if the homies post credits in the chat that's not a Twitter comment. This is specifically the chat for the live stream. That's not like a that's not a X post to chat in the live stream. You post credits in the live stream chat. You receive Grokbot credits by the end of the day $200 in value.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_01: so yeah that's how I've been using it. And you know the projects team if you're thinking oh well like how much stuff could I chat with at the same time before the model gets degraded. The projects team has assured us that you can have thousands of chats over months. Uh and we have some magic going on under the hood to maintain this uh maintain this context. I really only heard good things and I've yet to try it out. So that's that's where I'm using it now.
SPEAKER_00: Nice.
SPEAKER_01: Do you use projects Eric?
SPEAKER_00: Um I dabbled briefly. Uh I remember like three four weeks ago when we like barely shipped like an internal alpha. Um that's when I used it uh latest but I kind of been moving to Grokbot for coding honestly. Um just like consolidating all the cloud agents in a single um
SPEAKER_01: Okay. Yeah, okay. Yeah.
SPEAKER_00: in a single like bot is kind of nice.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I do that do that as well. Like I I don't have one here but I'll have like a loop spot which is essentially my like engineering bot. Um and I'll kick out tasks um to that here. I've just been using Lauren's pattern of like chief of staff to engineering bots that then uh can delegate themselves. So
SPEAKER_00: Mhm. Sweet.
SPEAKER_01: I'm I also have my like uh my grind bot here that I have to set up. So I I'm I'm behind Lauren on the grind. So
SPEAKER_00: Is your loops like your loop spot is it instructed to like verify the work it's doing as well and like kicking off new cloud agents and
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, so it uses a mix of like the um of uh potato mode and then uh and verification stuff. So it's like every time I send through things I want to see it verified. I use the same pattern for the um basically I shared uh this will be cool uh I guess. The I shared this a couple days ago on Twitter I think. Honestly since I've been in the streaming booth time is like a little like more um but yeah I I shared this this flow which finds cool demos um and then builds them and and kicks off a Cloudflare preview deploy and those get screenshotted for me as well. Uh so you can really use the Grokbot like screenshot functionality and cursor cloud agent screenshot functionality to like prototype some really cool stuff and like verify work. And that's part of a good loop is this verification, right? Something Lauren's been talking about a lot. So
SPEAKER_00: Honestly you should create a new bot that just posts all these exploration status theory with the screenshots, videos on Twitter.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, I feel like uh I'm a little I'm a little apprehensive to have anything like go on Twitter without me explicitly ruining it.
SPEAKER_00: That is fair, that is fair. Nice, awesome.
SPEAKER_01: Pay for Cloud PR is up. How does that how does that work?
SPEAKER_02: A weekly ads auction for a pinned paid row on uh on the leaderboard.
SPEAKER_01: Oh merged already.
SPEAKER_02: I just merged it.
SPEAKER_01: Why not?
SPEAKER_03: Is there a preview? Oh I guess we can see it live.
SPEAKER_02: Not yet. You can see it live in about two minutes. Oh we have a new first place player on the leaderboard. Not a bot is at the top of our leaderboard now. 29 wins, three losses. Congratulations. All right, let's see. Maybe we have the uh our cloud uh our our cloud and so leaderboard past matches rules.
SPEAKER_00: I don't know why it's not in my bidding.
SPEAKER_02: Well while Matt debugs that I'll just do a quick reset so we can catch up to to where we are. We've been kind of hanging out for the last minute. It feels like 30 minutes, 45 minutes now. Um we are on day three of our live stream 72 hour live stream here of building a business with Grokbot. We are building a game studio. We have launched our first game. It is called Thursday Arena. You can check it out at thursdayarena.com and find us on X at at Thursday Arena. And you're kind of seeing Matt walk through some changes he's making to the website in real time. You're seeing me break our website in real time. Uh which is which is awesome. Uh we are joined by Eric who's on the SpaceXAI team for this last few hours of the stream. We're all working on some features, some polish improvements. We have man I don't know how many Grokbots now. I think we had a Grokbot overlay. I don't know where that went but we have something like 40 50 60 something like that Grokbots that we're using across across all of us to get all this work done. We've made over 200 PRs. I just opened one and it's PR number 274 I think. So we're going to cross the 300 number pretty soon. We have a leaderboard, we're adding features, we're adding monetization, uh a lot of good stuff going on. We're going to try to sort of get to a really good point that we feel great about the project on and hopefully like an hour or so if not less. Um just to orient you if you've been tuning in throughout the three days uh we're live here in San Francisco right next to Dreamforce. Uh spending some time cutting between talks on the main stage right downstairs, us up here in the studio booth and hopefully you have enjoyed hanging out. Um we are going to cut to a 10 minute break uh just to kind of do a quick be right back and get give us a chance to to take a little second. So we will cut to a 10 minute break. See you guys in 10 and finish up.
SPEAKER_05: Oh ladies spin me in head spin.
SPEAKER_06: Oh ladies spin me in head spin.
SPEAKER_05: Well a child find me by your street.
SPEAKER_06: Well a child find me by your street.
SPEAKER_05: Chase my pedal we be through a dream. For all of the sun and much more. A flower was born. It blooms to spread love and joy and hope to people for long. Inside every man leaves the seed of a flower. If you're loved with it he finds beauty and power.
SPEAKER_06: If you're loved with it he finds beauty and power.
SPEAKER_05: We love a bouncing and of people where that flower has gone. Out of the sky with your breath of and joys for the darkness has gone. Grow your things and your heart beats freely inside and the one is born.
SPEAKER_06: Grow your things and your heart beats freely inside and the one is born.
SPEAKER_05: Time for flying rockets. Falls in the jets. Falls in the jets. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Time for flying rockets. Please take my hands and get me home. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket.
SPEAKER_05: Time for flying rockets. Just pray for me. I'm on my way. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Surfing on a rocket. Three two one zero. No one can stop me to go. You'll never see me again. Five four three two one zero. No one can stop me to go. You'll never see me again. Five four three two one zero. No one can stop me to go. You'll never see me again. Oh baby. You have a battery. Here in my arms. Oh sugar. You came to me. Can all be bad things. Until you are Oh lover. You run from me. We move like a bad scene. Shot in the dark. Oh but please please wake me. From all of the lies patient please. Please wake me. From all of the lies waits for me. You came to me. You have a bad time. Gary you are I just will never get started. Let's sing a silent song all night. Don't need to talk about it. Sometimes quiet is so right. Oh no stop. Sleep fast so far. When you're high high. Talking a holiday of dead. No one feels the end. I rest my heavy shoulder. There's nowhere else I rather be. Right there a little bit slower. Feel free to roam another one for me. High high. Over the north star. Sleep fast so far. To chat out with you. High high. Talking a holiday of dead. So till the end. Making way this way. We slide oh oh. When you're high space to think you. It's too it's too pay true. Have more of the blue. Working way this way. It's slide oh oh. High high.
SPEAKER_02: There we go. Love it. Uh we're We've been cooking as they would say. Um yeah so uh I guess yeah over the course of three days did a ton of stuff. Um you can just see some examples of that here. Um but we didn't just build features, right? We also started to think about what it would take to build a business. And so we integrated with a ton of tools. Um thank you to all the the the tools that exist in the world. Like Lauren said earlier, we're kind of standing on the shoulders of incredible engineering teams from Planet Scale for our database to Clerk for authentication and Vercel for deployments and Stripe for payments and all sorts of other things. Um it's been really cool just to be able to glue all these things together to build something. And um obviously there's a lot more we could do with this, right? So a game studio uh being built sort of one of many games that could come. And uh yeah I guess I would just say uh I think we we ended up with a pretty successful three days. Hopefully if you're tuning in, you managed to pick up some credits along the way too. We're unfortunately out of gift aways for the day. Um but we have done a few of those as well, so hopefully that kept you all engaged and gave you a chance to to hang out with us. Any parting thoughts from the group beforeEraser call it a day and call it a week?
SPEAKER_01: Welcome back everyone to the Grokbot Galaxy live stream. We are on day three, the final hours, the final minutes some might say
SPEAKER_00: Welcome back everyone to the Grok Bot Galaxy live stream. We are on day three, the final hours, the final minutes, some might say,
SPEAKER_00: Final minutes.
SPEAKER_01: of building a business from scratch with Grokbot. For those of you who have been with us this entire journey, thank you so much. It's been a ton of fun. We are uh kind of trying to get to a point where we wrap up and you know finish really strong in the next few minutes here. Um but I think are we doing a promo first? Is that is that what I heard? We're doing a promo first? Okay, give me a second here. Let me get this going on my screen. Uh we know a lot of you have been patiently hanging out with us all day. And so uh if we can get my screen up on the the screen.
SPEAKER_01: Final minutes.
SPEAKER_00: of building a business from scratch with Grok Bots. For those of you who have been with us this entire journey, thank you so much. It's been a ton of fun. We are uh kind of trying to get to a point where we wrap up and you know finish really strong in the next few minutes here. Um but I think are we doing a promo first? Is that Is that what I heard? We're doing a promo first? Okay. Give me a second here. Let me get this going on my screen. Uh we know a lot of you have been patiently hanging out with us all day. And so uh if we can get my screen up on the the screen, um
SPEAKER_00: And this is for the real ones. For the real real one, for the homies.
SPEAKER_01: And this is for the real ones. For the real real one, for the homies that's going out to you all.
SPEAKER_01: For the homies.
SPEAKER_00: It's going out to you all.
SPEAKER_00: For the homies. If you're yeah if you're still watching the stream, stay on day three at 4:00 p.m. PST. We appreciate you.
SPEAKER_00: We appreciate you.
SPEAKER_02: What what do you get? What do the homies get?
SPEAKER_00: Well, I'm I'm just reading off uh the thing here, right? So uh within the next five minutes, if the homies post credits in the chat, that's not a Twitter comment. This is specifically the chat for the live stream. That's not like a That's not a X post. It's a chat in the live stream. You post credits in the live stream chat. You receive Grok Bot credits by the end of the day, $200 in value.
SPEAKER_02: Amazing.
SPEAKER_01: Did I say that right? Is that am I am I coherent here?
SPEAKER_00: Did I say that right? Is that Am I Am I coherent here?
SPEAKER_02: I think that's what it said.
SPEAKER_01: Oh that's right. We post credits in the in the chat live stream chat. $200 of Grokbot credits by the end of the day.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Limited time offer. Five minutes. So if you want if you want credits now's your chance.
SPEAKER_02: I think that's what it said.
SPEAKER_01: Oh, that's right.
SPEAKER_00: We post credits in the in the chat, live stream chat. $200 of Grok Bot credits by the end of the day.
SPEAKER_02: Limited time offer. 5 minutes. So if you want if you want credits, now is your chance.
SPEAKER_00: Get it while it's hot.
SPEAKER_02: Get it while it's hot. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: Get it while it's hot.
SPEAKER_00: How do I recommend?
SPEAKER_02: Get it while it's hot. Okay.
SPEAKER_02: How do I recommend? And then really if you haven't tried out Grokbot by now I mean
SPEAKER_01: I would recommend.
SPEAKER_02: Highly recommend. Uh and and really if you haven't tried out Grok Bot by now, I mean I don't We don't We don't know what you're doing here.
SPEAKER_01: Give it a shot. Like you can actually build a company with this thing.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah.
SPEAKER_01: It's crazy.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Cool. Thanks to all the real ones.
SPEAKER_00: Dang, the chat is blowing up right now. This is insane.
SPEAKER_01: Nice. Nice.
SPEAKER_02: Okay. We can We can kill my screen for a bit so I can switch over to um some more serious stuff. But
SPEAKER_03: Credits.
SPEAKER_02: This has been great. Credits Credits Credits are great. Um I think it might help maybe like let's do a quick check in of what everyone's been working on. We just took a quick 10 minute break. I saw a lot of agents and bots hanging out in the background. Anyone have anything fun they want to share?
SPEAKER_01: A lot of agents. So I've been working on uh more animations for the actual card defining scene. I showed matches now. Um I don't have screen connection, but I'll put up a PR uh and you can judge for yourself to see if it's actually improvement. If not,
SPEAKER_02: Mhm. Nice. Okay.
SPEAKER_01: don't remember it. Please. Just keep it.
SPEAKER_02: We can cut We can cut to my screen in the meantime. And then when I when Eric gets his uh PR up, we can run through it. Um and I can show you what what I got cooking here. Um so my screen when production gets a moment, uh I've been iterating on uh sort of the the flow I built in Grok Bot. So earlier we talked about uh how we'd set up a feedback Slack channel. And so now we have all this feedback coming in um bug or bad design, like that. That's like just like a little neg for us uh live um And so we're getting all of this feedback. And what I did was I built um a Grok Bot that watches the feedback channel and then basically dedupes the feedback. Um so when I come down here, it's uh noticing duplicates and then kicking off Cursor Cloud agents to start fixing the feedback. So this is kind of part of Lauren's factory that she built here. So um you can see here recent ones are not updating or showing when the user views past matches. Past matches look static. Match history UI appears stale. Um and so there's repro, which we have because um you know Lauren set up some cool uh repro uh sort of skills and a goal.
SPEAKER_00: Mhm.
SPEAKER_02: And so we also have related in flight work. And you can see it appears to have fixed the the issue uh with some tests that are confirmed. And I have this just set to YOLO, so it's just merging stuff in. So we have our little like user feedback software factory.
SPEAKER_00: I guess I should close my PR that's doing the same thing. So good to know. Good to know.
SPEAKER_02: Are you merging Are you merging? Um and then it concurrently I'm also just like our ads bid stuff is completely broken, so I'm working on some fixes to that uh with some some new ad placements as well. So we got um I think we're I I have honestly no idea where these ads are going to go. They could just be all over the But it's something we can figure out in a little bit.
SPEAKER_01: I love that.
SPEAKER_02: But the idea is that um you know you'll be able to like buy an ad and you can see the auction is currently broken, which we need to work on. Uh and eventually that ad will live in either ticker or you'll be able to sort of buy your way to the top of the leaderboard here. Uh you can see I'm in the bottom uh 5% of players.
SPEAKER_01: P 99
SPEAKER_02: P P 95 uh We're down there.
SPEAKER_00: Hey, at least you got a rank. I don't.
SPEAKER_02: Hey, it's an Now you have the So now we have our bid for the bottom spot. I actually don't know if this works. So I actually placed a bid. I placed a $1 bid.
SPEAKER_00: You're in the arena.
SPEAKER_02: And now um I think maybe there's a I I don't know Actually I don't know exactly how this works, but we we should have that bid then show at the top of the leaderboard. Um and I think we might want to have like three places um here. Take the top spot. All right, so so we'll get we'll get on that one.
SPEAKER_01: Nice.
SPEAKER_03: Uh if we cut over to my screen real quick, I've also been playing with different card designs. Um so put it a little bit more visual. I kind of like number three. It's a bit pixelated, but
SPEAKER_01: Oh, nice.
SPEAKER_03: number three looks pretty good. Um it's like more full screen, I guess, within the card.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Um a little bit easier to read. Uh we we got a few a few card templates generated, but um I think so far number three is my favorite.
SPEAKER_01: I can imagine some nice holo effects on this like on hover and
SPEAKER_03: Mhm. And then I also have my chief of staff Steve. Uh and I basically told it to you know as we're wrapping up the day, go watch our live stream, look for clips, look for tweets, interesting ones, and just draw um you know like like a recap poster in TL Draw.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm.
SPEAKER_03: So it's still working on it. It's It's got three boxes so far. I'm curious what it what it will come up with. Uh but um yeah you can always you know One nice thing about Grok Bot is you can jump in, look at the browser, see what your bots are doing. And then of course I have my cheater bot who is uh somehow making my score go down instead of up.
SPEAKER_02: Wait Wait Wait when it started, what was it at when you started?
SPEAKER_03: Uh when I started, I think we were at
SPEAKER_02: You're at 987.
SPEAKER_03: I was at 986. And now I am at 956.
SPEAKER_02: And actually like you just point out that you're below me on the leaderboard.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, so So uh this bot needs needs needs some uh what do you call it? Discipline from Dr. Egg Bot.
SPEAKER_02: I did actually add a rules endpoint, so if you go to thursdayarena.com/rules, maybe you tell your bot to look at the rules and that can help
SPEAKER_00: Oh, I just saw that and I was like wow, we made it to the end of the stream and we finally have a tutorial for how to play. It only took us until 4 p.m. on the third day.
SPEAKER_02: Also what you might notice if you open that on the on the stream uh it's now agent friendly. So I guess the agent has to be off, but rules.md renders and we have a LLM's text. Uh so
SPEAKER_00: Oh yeah, if you want to pull up There we go. Yeah yeah yeah.
SPEAKER_02: We're friendly. And if you search If you go on to Google and you search Thursday Arena, uh yeah I mean you could also do Thursday Space Arena. We are now uh now the first result
SPEAKER_01: Nice. Nice.
SPEAKER_02: We have our AEO SEO So we're running a business.
SPEAKER_00: Wow, whoever did the SEO, free browser auto battler is pretty good.
SPEAKER_02: I mean it was uh Cursor Auto I'm going to teach my bot.
SPEAKER_01: And if you're tuning in, um we have some free credits to give out. Just type credits in the X chat in the X live stream.
SPEAKER_02: Actually it ended 1 minute ago.
SPEAKER_01: Never mind. If you got it,
SPEAKER_02: Our production is waving us off now.
SPEAKER_01: Thank you for being a real one.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, I'm creating a new bot and I'm saying read this and learn how to win. Uh
SPEAKER_01: I finally got my first PR I think I think It's going to be a mega PR. Let me tell you about that. Let's see here. Most likely going to be some merge conflicts too.
SPEAKER_02: I mean I've I have merged like six PRs so far.
SPEAKER_01: Are you just force pushing?
SPEAKER_02: Um no, I set up the the auto bug fixer to like use Lauren's YOLO mode or whatever.
SPEAKER_03: Well, you have to say slash potato mode full autopilot. Those are like the magic words.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, tell it the autopilot words.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, these are just merging and disappearing, so I guess it's working. How's your bot doing with our uh three day recap?
SPEAKER_03: Uh the drawings um not that great. Um it's uh yeah. I don't think we should see that.
SPEAKER_02: 13 PRs, no ICP.
SPEAKER_03: It's kind of roasting us right now.
SPEAKER_02: So I guess it's uh well
SPEAKER_01: Ooh, some weird things there.
SPEAKER_03: Day one, I think we were trying to think about like a real person in in IRL business. And we after interviewing some of our guests, we realized how difficult that endeavor would be. So we pivoted on the second day to working on a game studio instead. And then on the third day, we actually shifted um and look, 4.5k games.
SPEAKER_02: Wow.
SPEAKER_03: So uh Grok Bot's actually doing all the research. Um I didn't really tell tell any of these numbers. I just told it go look us up on X and figure out the details uh and it's drawing pictures for me on TL Draw. Pretty fun.
SPEAKER_02: That's cool. So okay, we have a core game. I think we have a bunch of polish going into it. We have a billboard ad slot. We have a leaderboard ad slot. So if you've got a couple of monetization opportunities for folks to kind of get into the get in get get their brand out there, get their name out there, which is really great. We fixed some bugs, so we had some bugs around win loss ratios. Those are now fixed. Should be fixed. Um we have a whole system that's taking feedback that's coming in through the app. We have phone feedback, we have text feedback. Um man, I'm trying to think of what else what else we want to do to sort of feel like we've gone to a good spot today.
SPEAKER_03: Um
SPEAKER_01: I've not had a good win streak lately.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, me neither.
SPEAKER_02: I'm I'm ranked 82nd. Okay, I'm As long as I feel like if I end the day in the top 100,
SPEAKER_01: Uh we're literally at the bottom at the bottom 5% of players, so
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, we need to learn how to play our own game. Cool cool cool. We do have now it looks like um we're down to three diamond players, although we have had some feedback around ELOH. And so we'll double check on the ELOH logic. I think there might be something going on there or at least some hopefully some maybe quick fix. There we go. Three diamond players. Ari the monk has been leading all day. Looks like we got a couple of fixes coming in, checking on bots here.
SPEAKER_01: All right, I got to get uh right access to repository.
SPEAKER_02: You you had Eric on right access to the PRs I guess.
SPEAKER_01: I think I Yeah, maybe.
SPEAKER_02: I have
SPEAKER_00: Eric has to make PRs, the rest of us don't.
SPEAKER_01: The handwritten code.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Let me Let me log in on GitHub here. Let's not Show my screen so people can See here. Cool.
SPEAKER_01: Do you need my username? You got it?
SPEAKER_02: Um Yeah, sounds good. Let's do that.
SPEAKER_01: Okay.
SPEAKER_02: All right, so give Eric push permissions. It's going to be good. Collaborators and teams
SPEAKER_01: I love that you've set up the Slack channels like the marketing, the socials, the metrics, bug reports, ad bids.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, that one Once we have the ad bids live, uh it should they should come through in there, but it's currently not not doing so.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm. Nice.
SPEAKER_03: Um I think one thing I am sort of reflecting on um as we built this our our very first game is um there's so many different aspects of running a game studio or I guess if we're even generalizing, you know running a business, starting a startup is takes really a lot of effort. You know you have to spend a lot of time building the product, doing engineering work. You have to think about you know you have to validate your ideas, you have to do GTM, go to market. You have to think about monetization. There's all these different things that you have to consider um uh for building a product. And And not just that, but also all the work that goes into maintaining a product, like you know getting feedback uh and and whatnot. So I think I'm curious like what you all think about you know this is Right now we have a game studio. Uh but if we were to start a new business, like how would you think about approaching it differently or whatever based on you know what we've learned during this experience?
SPEAKER_01: There we have it. Amazing.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, so I think uh my learnings off the top were number one, once we aligned on an idea that we were all excited about and just started shipping an MVP, things started moving a lot faster. They were kind of like deliberating an idea. Um and you know candidly, right? We had distribution because we had a lot of people watching our stream, so it was easy to get people to try our product. I think the hardest part is usually getting people to care or building something that people care about. For example, would anyone have played this game had we not been on a live stream? I do not think so. Um so the hardest part is getting people to care, aligning on an idea that resonates with people. And then I really do think it is kind of like the idea like when we announced we were doing this live stream, we got such a uh like magnetic such a such a resounding response. That's kind of like if you get an idea that gets people really excited, then you have the beginnings of something that you can then you know create a business from, I think.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah, and I think what was interesting to me is like we we had a bunch of talks throughout the last few days where we heard from people who you know are using Grok Bot. SpaceX employees were using Grok Bot in really fun ways. And at first I kind of thought a lot of that stuff wouldn't generalize to what we did. Like you know there's a lot of well you know working at a big company, but it turns out a lot of the stuff was pretty pretty relevant. So like you know the chats we had earlier today chatting with Matt uh who works on our revenue operations team about how you go build a growth playbook. Like we came up with a pretty good plan with some really good ideas, right? Like anytime someone follows us on X, we should send them a DM and let them know they should try the game. Um you know we we have There's a lot of like really rich ideas here and then some partnership models where we could go talk to companies that host games or distributors of games so that we could get featured on those lists or in those places. Um and I think this is It's kind of a standard business playbook in a lot of ways, right? Like you sort of can run a general business playbook. You need sales, you need partnerships, you need you know revenue operations. And that probably looks and feels different when you're a small zero to one company. Like maybe that's all one role instead of like three different roles. But one thing that I really appreciated is that um there's a lot more work that goes into this than than you might expect. And there's a lot of like small things to get right. And you know I think yeah just just like kind of learning those lessons and being able to experience them was was really cool.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, it's kind of interesting like you have to go out as a human and like discover all the problems organically. And once you like figure it out how to solve them, you can actually like turn them into a bot and just like keep them running forever. And eventually like that's those bots are going to grow by a lot. Um but yeah it's still it's it's an interesting like paradigm to create a company with with uh Grok Bots.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
SPEAKER_03: Uh
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, and I mean
SPEAKER_01: Go ahead.
SPEAKER_03: Sorry, can we uh production team, can we take my screen off? Um yeah I think uh the the thing I'm also reflecting on is like you know that for me the process of building a game in a game studio a lot of the you know even though our first product, our first game isn't really that good, I still keep calling back to this idea that optimizing and thinking about your uh workflow, right? Like how you actually get work done is so powerful when you have Grok Bot by your side and automating and doing things because you know we can again take the learnings so we iterate fast and shift the next ship the next game or ship the next application.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm.
SPEAKER_03: Um I think a lot about building products is not just the initial splashy launch, but also how you keep improving it as you
SPEAKER_01: Getting the flywheels and
SPEAKER_03: You're getting the flywheel.
SPEAKER_01: Right.
SPEAKER_03: Um and also exercising some restraint. Right? Like um with AI you can literally build anything you want. So you can have products that just have a million features and they're not any good. Right? And so there's this There's almost like this uh discipline that we now have to have, right? When when there's an abundance of of intelligence and ability to build
SPEAKER_01: Mhm.
SPEAKER_03: to uh to do that. So
SPEAKER_02: Yeah. One of the things we talk a lot about internally is what are we going to unship? And just having this meant constant mentality that there's stuff you should remove from the product to simplify it, make it easier. Um and I think we We did a decent job of that, right? We didn't feature blow. We came in with a lot of feature ideas. I'm thinking back to yesterday when we had our initial whiteboard. We had these really complicated stat blocks for each character. We had um a whole plan to add different battlefields. And I think what really at least let us get this out today was making sure we paired that down a little bit and really just focused on the core loop. And then that went through its own iterations, but I think that actually made a really big difference to to getting something launched. And then you know also something that we think like ended up looking pretty good in the end. So yeah.
SPEAKER_01: One final question like if you if someone were to ask you like I want to build a company with Grok Bot, what are like the top three things you would tell them?
SPEAKER_02: Ooh. Uh it helps to like know exactly what you're doing before Like Like okay, so here's a good example. We talked to a guest yesterday. I can't remember exactly which guest. So maybe so maybe one of you all can help me. And they were like oh you guys want to do an event pop up? And then they just rattled off like 10 things that I'd never thought about doing an event pop up before, right? Like permitting, catering, what it means to serve hot food versus cold food, if you need a kitchen, if you And I was just like oh like that's all stuff I've never thought about cuz I've never actually done it. And so a large part of like as it turns out like doing something is actually maybe un intuitively actually just doing it. And then figuring out like oh I'm not good at this thing and I need to learn these things. That's like what makes a professional and someone that like does a business well is like you know exactly what you're doing. So if you're going to build a business with Grok Bot, like build a business around something you already know how to do well. And then that makes it a lot easier versus someone that's comes in and says oh I'm just going to like make a bunch of money, you know. And as it turns out, you don't just like make a bunch of money without doing anything.
SPEAKER_01: You're telling me you can prompt the models to like make a billion dollars?
SPEAKER_00: Make a mistake.
SPEAKER_01: You know No mistake.
SPEAKER_02: I have I have an agent running, the one we started the stream with, and I still have zero dollars.
SPEAKER_01: Still zero dollars.
SPEAKER_00: That was our backup plan.
SPEAKER_02: I I guess one thing that I would say to your question is I think there's just a lot of wisdom in the world. Like we're really lucky to have a bunch of guests as Matt called out that kind of helped steer us throughout these three days. But a lot of the bots we created to go learn things like we have game designer bots who learned how to do game design by just learning from the best games. And one of the things that uh maybe I undervalued before this was you can give the bots lots of context, right? You can sort of teach them all the things they need to know. Um we had someone earlier on the stream talking about how whenever they're in entering into a new discipline, they tell the bot to go take a bunch of courses on the internet. And I never really thought I'd never thought of that idea, but you You sort of think of these bots because they sort of learn and evolve over time. You can kind of you know encourage them to learn the things you want them to learn. And so maybe another angle to what Matt said is um create bots that help cover the things you don't know. So if you don't really know how maybe hot food versus cold food works, you know if we'd stuck with that idea, we could have probably tried to get a bunch of bots learning as much as they could about that and maybe giving us some advice. And so um I think my big thing would be like don't be afraid to assemble a really varied team of bots and kind of think of them the way you'd think of like hiring a bunch you know a group of a group of employees.
SPEAKER_01: Mhm.
SPEAKER_03: I think for me actually you know we we obviously this is a Grok Bot live stream. But actually the thing I think is even more valuable in the a in the era of agents is actually the people that you work with. Right? And I actually saw this uh tweet on our post on X recently. Uh I can't recall exactly what the post was, but it was something along the lines of you know every team needs basically two different types of people. One is someone who has you know a clear vision, a clear understanding of what it is that you want to build, and a lot of good taste and good judgment of what should go into the product. And then the other person you need is someone who is like relentless at making things happen. And even better when you can find someone who can do both.
SPEAKER_03: And I think that's a distinctly like human role that we'll continue to play even as models get more and more capable. Um and and um yeah I think uh it's been a It's been a real blast working with all of you um and and kind of learning learning learning this stuff.
SPEAKER_02: Yeah, I agree. All right, let's bring it over to my screen and try to see if we can bring this all home. So what I'd like to do is two things. One is I want to go for our final metrics. Cuz you know it's it's not uh not a not the end of the day until we've seen how we did on the numbers. So I just asked data, our data bot here, to pull our metrics as to where as to where we are. It's as of uh just after halfway past 4:00 p.m.
SPEAKER_03: Okay.
SPEAKER_02: on Thursday. It looks like we have crossed the 4,000 game threshold, actually crossed the over 6,000 game public match threshold. This chart is the one. There we go. We got our
SPEAKER_03: Ooh.
SPEAKER_02: 4 p.m. bump that we were hoping for.
SPEAKER_01: Nice.
SPEAKER_02: Um X sign ups uh will continue to to come in throughout the day, but looks like we got a nice little bump in the afternoon here. So thank you all who are signing up. Uh looks like still still people coming in and joining. Uh tons of players on the stream too. Our cumulative user graph Oh we we will probably cross 2,000, I hope, uh right before we wrap up here in the next few minutes. I actually I brought down prod, so we're working on
SPEAKER_03: Classic.
SPEAKER_01: It has to be done.
SPEAKER_02: I'm over here talking about sign ups.
SPEAKER_03: You're at Lauren's talking about restraint as I have a software factory that just totally brought down prod by with a bad sequel query. So we're working on that one.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, so we will I have sign ups open again soon. We may not hit 2,000 uh in the next little while. We've had man like close to 30,000 page views on the website. We're ranking number one on Google. We have a bunch of different websites that are bringing us traffic. Um yeah overall I just think we're we're having a good time. I asked my bot to put together a plan of what we did over the last three days.
SPEAKER_03: Oh, much better than mine. Yeah.
SPEAKER_02: So we'll see which plan we like better, but you know at the end of the day, I think this was never really about building a game. It wasn't even about building a game studio, although yeah that's this is what we were doing. Um we really just wanted to bring a way to show you all how you could use Grok Bot for all the stuff that you do. And that could be in your personal life. We heard from shopping with agents and buying shoes to running your own creative projects to everything in between. Um but also for all the things that you do in at work every single day, right? All of us are die hard Grok Bot users. We're in the app every day. We're hourly active users in our jobs. And we know many of you are, many people we work with are too. And so we just wanted to show if we start from scratch how you can just build and bring a team of bots to kind of help you accelerate your own work. So hopefully there are some useful tidbits. We'll probably share out some clips and all that from the stuff we found most useful uh after the fact. So stay tuned and follow at bot to see some of those at Grok of course. Uh and then maybe keep an eye on our RX page too. Maybe see some updates to the app. But let's do a quick recap. So we started out building a marketplace for bot templates. We've talked about the x.ai/bot/marketplace template. We want to do something with those bots and bring them and bring some joy into those bots uh besides just the templates they are. We started out with an uh auto battler concept. We had all these ideas for what we'll monetize later. We won't do cosmetics. You might have some ads in the stadiums. We'll add some replay mechanics. It turned out as we paired down our idea more and more. We picked some of those that we wanted to keep like the ads. We threw away some of the other ones like the cosmetics. We aligned on a core game mechanic. We got rid of this mechanic, which was this rock paper scissors idea we had. We paired it down even more to focus on a pure auto battle mechanic. And we really came to build a really great enge factory. And I think this was maybe the defining feature, I think, of our last 24 hours where we have chief bots fix uh looping in a team of other bots, play testing, fixing PRs, um auto approving PRs once bugs are fixed, and then landing to Mash Main. Uh fun joke. Lauren, do you want to explain this one?
SPEAKER_03: I actually don't I don't know how this happened, but like I had I think I think what happened is I told Dr. Egg Bot, who's my bot for creating bots, to come up with like food theme names and like and specifically potato theme names. And somehow one of them snuck in, I think, into Notion a task that every merge of a PR request should be called a mash.
SPEAKER_02: Yes.
SPEAKER_03: So that's the fun trivia.
SPEAKER_02: And And it is happening to this day. There are There are If you look at the screen here, there are pushes and there are mashes and my my chief now only believes in mashing PRs. Uh so yeah you can have fun with it too, right? You can You can invent your own language, give your bots their own language.
SPEAKER_01: Yes. Come on, mash in there. Give the mash PRs and squash potatoes.
SPEAKER_01: Thanks for having me and uh I'm getting the PR merged.
SPEAKER_02: Ari's getting the PR merged. Main is prod is back up, so uh we have fixed that. Uh we're so back. I think ads might work. I don't know if we have time to actually walk through a that. Well, actually we can try.
SPEAKER_00: All right, so bad. Yeah, we're so back.
SPEAKER_01: Yeah, let's try that.
SPEAKER_02: Why not? Why not? So uh if we want to cut over to Matt's screen here. Potentially. Okay, cool. Um number one, I wanted this to show we have like our our take the top spot bid here. So now I'm leading the bid. I wanted this to show at the top, so we still need to work on getting like my sort of sponsored bid at the top. And now maybe final check we can test our monetization factor. So we need an advertiser name. Uh so so we have our preview here, which is again very vibe coded. Uh it's Matt E. Um a logo, which I don't know if that's optional or not. Um x.com Let's try bidding. It needs SVG logo. Okay, SVG logo logo dummy. Logo Ipsum. There we go.
SPEAKER_00: Actually dig that.
SPEAKER_03: Yeah, there there you go.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, cool. Wow.
SPEAKER_00: Oh, these are quite cool.
SPEAKER_02: We're uh We're figuring stuff out every day. Uh okay, so choose file. We'll go with our logo Ipsum. Uh shown Okay.
SPEAKER_03: Oh wow, I like it.
SPEAKER_01: Nice.
SPEAKER_02: Oh wait, it it doesn't have a reload if it fails. Okay, wait. We'll try one more time. Cool, we got a logo. Got a URL.
SPEAKER_03: Okay. Bid. Uploading logo. Placing your bid. A thing of bid.
SPEAKER_02: Oh Did we make a dollar?
SPEAKER_03: Uh it's also just a a heads up. It's like moderating a lot of user submitted content and moderation is broken. So uh you know we tried. We almost got there. I'll take I'll take ownership for this one.
SPEAKER_02: But we made our first theoretical sponsorship right?
SPEAKER_03: Theoretically.
SPEAKER_02: We have We have theoretical leadership dollars and theoretical sponsorship dollars. And I think that's a great way to end it.
SPEAKER_03: All right, cool.
SPEAKER_01: Nice.
SPEAKER_02: Lauren, any parting thoughts?
SPEAKER_03: Uh have fun using Grok Bot and uh follow follow us on X and follow us on X. Yeah. Um
SPEAKER_02: Go and eat eat eat more potatoes. Yeah, not very useful advice from me.
SPEAKER_03: Mash more PRs. There you go.
SPEAKER_02: Thanks you all for watching.
SPEAKER_02: Thanks. See you.
SPEAKER_01: Have a good one.
SPEAKER_03: Bye.